Consider: Can the universe be
justifiably called "infinite?"
Doubtful...
It may not have a discernible
end, but it had a beginning...
And its component parts
definitely have a limited
cosmological shelf life...
Splitting hairs or not,
if history tells us anything
it's that scientists often
make very poor poets...
We're a ship of
fools chasing phantoms;
heedless of what really
underwrites natural law.
Okarin.
Yeah, yeah.
Prologue
to
the
Beginning
and
End
Infiltration commencing.
El. Psy. Congroo...
Over and out.
Place is a mortuary.
Organization stink
is all over this.
Why did we
come here again?
Huh? You're here because
I permit you to be.
Ooo! A time machine? Neat!
Professor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
The good doctor has
beaten us to the punch,
oh devoted one...
He, in his unqualified hubris,
has broken ground on the
invention of the millennium
and I'm morbidly curious
to see where our theories
intersect, if at all. Hmph!
Professor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
Huh...?!
The roof!
Eh...? What the hell?
Is anything not an emergency?
I'm sorry.
I know sometimes it's not,
but this one counts for sure.
These are really,
really rare, and I'm broke.
I look like an ATM to you...?
Too bad so sad,
Greedy Gus... Life lesson.
Awww!
The Reality Principle does like
to disabuse us of our whims...
Case in point:
this one's a dud.
Look...! He's metal...!
Huh?
I don't believe it...!
A metal oopa!
And that's good?
Ahh! You bet it is!
Hhhh... Yes, well. You
would know better than I.
Thank you, Okarin.
"Hououin Kyouma."
Whatever. You're the best.
My name is a matter of--
Your attention, please.
Doctor Nakabachi's
conference is about to begin
in the 8th floor lecture hall.
All who are interested
are welcome to attend.
Printed on the handouts
there in front of you
is more or less the
hard blueprint
for one of mankind's
oldest ambitions...
Of course...
The theoretical scaffolding
begs some explanation.
As I'm sure you're aware,
mainstream science currently
boasts something like ...
Received Mail
Time:
Sender: Mayuri
Subject: My Upa...
"Okay, don't be mad.
I think I dropped my Oopa,
but I'm looking for it!"
Each separate
discipline involved...
"The, inter-dimensional
vectors of time travel..."
Doctor!!!
Save your questions until...
I have none, sir...!
I throw down the gauntlet as
to your "theory's" authorship!
Do you take us all for
babes in the wilderness...?!
Please! World lines?
Kerr Black Holes...?
Two words, sir:
"John Titor!" Oh, yes!
I submit to all and sundry that
you have shamelessly plagarized
the decade-old scratchings
of an internet meme!
Oh please...!
Far from it, my friend!
Titor's so-called theories
are borderline schizophrenic!
Well, you'd certainly be in
a unique position to know...
I wonder if you might indulge
us with a brief overview
of just where
your views diverge?
Excuse us.
H-Hey...!
Seriously? John Titor...?
Guy's got a point.
There's, like,
similarities out the wazzu...
Hmph!
Who in the Hell are you?!
I think that's my line.
Uh... Beg pardon?
'Kay, so...
What were you trying
to tell me back there...?
Earlier I mean?
Earlier?
Quarter of an hour ago.
They let you outta
the nut house?
Hold on a second...
Makise Kurisu...
The published Makise Kurisu...
Okay, that's impressive...
I'm guessing you're a
grunt in some university lab?
Damn your eyes!
What is the
Organization playing at?!
Uh... I'm sorry...?
Look, I just wanted
to ask you about what--
And you're a fool
to expect I'll talk...!
Red Alert. I've been
cornered by an Agent.
Possibly a sleeper.
Certainly illustrious...
Who are talking to?
Fear not. I'll give her
the slip. Somehow. Perhaps--
Uh... It's... not on.
Hahahahaha!
Well...! You are a credit
to your training, madam...
Few discover the ploy...
This phone shuts
off automatically
in all hands but mine...
thus preserving the
integrity of my communications.
Great. You're crazy.
Clearly this is asking a lot,
but I need you to summon up
whatever focus you can spare.
Think back fifteen minutes...
You were trying your damnedest
to tell me something...
And going by the look you had on
your face, it was worth hearing.
Nice...
But don't think to ensnare
me with this gambit...
And rest assured,
when next we meet I shan't be
caught off guard so easily...
Uh...
Very well.
Wait, I...!
Clearly a lunatic... I think
I'd remember meeting her.
Received Mail
Date: 2010/07/28 12:26
Sender: sg-epk@jtk92.x29.jp
Subject: (No Subject)
Attachment: IMV001
Ah! There you are.
Mayuri! Where have you been?
What do you mean? I texted!
My oopa's gone missing!
I wrote my name on
it and everything...
D'you drop it somewhere?
Probably.
Such is life.
Ah! You have any idea how much
a metal oopa goes for on eBay?
We're talkin' ten thousand yen!
Ten thousand yen?!
Yup.
Well don't just stand there!
That lil' bauble could be the
lab's ticket back to the black!
I'm not gonna sell my friend!
Just imagine all of the
gloriously wicked experiments
we could get off the ground with
ten thousand yen in the coffers!
I'm not gonna sell it. Don't--
Whoa...
Get outside!
Uh...
I know you're there...
Holy... Crap...
What's going on?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Hey, Okarin!
Hey you feel alright...?
'Cause you look like
you're about to throw up.
Someone's... been murdered...
The eighth floor...
Looks like someone stabbed Makise Kurisu.
To: Daru
Subject: Trouble
Send?
Wha...? Uh...
What is going on...?
Too-too-roo! Bottoms up!
The Hell is this?
Um. A drink?
No, I mean...
Everyone just disappeared...
They did?
Yes! A moment ago
there were people here!
Really?
Stop kidding around!
You had to have seen it, too...!
Tell me you saw it, too!
I didn't.
This is ridiculous!
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Don't play games...
I know you're watching...
That's right, freak...
It behooves you
nothing to ignore me.
Take a good look.
Quaff deeply from the
trough of Future Shock...!
Allow that wooly brain
to be stricken with envy!
You are speaking to
Member Double-O One...
Lab Founder, Evil Genius and
Mad Scientist extraordinaire...
'Tis I... Hououin Kyoma.
I still think that
Okarin sounds way cuter.
Silence...!
My nom-de-plume is for
special missions only...!
The girl, is known as
Double-O Two. My assistant...
Cosplayer and resident
female... Shiina Mayuri!
Too-too-roo! I prefer Mayushii.
Next up... I give
you Hashida Itaru...
Our... Hack...
Member Double-O Three!
Ugh. It's hack-er.
The way you say
it makes no sense.
These are The Members.
Stop third degree-in'
the lil' guy, will ya?
It's gettin' painful.
Bad enough you yoinked him outta
the eighty percent off bin.
Heed me!
Future Gadget Lab
CRT
TV
Work-
shop
To find us,
pry open the tiny door,
hang a left at
Red Queen's Ersatz Botanical
and we're two blocks up
in the warehouse lofts
just before March
Hare's Haberdashery!
Chaos is our prime directive:
To pitch the world on its ear
via the maddest of
mad sciences...!
If you knew all of this prior,
continue to stare blankly...
Ah-ha! Just as I suspected!
Doff the charade, mutant!
Hey guys, you know what?
I was just thinking how weird
it would be if to Alpacaman,
we're the weird old piece
of discount software...
Maybe we could stitch together
an eight-bit Turing Test slash
First Person Shooter
and find out.
Ooo! And we could use it
on your Two-D girlfriends
to see if they're
really into you.
They're not girlfriends; they're
a harem I worked very hard for.
No one wants to discuss
your den of iniquity.
We were just having
a lively back-and-forth
about the age-old question
of whether or not the world
as we know it isn't just
some high-rez RPG programmed
into existence by a
higher intelligence.
It's not.
How do you know?
Because as a concept,
it's absolutely bunk...
And because every moment
we fritter away pondering
such nonsense we lose
time more fruitfully spent
devising ways to unravel
The Organization's plan.
Hhhh... Oh, yeah. My bad.
Didn't mean to take us
down the rabbit hole there.
Hold thy tongue Hack...!
You are addressing
the rabbit hole's preeminent
denizen, Hououin...
...Kyouma!
I'm sorry, you said something?
Mark me, my porcine friend,
one of these days you'll
despair to have missed
even the least of my utterances.
Exactly why I back up
every insane outburst
in triplicate, chief...
Press chopper's gotta
be on the scene by now...
Special Report
Where did it come from?
A mysterious satellite appears!!
...several sources
independently confirmed
that the impact
occurred around noon...
The object appears
to be a satellite.
As you can probably judge
for yourselves at home,
it's massive.
Okay... Retracing steps...
Mayuri came with me to see Dr.
Nakabachi showboat this morning,
I remember that.
We left the lab
together, in fact...
We were standing in the doorway
of a half-empty lecture hall
when the crash happened...
But then what?
I did?
Yeah. I was right
there with you;
we saw the crash on
the news and you said
"The Organization has made its
move at last," or whatever...
Then we ran straight
there to have a good look.
Canceled?!
How can you be surprised?
You were rantin' sideways
about it this morning,
said the doc got cold feet...
No, no, no!
Nakabachi's lecture started
at twelve o'clock on the dot!
Sorry, dude. You're havin'
a stroke or somethin'.
It was cancelled.
Good thing, too.
They'd be scrapin' you
off the bottom of that
satellite if it hadn't been.
What in the Hell
is wrong with me...?
Has The Organization been
tampering with my memory?
Ah! Of course...!
It's absolutely clear!
Stein's Gate has chosen!
And here we go...
Another reference
no one gets but you.
Consider your audience
once in a while, huh?
Daru! Future Gadget #1!
Alpacaman's mad.
You changed the channel on him.
Here.
Thank you.
Damn you, Mr. Braun!
Your shoddy equipment
will be our death.
What'd you expect?
He gave it to us for free.
Hack! Hoist this fossil!
Give the hack thing a rest...
And no: it's a sauna out there.
Just 'cause I've got
some meat on my bones
doesn't mean I'm,
like... strong...
Mutiny!
Mr. Braun...!
Hey. It's Mr. Tennouji or
it's nothing. I told you.
I require repairs...
Now... Or else...
Huh? The Hell you
do with it now...? Ugh.
You psychos screw up everything
you lay your damn hands on...
It'll be a thousand yen.
Ah! That is outright
extortion, sir...!
I will not stand...
I could always toss you outta
your digs, if you'd rather...
Damn the vagaries of haggling.
When you gonna wise up and
run with a better crowd, girlie?
I don't think I really have a
choice. I'm a hostage, you know.
I swear. One of these days...
Are you kidding?
The electron gun's fried!
That'll cost you double.
Take it or leave it.
Your decision.
New development.
The Organization has
apparently hit Cue Ball
into the corner pocket...
Our enemies multiply.
Here.
Huh?
You sure guzzle that stuff
like it's going out of style.
To exemplary IQ's, this "stuff"
is nothing short of ambrosial.
Listen to them...
they're singing!
Daru! It seems our
landlord has finally
gone over to The Enemy,
as we've feared.
Our hand is forced... Plan
Omega must be set in motion!
Alrighty...
This is no time to be glib!
We must conduct a
verifiable field test
for Future Gadget Numero Eight!
Oh, right. The "Phone-wave
(Real Name TBA)"...
Okay... How do you "field test"
a kitchen appliance?
Three and a half
years now, yes...?
That's how long you and
I have known one another?
Only if we're countin'
the year and some change
of high school when we
were in different classes
and never said a
word to each other.
Details, details...
The point is, our friendship
spans the abyss of time...
One would imagine our thoughts
to be simpatico by this stage.
Heh. Scary thought.
If you wanna give the
R.E.N.G another whirl,
though, I'm down for it.
Banana, Double O Two!
Why? You're just gonna
nuke the poor thing...
You'll make it all icky.
Steel yourself, woman!
This is for science!
Well, it's your experiment...
Bet you'd think it
was pretty wasteful
if you paid for
these yourself, though.
Yes, yes.
Welcome to the Radioactive
Entre Navigational Gopher
for your Phone-wave.
To set time, press the
numerical keys corresponding
to the desired
allotment of seconds,
followed by the pound sign.
One-two-zero-pound.
Solid turntable action.
Clockwise.
Unique for a
microwave, I notice.
Clockwise?
There's significance buried
somewhere in that fact,
I can feel it...
Approached from a
quantum perspective,
Hand's rule of
maximum multiplicity...
Don't get ahead of yourself.
No, of course.
Thank you.
Typical result.
Great big gobs o'
greasy grimy gopher guts.
Doesn't do that to
my chicken tenders.
Maybe it's something about...
Perhaps, but the
consistency of its effect
on bananas tends to strengthen
my Stein's Gate hypothesis...
Just what I was thinkin'.
Stifle. Eat one
for verification.
Hells no.
So be it. The honors
go to you, my lovely.
Hmm... Do I have to? The bananas
get all gross and floppy.
I don't really like
the way they taste.
You've eaten one?
Mayushii...
Huh?
Could you give me
that spiel again...?
Only instead of
gross could you say wet?
Alrighty... The bananas
gets all wet and floppy.
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Hopefully this gives
our viewers at home
a better view of this
thing's dimensions--
not to mention the
damage it's caused...
I'm totally dying here.
You've been outside
all of ten minutes.
Hey, put yourself in my shoes.
It's a lot farther
than a guy like me
usually ventures on
foot in the summer.
Why can't they do
it at Queen May's?
Because a college wants
nothing to do with a maid café.
Ugh... Yeah, well the
deans are beggin' me
to drop out with that attitude.
Whew! Air-conditioning!
I can feel the life coming back.
There's no way in
hell the satellite
can be just a coincidence.
You still harping on that?
You're telling me you're
not the least bit curious
to see the crash site?
Like we'd see anything
through the crowd.
'Sides, I'm keeping tabs on the
whole shebang via the interwebs.
Ah... Extra vacation days...
Another holiday?
Wait a minute, of course...
Give me your phone.
What for?
Stop asking questions!
Violation of my basic
rights, douche bag!
I sent you a text.
About Makise Kurisu's murder...
Dude. That was
like so last week.
Last week?
You broke it up into
three parts... Spam monkey.
See?
Huh?
Okabe Rintarou
(No Subject)
Received July 23rd,
12:56pm? What?
"Looks like
someone stabbed
Makise Kurisu."
Yup.
What the...?
Hang on, my outbox...
Mayuri
Re: Upa...
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Where is it? What's today?
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Daru
Re:
(No subject)
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Ruka
Re:
I made
snacks
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Feyris
Re:
Prophecy
Song
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Mayuri
Re: Don't
sell it
Mayuri
Re: Upa...
Daru
Let's go!
Mayuri
Look at
this
Huh? It's the
twenty-eighth. Why?
Spill it.
My text... Traveled
backward in time...
What?
kisei sareta chikai mujihi naru, juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
All those are being rewritten