How...? What in the...?!
All traces of moe
culture have vanished
from the streets
of Akihabara?!
Please, Okarin! Wait for us!
The hell, dude...?
I'm a hacker... not a hiker...
Where'd Toranoana and
Animate go, huh...?!
Where're Mandarake
and Gamers?!
Now you're just being silly.
You know we don't have
any of those around here.
That's why I gotta go all the
way to Nakano for my doujin--
Wait a sec...!
You still work part-time
at Queen May's, don't you?!
Huh? What's a Queen May's?
Our favorite maid café!
Impossible...
It's quite alright, actually.
Moe culture thrives here
mostly because of my influence.
So it's a compliment.
Did she send a D-mail
back in time to undo that?
An entire city... rewritten by
a mere text message...!
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Symbiosis
Homeostasis
Hard to believe May Queen
Nyan-Nyan is no more...
May Queen's a
type of potato, dude.
Not feeling it as the
name of a maid café...
What are you,
some tuber savant?
Wait, if Queen May's
never existed...
then how did we
first meet Faris?
You can mock my random
bits of trivia all you want,
but we wouldn't be
friends with Faris right now
if it weren't for the spuds.
Dare I even ask?
How'd you forget...?!
I was gonna kick some ass in the
Rai-Net tourney in Ikebukuro,
but some bad potato ramen
was all "No--not yours,"
and I had to skip it.
Go on.
So you and Mayuri filled
in for me against Faris...
Got both of your asses kicked,
in case you forgot that...
But the girls've been friends
ever since, so good times...
Hell, a little food poisoning
was worth the scenery.
Interesting...
Check it out, Ruka...!
It's a photo-book full
of professional cosplay
I bought in Nakano!
Oh wow...! They're so adorable!
So even though the past has
been substantially altered,
our relationships are
essentially the same...
Yeah? Me, too!
If only I could get you
to coo over schematics
the way you do over cosplay.
Oh...! Afternoon, Okabe!
It's super-cute, don'tcha think?
Whoa...!
Huh...?
Sedona...
So much detail!
And there's a
swimsuit version, too!
I wish I could wear that...
But I'm so not curvy
enough to pull it off well.
Don't you worry!
Small boobies
will have their day!
Hey! We should all
take a field-trip
to the beach some weekend!
You gotta come, Kurisu!
School swimsuits for the win...!
I dunno... Us and
the perv brigade?
Aww...
Hey! I'm not
saying we can't go--
if we make it a girls-only trip,
then I'm totally down for
some beachside fun in the sun!
Hahaha!
Abandon this charade, Christina!
In truth, you
don't want us along
because we might see
the unfortunate birthmark
marring your
hindquarters... Right?
What?! I don't have a birthmark!
Besides... if this
outing to the beach
were really girls-only, that
would leave Rukako high and dry.
Huh...? How so?
As I pointed out
the other day...
Ruka is, shall we say,
of the masculine persuasion.
Huh?
What the hell's
wrong with you...?
Calling her a boy is a
pretty shitty thing to do.
It makes me sad when you
say mean stuff like that...
Dude... Not cool.
Wait, why're you crying...?!
Oh, honestly!
You troglodyte...!
Apologize to Ruka right now!
Why should I apologize
for saying what is
clearly the truth?!
No--it's fine!
You shouldn't
have to apologize...
If that's the way that
you think of me, so be it.
Well naturally it is!
What else am
I supposed to think?
Put a sock in it,
you jackass!
I should go! I'm sorry!
No y'don't!
This has gone on long enough...!
If Ruka's really the
girl you say she is...
then why does she have a--!
Uh...What the hell?
No, stop!... Please...! Okabe!
Rukako... You're... a female...?
That's what we've... been
saying... this whole damn time!
You look thrashed.
Everything okay?
A little torture. Nothing a
new pair of legs won't fix...
Tortured...?! I bet it
was that Makise chick!
Yeah... But I... got it all
cleared up... I think...?
What did she
do to your legs?!
Huh?! Sweet heavens
no--don't touch them!
She compelled
me to sit stock still
on my haunches
for a full hour...!
Lesser men would have
broken... but not me.
I dunno...
That seems pretty darn
low on the torture-ometer.
Is that so...?
You sound alarmingly
like a woman
who knows what
she's talking about.
Let's just say that
I've done my time.
This is absolutely perfect
weather to go biking.
I suppose.
Hey... you feel
like going for a ride?
I did assume... you had,
a... second bike...!
So... I didn't come to
Tokyo to work in a TV shop...
I'm looking for my dad.
Why is that...? Did he
run off or something?
It's been years...
I don't even remember
what he looks like.
He's somewhere in the city
but that's all
I really have to go on...
It's not much of
a smoking gun...
but I have an old pin of his.
You might want to
think about dropping
the part-time job
and focusing all on this.
Look, I... can't tell
you why exactly...
but I'm only gonna have
one last chance to see him.
Huh?
Short version?
I think my dad's gonna
be somewhere tomorrow.
But if I show up and
he doesn't, that's it...
I gotta move on,
either way.
There's a place I gotta
be getting to pretty soon...
'Cause y'know...
I'm a busy girl.
Hell, if I don't find
him in Tokyo...
I might as well quit looking.
You are ill at ease.
And I... find I can relate.
However...!
You just made the
serendipitous error
of disclosing your tale of
paternal woe to a mad scientist!
Henceforth! You are
Lab Member Double-0 Eight!
Resign yourself to being
our newest guinea pig!
What are you gonna do to me?
Alter your past, of course...
It's all part of
my master plan...
Helping you is
just a side-effect...
You will send a D-mail to
your father, understood?
In it, you will tell him
not to leave--and presto...!
Home he shall remain!
You're a nice guy,
you know that?
What?!
Either way...
I feel a little bit better
about this than I did earlier.
Guess I should
get back to work...
Thanks for being a pal, Okabe!
Hey, listen, I want you to
promise me you'll come
to the lab tomorrow whether
you meet your father or not...!
If he's not there, we'll help
you... for science, of course!
For all your world-dom talk...
you're just a big ol' softie!
All right...
I will now summarize
the basics of Operation
Eldhrimnir in layman's terms.
What's with the Norse mythology?
If Suzuha locates her father,
we'll have a farewell banquet...
We'll have dinner if she doesn't
find her father, as well...
But we'll present it as a
kind of consolation send-off...
If so, the D-mail
will be dessert.
Uh oh... Who's gonna
tell Daru the plan?
He's off meeting
his online friends,
or some such nonsense...
But never fear,
I've got his number...!
This is how you hook a Daru.
To: Daru
Now is the time to choose
Feyris's cooking or your meeting.
Which will you choose?
I took the liberty of sending
him a little white lie.
Wait, are you bribing
him with food or Faris...?
Either way,
that'll probably work.
Huh...? But Faris told me
she couldn't be here tonight.
Which I'm willing
to look beyond,
since she's never
met Suzuha, but our
resident hack's attendance
is decidedly mandatory.
Um, actually...
I've never met her, either.
Is it okay that I'm coming?
But of course...!
You ladies can do the
shopping for our little soiree.
While you...?
While I tail the
scrappy part-timer
to see if her errant
parent "pops" up.
Aw, come on...
Don't go spying on their
father-daughter bonding time.
Yeah, Okarin...!
Why don't you just come on
our shopping trip with us!
Following Suzuha is my--
It's not gonna
happen, so drop it!
Where does my assistant get
off telling me what to do...?!
You remember earlier, right...?
How 'bout three hours?
All right...! Shopping it is!
So shall we be off...?!
I'm watching you.
Is something the
matter, Okarin?
It's nothing...
What in the...?
Do you think we should
go with the mild curry...?
Oh but, hot is so good.
Which do you
think she'll like?
Whatever is fine...
Let's go with the hot one.
Hmm... Good idea! 'Cause
Suzuha's a pretty spicy girl!
I betcha she can't even
taste the mild stuff!
Okie-doke...
Next stop, the meat aisle!
Wow!
Lookit these prices--they're
sure proud of their stuff!
Hey, Okarin...
You've been so
quiet all night...
I keep waiting for you
to say something like...
"Looks like the Organization's
been messing around
with the price
of local meat...!
Launching Operation
Half-Off Sales Event!"...
Or something like that.
"Operation Half-Off Sales
Event" lacks in Nordic flare.
It's me... They've
sabotaged the beef supply...
Operation Audumbla
is still viable,
albeit at a greater cost.
Unlock additional culinary
funding on the double.
Huh? Look...!
First star of the night!
Oh that's Venus, actually.
Hey, Okarin.
Remember back when
we were little kids...
and you had that
really bad fever?
Yeah... Right when everyone
was losing their head
over the whole Y2K thing.
I was scared...
You looked so sick and frail,
I thought you were
gonna just fade away...
I didn't want you to die.
So I looked up at the
stars, and said a prayer.
And right then... one went
shooting past right above me.
So, as it went I said...
"Don't take my Okarin!"... I
said it three times in a row...
And the very next morning...
your fever had broken and you
said you were feeling better!
I don't mean to brag,
but I kinda saved
your life, y'know.
Sorry, but... you didn't...
My surviving that fever was
the decision of Stein's Gate.
Yeah...? Aw... That's no fun.
I'm afraid so.
Okay... Hey, remember
when you first got sick,
how you fell down?
Remember what you said?
You said you were dizzy,
and that the
world felt all wiggly...
Like you'd been zapped
by lightning, you told me...
Like things didn't
make sense anymore.
When we were back at Faris's...?
Your face reminded
me of then.
Sick in bed with that fever...
I'd forgotten how that felt...
It's the same way I feel
when I shift world-lines...
I wonder... was
that bout of illness...
the emergence of my
Reading Steiner ability...?
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Huh...? What's that
odor assailing my nose?
Oh, that? Kurisu decided to
make an apple pie for us...
That stench is dessert?!
I'd love to help...
you have a job for me?
Sure! Why don't you
boil some eggs for me.
Okay!
Let's see... Ooh!
I'll just pop 'em
into the Phone Wave!
No, Mayuri--don't!
They'll explode in there!
I can take care of it!
Aww...
You can chop the
mushrooms instead, yeah?
Yaaaay!
Wait a second...!
What manner of Stygian dessert
are you trying to foist upon us?
They're for the salad, genius.
I defy you to find
me a single world-line
in which egg and mushroom
salad goes with apple pie!
Chop...! Chop...! Chop!
I'm calling a moratorium
on the "chop chop chop!"
Outta the way!
Woe betide me...
All the women have turned
into evil kitchen ghouls...
If I don't call you back
in an hour's time, please...
tell my parents
that I loved them...
right up until
the bitter... end.
'Scuse me, Okabe. Is there
a rice cooker in here?
Heeeere's Daru...!
Wait a sec, where's Faris?
Sorry... She can't make
it to our dinner tonight...
looks like someone pulled a
fast one on you--guess who.
What...?! Son-of-a...!
Man, you suck!
Y'know, truth is a very
subjective phenomenon.
Fat load of good that does me!
I skipped my time-travel
meet-up for this!
Time-travel meet-up?
Don't judge.
It's just a bunch of posters
from a sci-fi forum
I moderate sometimes...
We had a writer coming
as a guest tonight, too!
This little kit is so cute!
What do you keep in here?
I wouldn't go
touching that, Ruka!
It's Future Gadget
numero four: Moad Snake!
Is that a Claymore?!
No, no, it's merely a mock-up...
In actuality, it's a humidifier.
Aha! Here we go!
No--don't pull that!
I'm so sorry, you guys...
What's done is done.
Just watch what you touch
from now on, all right?
Hey... This might
help with the clean-up.
A vacuum? Yeah, good thinking.
Guess again...!
It's Future Gadget
number three...!
Or is it the second one?
Number Five. A.K.A.
"'I've Connected Yet Another
Trifling Thing,' a la Goemon."
A.K.A. a hair dryer
that uses the heat output
of a vacuum cleaner...
Here, gimme.
Hold on!
You have to
unplug everything else
before you use it,
otherwise the--!
...breaker will trip.
Yeah... Anybody know
where the flashlight is?
Um... is this it...?
Uh... no... That's a cucumber.
So... where's the fuse-box...?
What's with that giggle, Mayuri?
You're just going to
trip over something!
Told you so.
Oww...
It's by the front door.
Cool. Thanks.
You okay?
What's so funny?
Sorry 'bout that...
It's just...
Hmm?
I thought of the lab
I work at back in America...
It's top-notch, y'know?
We're talking wall
to wall geniuses...
But they're all so... cold...
Scientifically, it blows this
place out of the water, but...
I feel at home here.
Hey!
Don't go thinking that was
a compliment or anything...!
I was just comparing and
contrasting the labs...
That's all...
I made this place because
I couldn't invent friends.
It worked... I mean...
I'm still here, aren't I?
And you know earlier...
when you said you cherish
our friendship, it...
well... it made me
happy... Like, a lot.
Did you fall on your head?
Wait, what...?!
I try to say something nice,
and that's your reply...?!
You're such a bastard!
Suzuha sure is late, huh.
I hope that means
she found her dad.
Sure, I bet
they're catching up
on father/daughter stuff
and they lost track of time.
I made it very clear she was to
report to the lab either way...
But I guess my instructions
were all for nothing.
She isn't coming.
Let's call it a night.
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Why, that little...!
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
So she's going to
slink off into the night,
fatherless and alone...?
Not on my watch. Hououin
Kyouma cannot abide this!
Dammit!
Where could she be?!
Of course...
I'll send a D-mail
instructing myself
to tail Suzuha this afternoon
at all costs...! But...
After everything
that's transpired...
dare I alter the
past any further...?
You're a nice guy,
you know that?
Either way...
I feel a little bit better
about this than I did earlier.
I'm no thumb
twiddling milquetoast
trembling in his lab coat...
I am Hououin Kyouma...
I look into the
abyss with nary a fear!
"Ignore assistant..."
Do not give in to your
assistant's threats. Follow Suzuha!
"...tail Suzuha!"
Do not give in to your
assistant's threats. Follow Suzuha!
Whassup.
It's good to see
you're so hard at work...
Late night, eh?
No kidding--that party really
took on a life of its own!
I'm running on fumes today...
Humor me, if you would...
We threw a consolation
dinner for you last night,
one at which you served
as our test subject.
Did we not?
Yeah, but we never got
around to the guinea pig part,
'cause I don't have
my dad's contact info.
There's a detail
I'm kind of fuzzy on...
Refresh my memory as to how you
ended up at the lab last night?
Huh...? What were
you drinking...?
Sounds like somebody
needs to lay off the sauce.
Please, just indulge
me for a moment.
Yeah, okay...
I was just leaving the time-
travel forum meet-up when you--
Uh... Time-travel
forum meet-up...?!
When you told me your father
might show up somewhere,
is that what you meant?!
Yup. On the message boards,
he posts under
the user ID Titor.
Wait... John Titor?!
Nuh uh, sorry.
Barrel... It's Barrel Titor.
I told you at
the party, remember?
You recorded me
saying it and everything.
Oh man...! Last night
was so much fun!
Course, it would've been
better without you-know-who...
That pie of hers almost made it
a farewell party
for everyone...!
Ruka's curry, though...
now that was some tasty stuff!
I really do dig your lab...
Seriously cool!
You all get along, and
you're always having fun.
First time in my whole life
I felt like I really fit in.
Come on up whenever you want.
Surely I needn't remind you...
You are a member of the lab now.
Yeah. Maybe I'll stick around...
Look for dear ol'
Dad a little bit more...
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten