After the train... I leapt over,
and over, and over, and over...
So many times that
it's all a blur now.
But... however hard I tried...
Mayuri would always die...
Right in front of me.
When Moeka and her
thugs didn't attack...
it was as if fate
stepped in for them...
Like the whole world
wanted Mayuri dead...
And nothing I did
could change its mind.
What's the hold-up?!
This is ridiculous!
Train lines have shut down.
Can't you cut through
an alley or something?!
Come on, man!
That's not really
an option... Sorry.
Oh no. I just wound you!
Don't tell me you're broken.
So not fair...
I've taken extra good care--
Not again... Please.
Mayuri!
Shiina Mayuri is
confirmed dead...
HOE-oh-een-- Okabe Rintarou,
rather, has fled the scene.
No matter what I do,
no matter what I try...
she keeps on dying... I don't
understand. What is this?
Is this the choice of
Stein's...? No. No it's not...
Get out of your damn
head, Okabe...
None of that crap is real...
Not the Organization. Not
Stein's Gate... None of it.
You're an idiot!
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Physically
Necrosis
What's the deal...?
Explain it to me!
Dude, I just hit
a story branch.
The least you could do as
a man is let me save it!
Look, I'll do it for you...
Just get the hell out of town
before you don't have
that option anymore...!
I'll explain later.
What's going on?
It doesn't matter...
She's already left.
It's the same... Every
time I try to save her...
Every time...
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Not even the texts
change... Wait...
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Assistant
Did something
happen?
Tell me later, okay?
"Shining Finger...
There's something about the
time machine you should know...
I need to speak with you alone.
Don't move... Hands in the air.
Who the hell are
you working for?!
I just... work for Arc Rewrite.
Don't play games with me!
I know you and your
pals are planning
to bust into our lab tonight
and try to abduct us, okay?
How...?
Because I'm from
the God damn future.
Who are you...? Answer me!
Can I text it...?
Screw that...!
Tell me to my face...!
Are you people
working for SERN?!
We're Rounders.
You're what?
Our mission is to
retrieve the IBN 5100.
Haven't you psychos
already made off with it?!
What?
Do I look stupid...?!
It's been missing
since your D-mail!
That's right...
When the world-line shifted,
Moeka lost all memory of
sending that text, didn't she?
This isn't making any sense...
Why raid the lab
in the first place?
The IBN's not
even friggin' there!
I...
Answer me!
Do you really have to ask?
Three things...
First off: you have access
to knowledge you shouldn't.
Secondly... You've
created a time machine.
Last but not least: you
intended to go public with it.
You knew all of that...?
How long have your overlords
at SERN been on to us?!
FB is the only authority
I'll ever answer to.
And that's what...?
Like a splinter cell--
FB... is my... my everything...
Where am I?
Don't move.
Are you or are
you not John Titor?
That's the only
explanation that fits.
No!
Oh god...
Bomb threat
worked like a charm.
Trains'll be stalled for a
while... We're good to go.
Secure Makise Kurisu
and Hashida Itaru...
Everyone else is expendable.
No!
Wait! Don't do this...!
I'll give you whatever
the hell you ask for,
just don't kill Mayuri!
Look, I'm sorry...!
I didn't know what I was doing!
Who'd believe a nut like
me about SERN anyway?!
Take the damn time machine,
I don't care...!
I won't tell a living soul
about this, I swear to god!
Commence operation.
I'm begging you not to
go through with this...!
I'm just a nobody whose
curiosity got the better of him!
Nothing was ever
going to come of it!
Nothing ever does...
Please don't kill my friend...!
Too late.
Mayuri...
Mayuri!!
Shut the hell up!
Mayuri!
No...
What's with you...?
Earth to Okabe.
Not again.
No... I can't take it anymore!
Okabe, no!
Dude...
Calm down; we agreed
not to do it...
There's no point in breaking
the damn thing, alright?
There you go...
We've got a party to plan...
Let's focus on that.
Party--
Hey, wait for--!
Clackety-clack...! Look,
Mommy--it's the bullet train!
Ah, Oka-- um, I mean Kyouma...
Have you seen Mayuri?
Oh, she headed out
a little while ago...
I know.
She came here to invite
you to the party tonight...
As we speak she's stopping
off at her friend's place
to fix a hem en route
back to the lab...
I know. I know everything!
I'm sorry, I don't
know what to say.
I know everything...
And I'm powerless.
Do I want to know
what you're doing here?
Kurisu...
Something must be wrong for
you to use my actual name...
What happened, then...?
Or... What's going to happen?
Uh-huh. You
time-leapt, didn't you?
It's... It's all my fault...
What is?
From start to
finish it's my fault...
I'm the one who told
Daru to hack into SERN...
I'm the one whose
stupid idea it was
to build a time
machine to begin with;
and the one who brought
Moeka into our lives...
I'm the reason...
that Mayuri...
Well, I won't argue that
you aren't reckless...
Fact of the matter is we have
no idea how dangerous leaping
might be to you physically.
For all we know, do it enough
and you could possibly
leap yourself right out
of existence altogether.
Humans beings are
time haunted...
That's what Heidegger
thought, isn't it?
Oh, you've read him...?
Funny, I was just thinking about
that passage earlier today.
You were about two seconds
away from quoting it to me.
Okay. Not gonna lie.
Kind of creepy.
It's like you're rooting
through my frontal lobes...
Note to self:
time-leaping side effects
include the ability
to freak people out.
What am I going to do?
When exactly does
the lab get attacked?
Just after seven thirty.
I have a rough idea
why Mayuri keeps dying.
Several ideas, actually...
But sitting here brooding about
them isn't going to do anything.
Come on.
I am not about to let
a friend get killed...
You and I have work to do.
I'm so sorry.
Stop apologizing...
I'm in this mess with you
by choice... I'm one of you...
Perk up...!
You're supposedly a
world-class mad scientist...!
One bent on giving the powers
that be a run for
their money, right?
"Of course you are!"
Shut up.
Okay, I've set it for
about five hours ago...
Around the time we put
the finishing touches
on the time-leap machine.
Any earlier than that,
and we run the risk of
it not being completed.
You have to get everyone
to leave once it's finished
and re-tell me everything
you told me earlier,
even though it might be
difficult for me to take, okay.
Wear me down and I'm bound
to believe you eventually.
You sure about that?
Hey, I know precisely how much
crazy I can swallow at one time.
Think about it: I'm the
one who designed the machine
so I'll trust that it works...
Just play to my ego.
So, your willingness
to believe me
is proportional to
your narcissism...
Naturally...
I'm proud of the fact that I'm
a kickass research scientist...
Tell me I'm good at applied
science and you're in.
Just to be on the
safe side, though,
we should give you
a trigger phrase.
When you see me, tell me
I've been craving my own fork.
Like Personalized...?
That's kind of an odd thing...
Why not? I already have a
spoon waiting to go with it...
Hey, stay on task! My motives
are immaterial! Are you ready?
Uh... Yeah, okay.
I won't remember you
used my actual name...
Kind of a shame, really.
Might go a long way
toward endearing you to me.
Hey, hold this a second for me,
will you? Like that, yeah?
Like this?
Yep-yep... Nice
and stretched out.
Try to think like
you're a clothes-line.
Aw, Mayuri...
What a pretty ribbon.
I know! Oh! Hey, you should
totally try this one on...!
It's okay, I have other
outfits I can compete in.
It is kind of cute...
Got the cosplay bug?
Please. Don't even go there...
Like I'd ever traipse
around in public wearing...
That's right...
Five hours back lands me here
right before Mayuri leaves...
The time-leaper
is done moments
after she puts the
final stitch in her outfit.
Finished!
Yay...! Mayushii takes
the gold! I beat you...
Oh dear... This was a race...?
You cleaned our
clock then, didn't you?
But we're not far behind...
Matter of fact, we're done...
We're not going through with it!
Crap! Too sudden!
What are you talking about?
I mean, it's clear
that we're all completely
and utterly exhausted...
What we need is rest...
All further experimentation
is called off for today.
One beef bowl, please.
Coming up.
Explain why here?
Well it wasn't by design.
I didn't get your message
until after I'd ordered.
Just doesn't strike me
as the sort of place
that you would patronize.
I just found it; it's not
like I'm a regular yet...
Mayuri was the one who
recommended it... Ugh...
What'd you want to
talk to me about...?
First you send us all packing
for the day with no explanation,
then I get one of
your cryptic texts...
Listen to me.
I've come from approximately
five hours in the future.
You what...? Is that the
first half of a pickup line?
Damn it all, you told me
you'd know the precise amount
of crazy you'd be
willing to swallow!
I'm approaching this the
way you instructed me to!
Okay then, let me
stop you right there.
In the short time we've known
each other, have I ever once
struck you as someone inclined
to swallow any amount of crazy?
That's what I thought...!
But... Look,
think of it this way,
that I'm here at all is a
testament to your ingenuity!
Doesn't that entice belief?
You are certifiable...
Ever think you
missed your calling
as a schizoid case study?
Easy does it.
Mustn't slug her...
Right now what you crave
more than anything...
Is a monogrammed fork.
Convinced?
Where the hell is
that coming from...?
I say that five hours from now?
You have a personalized spoon
to go with it, so why not?
Damn it! Future me is in for
such a royal ass kicking...!
Surely this is sufficient
to persuade you
I'm telling the truth...
Okay... So you're
telling me a time machine
I constructed...
works as designed...
Here's your beef bowl, hon.
One thing is clear: if you've
got your facts straight,
this is serious stuff
we're dealing with.
Yeah.
Maybe our trouble is we're
focused too tightly on Mayuri...
Why not shift to Moeka...?
Couldn't she and the
Rounders be dealt
with before they
become an issue?
I've tried that...
The same basic scenario
played itself out
regardless of what I did.
Damn.
Still... Every
natural phenomenon,
however immutable it might
appear to be on the surface,
Cause
Death
Effect
is subject to change.
Death
We have to think in terms
of cause and effect.
Now usually cause of death
is directly attributable
to something: illness,
accident, whatever.
But really these are
just incidental details;
local manifestations
of a broader principle.
In Mayuri's case, the Rounders
are the obvious culprit,
but they're not the prime mover.
That's something more abstract.
We can deduce as
much from the fact
that she dies even when
they're not involved.
Cause
Death
Effect
So what's the
underlying cause?
I can't be sure...
I mean, it could even be that
the circumstances of her birth
somehow set her on a path which
made dying on a certain date,
at a certain time unavoidable.
You're sounding
like an astrologist...
That's fatalism and I don't
buy into it for a second.
You're right, it's absurd--
I just don't know a better
way to frame what
I'm trying to get at.
The point is, we're
not thinking back
far enough to expose
the real catalyst.
Indeed...
Maybe we need only think back
so far as to leave the
machine unfinished...
Hold on.
We don't know the machine
isn't just another detail.
But surely...
She's hit the nail on the head.
You know something...?
If so, please just to tell us.
You're right not wanting
to abandon the time machine.
Take my word for it
when I say this'd be
impossible without one.
You wouldn't have a prayer.
If you wanna save the world...
You've gotta push past
the divergence barrier...
That nagging one percent
gap between world-lines
attached to the same alpha.
Okay. Pay attention kiddos,
it's gonna get complicated:
The Divergence Number indicates
a given world line's latitude
on a continuum, so to speak.
The only way to keep
track of it is this:
A trusty Divergence Meter.
Nixie tubes...My hats off
to the taste of its inventor.
Funny you should say that.
This bad boy's papa is you.
Me?!
Your memories tend to stay put
regardless of the world-line,
so eventually you
developed--or will develop--
a gauge to keep track.
The meter records and
represents, numerically,
the gap between the
present world-line
and the one it
splintered off from.
Indispensable for the
discerning time traveler.
0.337187...
That's this world-line's number.
If you're havin' trouble gettin'
your head around the concept,
it might help to
think of world-lines
like fibers in a rope.
At first blush a rope
looks like a single thing...
But hone in, and it's
obviously made up
of many interlocking threads.
Now each thread is
its own thing,
independent of its neighbors...
but they're all moving
in the same direction.
That's why it's so strong.
Wait. Are you telling us
that every world-line
leads to Mayuri's death?
For now.
But all bets are off if you
can manage a big enough change
to push past the one percent
divergence barrier.
Something that'll derail
you off the alpha track
with enough force to
land you onto a beta line.
Okay. The one on
the right is yours.
Uh, excuse me.
I'm not quite athletic
enough to shimmy up a rope...
Ugh. Fine then. Wait here...
I'll be back in a second.
What is she?
Professional shimmy-er,
perhaps...? I dunno.
The coast is clear... Hop to.
Alpha and beta world-lines
play out differently,
so they lead to
different futures.
Very different futures,
most of the time.
Normally it's impossible
to travel between them.
You can D-mail or
leap all you want;
it's not going to
alter things enough
to break you away
from the alpha line.
That said, though...
There are relatively fixed
points in any line where events
of great enough significance
occur to break off
toward a beta, depending on
the choices that are made.
Recent examples of what
I'm talking about are,
like, let's say the Gulf War...
The Y2K panic from the
turn of the last century...
And, it should
go without saying,
the invention of
the time machine.
Is that...?
Points like that are the
only elbow room we've got;
the only way to "shimmy"
from an alpha to a beta.
Yes, but the question is how to
take advantage of such points?
Hold on.
First things first...
Don't you think it's time
to tell us who you are?
Is this...?
You know what it is.
I'm a time traveler;
specifically from the year 2036.
Dear god...
We've met online a few
times, you and me...
I post as John Titor.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten