Look... Just hear
me out, please...
I know it's hard to believe,
but... you really were a dude.
Why do you keep saying that?
No, no, no. Don't cry...
I promise you, I'm not
trying to be mean...
I'm doing this for Mayuri.
I need you to find
it within yourself
to give up being a girl.
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Fractal Androgynous
What's the damage...?
You're sitting there, like...
well... like an apprentice
who screwed up yakisoba
noodles in front of the chef.
Thank you... That's
not a bad analogy...
Well done...
Guess I prefer that to being
told I look like a busboy...
'Course could've gone the other
way with it... called me noodle.
Well hey, at least you
still have the gumption
to wring a bad joke
out of the situation.
Okarin! I am so mad at you right
now I can hardly see straight!
Wha... What are
you talking about?
Don't you even try to
play all innocent...!
You made Ruka cry!
How do you know that?!
I kind of put it together
when I invited her
to the lab today and
she burst into tears...
I asked what was wrong--you
know, like friends do--
and she told me
you called her a boy!
She didn't happen to
mention the D-mail, did she?
What's that got to do...?
Stop trying to worm your
way out of this, mister...!
You owe Ruka an apology
and that's all there is to it!
You jerk.
You don't say things
like that to a lady,
what's wrong with you?
Don't jump to conclusions...!
There's method
to my crassness!
Of course there is.
If I may speak with you
in private... I'll clarify.
Damn it! Would you quit it
with the jacket already!?
That's the long and
short of it, really.
The next D-mail I have to
undo is the one we let Ruka send
to his mother's pager while
she was pregnant with him.
So, Urushibara
really is a boy...
That's rather hard to take in.
Well, believe me, it's the
truth... At least it used to be.
But she's so... feminine...
Next you'll tell me
she looked like Hashida.
Ooooh. No.
Heh. look-wise, Ruka's no
different than he is now.
Whew. Okay, then.
Anyway... Point is, if
we intend to save Mayuri,
we have to persuade Ruka
to go back to being a boy.
Think about it, though:
is it necessary...?
In this case you know
what the text said,
so you can undo it without
her being a part of it...
A little underhanded maybe, but
it might spare some feelings...
I don't think Ruka could
ever be "persuaded..."
The problem with
that scenario is
that I haven't the first clue as
to his mother's pager number...
Besides... I'd really rather
not resort to cheap trickery...
We're playing with another
human being's identity here;
I don't want to be clever.
Good luck upholding
those principles
without reducing her to tears.
You're just joking
around with me, right?
'Course you are...
That's what you do.
There is such a thing
as taking things too far,
though; in case no one told you!
That didn't hurt for the
reasons you think it did.
What? I don't follow...
I was just trying to be as
straightforward as possible...
It's not like I told him he
was hideously deformed.
She's in love with you,
you moron...!
You might as well have told the
poor thing she was Quasimodo.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Stop...! Put yourself
in her place for a minute.
How would you feel under
the circumstances...?
Essentially sexless to
the person you desire.
But, he's... What am I supposed
to do? He really is a guy!
In another world-line
maybe, but not in this one.
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
No Subject
Rukako
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
Rukako
No Subject
He--she--wants to talk to me.
Could you come by the shrine
when you have a chance?
Hi, Okabe.
Uh, so yeah.
Sorry about earlier.
No... I'm sorry for
getting so emotional.
Water under the bridge.
You wanted to talk?
Um, yes... I kind of had
a favor I wanted to ask.
By all means.
Okay, I'll just come
right out with it:
I believe you... So... well...
Yeah?
I'll agree to go back to
being a boy if... if... oh...
If you'll be my boyfriend!
I'm sorry...?!
I don't, uh... Why me?!
Because I like you.
More than that:
I'm crazy about you.
All I...
All I want out of this is
to be with you for a day...
Just one day... Give me
that before I change back!
But... You're a dude... I...
Okay, okay: yes! Done deal!
Just stop crying...!
So be it...!
I'll take one for the
team, if only for day!
Let us be an item!
You really mean that?
Uh, the waterworks...
I'm sorry... I'm just so happy.
Unexpectedly touching...
So the only way
through this is for you
to go on a date
with her tomorrow?
That's correct.
Bleh. A mad scientist
and a high schooler...
Pardon my flesh
for crawling a little.
Ha ha... I realize
I'm throwing caution
to the wind by coming to my
assistant for dating advice,
but that's no
reason to taunt me.
I am not your assistant!
Oooh...! Kyouma's
going out on a date?
That's interesting... Here's
your iced coffee, Meow-ster...
Now, surely we're close
enough to tell me who with...
That is unless...
It's patently obvious...
I do not foul my own nest.
Mind if I make an
observation, Casanova sir...?
All this woman-chasing
is going to play havoc
with your special technique.
What does she mean
"all this woman-chasing?"
Hey! You can't leave
loaded statements
like that just
hanging in the air!
So... a special
technique, huh...?
I bet Ruka would love to
see what that's all about.
Wait, that came out wrong...
I was aiming that
at your alter ego...!
Well neither of us is amused
by your lewd insinuation...
Filthy assistant.
What...? Are you serious?
Wow, thanks for
making this awkward...
Look, she brought up
your special technique...
I was just pointing out
how stupid it sounded...
I wasn't... trying
to be all perverted.
You look like a radish.
Oh shut up...!
I'm blushing 'cause I know
your mind is in the gutter.
Point is, just go
on the damn date!
Why do you think we're having
this awkward conversation
to begin with?!
Okarin...
There some special
reason you were waitin'
to fill your ol' pal in
on the sexy details?
Dude, if it's dating
advice you're after,
I'm like the golden child!
Seriously, I've made
out with so many babes
they're thinkin'
about passin' a law!
Nene... Shiori...
Honoka... Rinka...
Thank you, Lothario, but no...
System cheats aren't going to
help me on a real tête-à-tête.
First things first, I need
to find somewhere popular...
Aoyama, perhaps...
Or Nishi-Azabu...
"Fashionable and trendy...
Premium night...
"Special dinner..."
I give up... This world
is alien to me...
How can a Martian be expected
to navigate the oceans of Venus?
Better steel yourself, capt'n.
Bite your tongue...!
My IQ is on par
with Sir Isaac Newton.
And like his august self I have
no use for the fairer sex...
Hououin Kyouma is
dedicated to higher purposes
than these ridiculous
flights of fancy!
Yes, we get it:
you're a genius...
As dedicated to science
as you are to virginity.
Oh and I suppose
you're experienced...?!
Pray tell how many wayward ships
have you coerced into your port?
Go on, I'm listening!
Just as I thought!
You're no less chaste
than the rest of us seekers;
ergo utterly devoid of
input on the topic at hand!
Not that I'd expect otherwise.
Fine! So I've never gone
all the way! Screw you!
"The key to making your
first date the first of many
is to put your
best foot forward...
What you wear is crucial;
brand names don't matter,
but overall cleanliness
and style certainly do..."
Good to go in that department...
Nothing broadcasts chic
like a crisp, white lab coat.
You are not
wearing a lab coat...
"Where you choose to dine
is equally important...
However, don't feel
you have to pick
somewhere terribly expensive...
Usually the ideal restaurant
is one you already frequent."
Ah, well in that case...
There's always here.
That's not what
they're saying, tool...!
A ramshackle greasy
spoon like this
is no way to wine
and dine a girl!
Okay... That only leaves
one option... Queen May's.
In what universe
is that acceptable?!
Then a weapon shop?
You gonna club her
over the head?!
Will you pry yourself from
the twaddle in that book
for two seconds and bring this
discussion back down to earth?!
You're a virgin, lest we forget!
I don't know what that
has to do with anything!
That's the point, isn't it?
How would you know?!
I'm going to punch
you in the face.
Excuse me...
Have you considered
giving the wisdom between
these pages a try?
That's a hentai game
strategy guide, jackass!
So...?! You don't think dating
is a giant part of that scene?!
Where do you think I learned
the best way to hold hands...?
The trick is to position your
arm so that a strategically
swinging elbow grazes some
boobage while you walk...
Before you know it,
you're all over each other
ike sea otters.
Man, it's so hot!
In fact, to hell
with you losers!
I've gotta go see a
man about a unicorn!
It's morning...
And I still don't have the
first glimmer of a plan...
Stop feeling sorry for
yourself and put it on.
Take the tags off;
you're not a mannequin.
And oh my god, have
you never worn a tie?
Seriously... Why am I even
bothering with this...?
Aright then.
Why do I feel like I'm about
to be taken out for a walk?
Your handkerchief...
Not that I expect you
to know how to use it.
Isn't this supposed to
symbolize something specific...?
Like "I've waited for you..."
Only if it's yellow and
you're in the eighties...
Why is some obscure
little factoid like that
even rattling around in
your head to begin with?
Same reason it's
rattling around in yours?
Uh! Stay focused...!
A gentleman spreads his
handkerchief out on a park bench
so his companion can sit
down without getting sullied.
You know what? Never mind.
I'll be following you covertly
so I can text you when you're
about to screw something up.
That, seems like a bit much...
Nonsense. Hashida! To arms!
Huh?!
Commence Operation Valkyrie!
Huh... catchy name.
"When meeting your date,
time is of the essence...
Be sure to arrive at
least fifteen minutes early."
Okabe!
I'm so sorry!
I thought I'd given myself
plenty of time to get here...
I, uh... hope you
haven't waited long.
No, no... I... Just got
here myself, actually.
Whew, oh good...
So I'm not late.
So ... Shall we go?
Sure!
I've never seen you out
of your lab coat before;
you look really sharp.
Well... this being a
special occasion and all...
"When walking down the street,
take the side of oncoming
traffic, but be subtle."
Something's
bothering you, isn't it?
No, not at all!
I'm just... thinking.
Oh my! What on earth is that?!
At least his heart's
in the right place.
"Causally-delicately--shield her
from any passing cars
and/or motorcycles."
Fire in the hole!
Atta boy!
Okabe...
Oww...
Are you two alright?
Don't accept help from
a maid, damn it all...!
A girl doesn't want to
see her man touching
some frilly little chit and
don't take her tissue pack!
Is it me, or are you gettin' a
vicarious thrill from all this?
So, the weather sure
is nice today, huh?
Yeah...
It is partially cloudy, though.
Yeah, I guess.
The cake is really good.
Not too rich...
Yes. I'm liking the coffee, too.
What is wrong with me...?!
I'm a master of small talk,
especially around Ruka...
Why does dating
change the dynamic?!
How did you find this place...?
I assume you must be a regular.
No...!
This is a shipwreck...
"The key to good conversation
is treating it like
a game of catch."
This is actually
my first time here.
He tossed it back!
And on the subject of firsts...
Today being August fourteenth,
this is the anniversary of
the first patent ever issued
in the country of Japan.
Isn't that fascinating?
Yeah, tossed it
back into the pit!
You're like an
encyclopedia of neat stuff.
Hmm? Well you know how it is.
Can we please get the
hell out of here now...?
It's not like we can just
bust through the window
on zip lines and rescue him...
We're not going anywhere until
we've seen this thing through.
Thank you. Come again.
Umm... Are you bored?
I mean with the
whole date thing...?
I'd understand... It's okay.
Don't be ridiculous,
of course not...!
I was just marshalling my
strength for phase two...!
Come along!
Ruka?
This heat is killing me...
He just walked straight
to Ueno and back!
What the hell?
Hey, Okabe...
Do you remember the first
time the two of us met...?
That amazingly chivalrous
stunt you pulled?
Those wannabe paparazzi
were swarming all over me
with their cameras and stuff.
I was terrified
and you jumped in to defend
a complete stranger.
Oh. Yeah.
I... I can't even
begin to thank you...!
Sorry for all the trouble.
Hm? Why are you apologizing?
Because I look like a girl...
People always make
a big deal out of it.
What you look like is
neither here nor there...
People are idiots.
The genuine you...
transcends that rot.
You have no idea what hearing
those words meant to me then.
For the first time
I felt like a real person.
It stuck with me...
Made me fall for you...
Hey... You'd have heard it
from someone eventually...
I... Wait! You
remember all that?!
But that comes from when you
were a guy, doesn't it?!
Well... I... That...
shouldn't make sense,
but I guess so...
I'm suddenly confused...
This is exactly what
happened to Faris...
Her memories are reaching
across conflicting world-lines.
Thank you... It was
sweet of you to do this.
Having you for my
boyfriend, even... for a day...
It was... It meant
everything to me...
Hey...
Here. My mother's
old pager number.
"Meat veg. Meat meat
veg. Meat veg meat. Veg."
That ought make Urushibara's
mom take the first message
with a big grain of salt.
She'll discount the
whole thing as a prank.
I think we're
ready to fire it off.
What's wrong, Okabe...?
You look a little...
Too-too-roo!
Great news, you guys...!
I saw Ruka out on a date with a
tall, dark man of mystery today!
How awesome
heart-warming is that?!
Uh... Yeah, she
was with Okabe.
What? Nuh-uh...!
This guy was wearing clothes
he wouldn't be caught dead in.
There was just this aura
about him, you know?
Total gentleman. Definitely
not someone we've ever met.
Exactly!
That wasn't the
real me out there...!
Ruka was duped by a figment of
our imagination; a mere charade!
What happened?
Our date isn't over yet.
Wait, what? Okabe...
Kyouma...! How dare you
saddle me with that insult!
And enough of the boyfriend/
girlfriend, shemale shtick!
Prattling on about gender roles;
hell, I wasn't born yesterday!
The only thing that
matters is chemistry...!
Everything else
is a non-issue...
I'm the guru.
You're the grunt...
That's how it's
always been with us...
That is how it's always
going to be... Understood?
Yes sir!
Then showcase what you've
learned from knowing me!
Take up Samidare!
Excellent!
Don't falter! Keep it up!
Right!
Heed me, grasshoppa.
You have much to learn...
Stories of this blade's
supernatural proclivities
are notorious...
Many of them traceable
to Yoshitsune's time.
The most gnomic
and profound of these
tells of a wandering samurai,
lost beneath the--
This is officially a disaster.
Oh stop it, silly...!
Look how much they're
enjoying each other's company!
I think our work
here is done, people.
Promise me you'll save her...
Do whatever you have to.
I think I might know
what happened
to that old PC you've
been looking for.
The 5100?!
We had a computer from the
seventies that I kind of
maybe knocked over and broke
while going through storage.
But... it was a total
accident...I didn't know!
It was just another piece
of junk thrown into the mix...
I'm so sorry!
It's my fault... I'm an idiot...
But you've got to find a
way around it and save her!
Thank you for training
with me like we used to
in the old days;
it meant more to me than
I think you'll ever know.
I...
Please go... I don't
want to cry again...
You've seen me do it enough.
Hey! Aren't you
forgetting something?
The password...
El... Psy... Congree.
Congroo.
Sure... Whatever.
I... I really don't want
to do this... It's so...
I mean... The second
I give up being a girl,
I'll have to bury
my feelings for you
the way I've always done!
It's not fair!
I'm not allowed to
like you if I'm a boy!
People won't understand...
Rukako...
The thing is I could
handle all that
if I was just allowed
to remember how
wonderful today's been...
But this'll all go away...
I'll have no idea that you
and I actually went on a date...
That I got to hold you
like this without worrying
what everyone
else would think...
God, if I'd known being a girl
would hurt this
much in the long run,
I wouldn't have changed...!
Why did I do this to myself?!
Listen to me, damn it!
What you are doesn't matter.
It's who you are...!
Nothing's going to
change between us!
When you say it like that...
I can almost believe you...
And I'll have the first
thing you said to me...
That should be enough.
Just do me one
more favor, okay...?
Remember when
I was a girl...
Remember how different
things might've been.
I... won't be able to help it.
Why are you standing
there like that?
Urushibara Ruka...
Delicate as an orchid.
Fair as a cherry blossom...
The personification
of feminine grace.
Hey, uh... Question.
Yeah?
Do you... Like me?
Where's this coming from?!
Do you?
Kyouma, please...
I... I respect you.
And... a dude.
One more D-mail... Deep breath.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten