Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Hurry up and cook, noodles!
I had fun at Comima this --
You're gonna go back
tomorrow, aren't you?
Huh...?
Uh... yeah...
And, you'll be coming
back around now?
I think so.
Ooh! You should
come with me, Kurisu!
Uh, I dunno. Big crowds
really aren't my thing...
But tomorrow's the second day,
so it shouldn't be too bad...!
Hey, Okarin!
Wanna come... with...?
You--roof. Now!
What the hell's
wrong with you?!
Mayuri's been trying to cheer
you up ever since you got back!
Could you at least pretend
not to be a jackass?
I'm sorry. It's just...
the waiting...
God, it's killing me...!
What...?
She isn't dead...
But it's a stay of
execution! Nothing more!
I've told you this...
over and over again.
What do you mean?
Our D-mails have come at a cost.
Endless
Apoptosis
Mayuri's going to
die tomorrow...?!
Short of a miracle... yes...
It used to be Friday the 13th...
That night. Every time...
But each D-mail I undo
pushes it back a day.
That's why...
I have to go with her.
You've thought of
a way to save her.
I'm going... to watch her die.
Why?!
It's the only way
I can be sure how long
Mayuri's got on this
world-line... and once I am...
I'll leap back
once last time.
And I'll stop it.
So, the next D-mail...
It was from this
Kiryuu Moeka girl, right?
Indeed... And
I know what she wrote.
She cautioned her past
self against purchasing
a new cell phone.
It'll only work if I
send her a new message
from that phone, though.
Then you had better
start looking for her.
I'll go with Mayuri to Comima.
What?!
Maybe we'll get
lucky and she won't...
I'll be with her and that's
gotta count for something!
And what if it doesn't...?!
If I don't find Moeka tomorrow,
are you ready to watch her die?!
No! And neither are you!
Okabe... you don't have
to bottle this stuff up...
From this moment on,
you and me are in this
thing together, okay?
You're right...
You've always been right.
Don't you forget it...
'Cause no matter how
many world-lines you jump,
that's never gonna change...
I've got your back.
Assistant
Too many people here.
Way more than I expected.
Save me!
Assistant
Now in Ariake
"At Ariake now...
Huge crowd here, worse than
I imagined... Save me..."
"No reply from Moeka, but
I found out where she works."
"I'll see what
they can tell me..."
"Roger. Don't do
anything crazy."
Moeka, you said...?
If she's the girl I'm thinking
of, she lasted a day or two
and then flaked out.
Her address...?
Yeah, I have it...
but why should you?
Affirmative.
Excuse me...!
You're saying she...
killed herself...?!
Moeka... you're sure
that was her name...!
Yes, sir.
When did she die?!
Late last night, more or less.
Body was taken to
Third Chiyoda Hospital.
Having trouble with
the next of kin, though.
I'm too late...
You feeling all right...?
Suicide...
Think...!
Maybe it was murder...
One of her fellow
rounders... But why...?
Damn it, man--it
doesn't matter...!
Mayuri... is doomed...
Wait. Another time leap...!
If I can get to Moeka
before she dies last night...!
Go ahead.
She... oh god, Okabe...
She... she's dead...
Mayuri's dead...!
Time of death... 7:52 p.m...
I should have been with her.
What the hell...!
Okabe, you jerk!
Did you eat this pudding?!
Don't look at me like that...!
I wrote "Makise,"
on here plain as day!
Are you even listening to me?!
"I've got your back...
don't you forget it."
You were right... I can't
do it alone... Kurisu.
Huh...? did you just...
call me by name?
Does the name "Kiryuu Moeka"
mean anything to you?
How come... Should it?
Finding her... is now a
matter of life-or-death.
What do you mean...?
FB...FB... Write me
back... Please...FB...
Did I do something wrong...?
Why won't you respond...?
Please... What did I do?
FB...
You and I need to chat.
Everything you
asked for, I did...
All of it...
Moeka... Look at me...!
I need you to
give me new orders, FB...!
Forget the damn phone...! Hey!
...FB...
...FB... FB... FB...
FB... FB...FB... FB...
No...!
No, it's mine!
Let go...! It's... mine!
I'm sorry...
But you started this...
when you killed my friend!
Give it back...!
Give it back! Give it back!
Okabe Rintarou
Hey, I'm here!
You have her phone?!
Just pried it away from her!
Everything ready on your end?
We'll all set!
Wow, is that her?!
Let her carry on!
Where's Mayuri!?
Is she down there?!
Yeah! And the TV is
definitely on! I can hear it!
Texting now...!
Kurisu!
Change your phone. It will sell out soon,
and you won't be able to get one.
Fire it up--now!
I'm on it!
Give it back!
This is it... The last one.
One message left to go...
and she lives...!
Give it back...!
Gimme back my phone...
Hold on... Why am I still here?
Problem!
It didn't work?!
Are you sure it was on?!
Did it light up like before?!
There was arcing all over
the place...! What happened?
My whole Reading Steiner
thing never kicked in!
Huh?!
I'm still on the same
world-line as a moment ago.
Why'd it fail?
Give it back!
Aw, come on! You share this
building with other people ...!
Give it back!
Why the hell isn't it working?!
The process isn't exact--
we just send new texts,
we don't know how
they're received...!
What if your message just
wasn't convincing enough
to keep her from
buying that new phone?!
How'm I supposed
to convince her?!
You're right.
It's the same one...!
It's the same phone she messaged
her past self not to buy!
That's gotta be it, then!
We just need to
figure out a better text!
"I got this cell phone four
days ago, but I don't like it...
So I want to tell the
past me not to buy it."
What if the message she showed
us wasn't the one that she sent?
Are you telling me we have no
idea what she wrote to herself?!
Whatever she wrote, there
should still be a copy...!
I'm checking for it now!
Give it back...! Give it back!
What's going on,
Okabe...?! Talk to me!
I'll call you right back!
Enough with the shouting! Give
it a rest, for cryin' out loud!
Give it to me!
Gimmie back my phoooone!
Gimmie the phone! It's mine!
Calm... down...!
Guess I better check it out...
I...
The hell're you--?
You should be ashamed, goin'
at it with the door wide open...
The hell is wrong with people?
What can I do...?
What can I do...
to make you give it back?
Do you remember sending
yourself a D-mail...?
What...? I don't... I...
You, got a message...
A very strange one, two weeks
ago... From your future self.
How'd you know...?
Tell me what it said...
and you get your phone back...!
Must've been something
important, right...?!
The IBN 5100, perhaps...
a meet-up with your
gun-toting thugs?!
Tell me what it said!
I know it's gotta be
something like that--
it's written on your damn face!
I'll break it--I
swear to god I will!
I'll never betray them.
"Them" who?!
FB, Moeka?
My life... is empty
without FB...
FB gives me
guidance... purpose...
"Purpose"?! So FB's
calling the shots...?!
You're not going to tell me...
Because you're such a
loyal little foot-soldier...
Even now... when it's obvious
that your precious FB
doesn't give a good
goddamn about you!
You've been written off!
FB has abandoned you!
I'm not gonna
fall for your lies...!
But they don't write
back, do they...?!
And you know why
that's happening......?!
They don't need you anymore!
No!
FB would never
just throw me away!
I was lost... FB...
rescued me...
...in Cabinet Office...
"Rescued you?"...
They condemned you...!
Rounder Recruitment
Ask me why I would say something
like that... Go ahead...!
FB is like...
is like a mother to me...
A Question
What sort of work
would I have to do?
Re: A Question
I possess a
text-based time machine...
You messaged yourself
from the future with it!
Another Question
Even work I could do?
Re: Another Question
Of course. We offer everyone
the job that best suits them.
FB... made me
feel so needed...
I've never had a job before.
I don't have any skills, either.
It's okay.
Let's do our best together.
You wanna know how your
FB fairy-tale ends...?!
'Course you do...!
You ready...?
You die... Four days from now,
you take your own life.
Huh...?
You sit here waiting for
a text that never comes...
and then you kill yourself,
here in the dark!
That's a lie.
You know in your heart
that you are never going to
hear from FB again, Moeka...
It's torture, isn't it...?
Worse than death!
Stop it...!
When's the last time
they responded...? Huh?!
Poor, patient Moeka...
abandoned yet again...!
You're going to die,
Moeka...! Right here...!
No...!
You're going to murder yourself,
surrounded by darkness!
No...
You know what your grand
reward is for killing Mayuri?!
You die like a stray mutt!
Forgotten until they
trip over your corpse!
FB--!
FB won't help!
All it would take is
a single text, right?!
But they don't care!
Nooooo!
I'm sorry...
I assume FB is a woman...
You did say before they
were like a mother to you.
I guess...
You guess?
We've never met in real life...
I don't ever wanna...
What's the point......?
I'm sure she would hate me...
You've never even
spoken on the phone
with each other
before, have you...
Why are you so
committed to this woman?!
She made me feel
like... I belonged...
What and that's all?
You're a fool...! So did we...!
The retro-PC is
in Yanabayashi Shrine.
Recover it immediately.
Okabe?!
You call that "calling
me right back"?!
What's the matter...?
Were you worried about me?
No...! Maybe.
Oh. I'm sorry.
What'd you learn?
Wait, so... the IBN
5100 was stolen by...
Moeka, yeah.
Well, where is it right now?!
I wish I could tell you...
It won't matter anyway
after we undo her message.
The new one's going back
to 11 a.m. on July 31st.
Don't go to the shrine.
It's a trap. It isn't there!
It's activated!
This should do it...
Not again...!
What?
It didn't work!
So, the message is
about the right thing,
but the past her
didn't believe it?
I'll prep the Phone Wave
and you can send her another!
She'll have to believe one
sooner or later, right...?!
No...
There's only one person who
Moeka is going to believe.
If she gets a D-mail from
that particular number...
she'll obey in a heartbeat.
Who is it...?!
I'm going out to find FB.
I don't suppose that
you have any leads.
Not that you would
tell me, anyway.
When you were yelling...
you told me that I killed
somebody... Will that happen?
Yes... Would you, if FB asked?
Without question... I would.
Even if you knew she was
about to throw you away?!
Because that is
exactly what happens...!
And then you cave
in under the despair!
Four days from now, you're
going to commit suicide...
Deny it all you want, but that's
what's fated to happen...!
There's no escape!
Luckily... I don't leave
things to fate anymore.
I've fought against
it far too long!
I'll keep fighting...
until Mayuri is safe!
The coin lockers...
At the Dai Building...
The computer is
inside one of them...
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten