Huh? What are you doing?
Impossible...
How...?
You're... You're alive!
Are you a zombie?!
I'm about to scream bloody
murder here in a second, mister.
Look, I only want to
get to the bottom of this.
Where are the stab wounds?
What is your trauma?!
Get away from me!
Feel free to slap him
if he gets too grabby.
You were skewered like a pig!
I saw it plain as day!
Not more than three hours ago,
during Dr. Nakabachi's lecture--
Ix-nay on the azy-cray, dude.
We've been over this,
the doctor's lecture
never happened, remember?
But, I...!
Excuse me... They're
ready for you now, ma'am.
Uh... Coming.
You can't just saunter off!
No you don't.
You are sick.
Far from it!
I am Hououin... Kyouma!
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Time Travel
Paranoia
Are Time Machines Possible?
First off, thanks
for coming today.
I appreciate it.
Um... It's only fair to
warn you I'm really not
all that accustomed
to speaking publicly,
so you'll have to strap in
and bear with me a little bit.
Wow, she's cutting
her teeth on us?
So I guess a zombie's
out of the question...
Will you get over this please?
Time machines will be the focus
of our discussion
this afternoon.
Kind of left
field from the topic
covered in my article,
I realize, but...
I'll try my best to
sound semi-coherent.
Coincidence, surely.
Personally, my assertion...
...is that they're no more
real than the boogey man...
Tantalizing to consider,
perhaps, but framed objectively,
something any serious physicist
simply outgrows--
Objection!
I'm sorry?
"No more real than
the boogey man..."
HA! Your evidence,
skeptic, please!
I hope no one saw
me come in with you.
That's not really...
Well-established
theoretical foundations
in virtually every branch of
physics argues against the idea.
I'm not a lone nut.
Pray continue.
Alright then... Fine...
You're so keen,
let's do this open forum...
Wouldn't want the conversation
hijacked by entrenched
nay-sayers, now would we?
Agreed...? Hououin Kyouma?
That infuriating...
Safe to say string theory
doesn't gibe with the notion
of bouncing around through
time in a blue police box...
However charming that sounds...
Any argument from you, sir?
So much for Gödel's view...
Let's forge ahead to
the next contender...
That is, I should say...
if I'm not moving too fast...
That concludes my reasoning with
regard to the quantum view...
Unless of course the
gentleman would like
to point out
something I missed...
Feel free to jump in, sir.
Auuuugh!!
Why must she be so
damnably articulate...?!
Blast...
I'm gonna leave you to
ramble, go find some AC...
Clearly the bastards
mean for this
to escalate into full-out
psychological warfare...
Easy enough though...
I'll just beef up my defenses.
Yanagibayashi
Shrine
Eight!
Nine... One more to go...
You can do it!
Ten!
And the great Ruka
is victorious...!
Oh...! Hey, Okarin's
here! Too-too-roo!
Huh? Oh, Okabe... Uh,
I mean Kyouma... Sorry.
Don't tell me the password
has slipped your mind yet again.
Huh? Oh, right.
Um, El Psy... Concrete?
Congroo, I'm sure you mean.
That's the one, yes.
Right-o, so what did
you need me to carry?
Oh, it's right here...
I kinda...
Well, you might say
I wasn't expecting the shrine
to give us so
much corny goodness.
Father received
them as a gift...
But we can't eat enough to
keep it from going to waste.
Works out for us...
Your donation to the
lab is most appreciated...
No doubt it'll give member
morale a little boost.
Really...? You're not
just saying that, are you?
Uh, errr...
Don't you think Ruka's sword
practice is starting to pay off?
Thank you... Oka--
I mean Kyouma wanted me
to show some discipline.
The Samidare Blade is
very close to revealing
its otherworldly secrets
to you, I'm certain.
Keep at it, and you'll be
a worthy wielder in no time.
Yes, sir!
And to think, you found it in
the weapons shop for only
980 yen and they didn't even
know it was magical and stuff!
Well then, let us inspect
your progress, grasshoppa...
Demonstrate an exorcism.
Uh. Well, sure.
I guess... Except, I...
Don't really perform
them all by myself...
Father's usually around to--
Auuuuughh!!!
A malign spirit has
taken possession
of my right hand, Rukako!
Banish it before I'm forced
to do something unseemly!
Be right back!
That spirit sure likes messing
with you while you're here.
Indeed! It is insatiable!
Urushibara Ruka...
Delicate as an orchid.
Fair as a cherry blossom...
The personification of
feminine grace... And a dude.
Tall as a willow...
Slender as a reed... A dude.
Radiant in shrine
vestments... Dude.
The sun dips low in a rosy sky.
Cicadas buzz...
Ruka... is a dude.
Bye!
How cool is it that we know
someone who can do exorcisms?
Being in good with the
shrine has its perks.
Take that evile spirits! Oof!
Oopsie... Heh.
Akihabara
Police
Restricted
Area
Aww...
Don't tell me they've
blocked this off.
They had to. It's leads to the
back of the Radio Building.
Guess that makes sense.
I'll take the swag.
You've got work, right?
Hand it over.
Hmm... Aren't
you a gentleman...?
It's a late shift today,
so I'll probably just head
on home after I get out.
Hey...
You, uh...
really don't remember hearing
that scream this morning?
What? Where?
The stairwell of
the Radio Building.
Umm...
That'd be the kind
of thing to stick out.
You'd think so, yeah.
Well, anyway. Never mind.
Hahaha. You're so
random sometimes.
I don't get it.
No one remembers but me.
If this isn't some elaborate
prank, I'm losing my mind.
Open
Closed
Shuttering up early
today, Mr. Braun?
Can't speak for this Mr. Braun
fella, but I am, yeah.
Interviewing a part timer.
You're kidding me...
Has father time encroached
so swiftly that help is needed
to maintain a clientele-free
cavern like this?
Come closer and ask.
Hey, you guys!
Sorry.
That's how all the cool kids
are sayin' wassup these days.
I'm guessing she's
not here to shop.
You stay out of this...
Gimme a name.
Amane Suzuha.
Your age?
Eighteen.
Reason for applying?
Serious CRT buff.
You're hired.
Nice bit o' vaudeville; you
should take it on the road.
Should I care what you think?
Not 'less you give a
crap about some idiot
rentin' the space above us.
An "idiot" who happens to
be none other than Hououin--!
You want me to double your rent?
Okabe Rintarou.
Nice to meet'cha!
Whacha got in the bags?
Have a look. Donations in
the form of intelligence corn.
I could, part with
an ear for a song...
Groddy. Looks like it's made
of little yellow blisters...
Cool to see how it
starts out, though.
You've never seen...?
Lemme touch it!
Easy.
Be warned, girl...
Many a passing
acquaintance of mine
has been hounded
by the Organization...
Sara. Dear Claudia.
Innocent Simone...
That's so tragic... Well,
I don't frighten easily, mister.
Please don't
encourage the guy...
He's whacked enough as it is.
Yeah?
Ha! Just keep telling
yourself that, Cue Ball.
One day, the world shall
tremble beneath my feet.
So... Evil laughs are trendy?
Unknown satellite crashes near Akihabara Station, around 12:00...
The crash was right around noon.
Then that corroborates
Daru and Mayuri...
Professor Nakabachi's Press Conference Cancelled
So it was cancelled.
"Makise Kurisu..."
Working hypothesis: Reality
and my brain are at odds.
Huh? What do we have here?
A time traveler's here! lololol
SERN maintains a strict monopoly
on the time machine market...
Civilians and corporations alike
are banned from acquiring one.
This is how they've
been able to implement
their vision unchecked;
why the world's the way it is.
I'm here to reroute the past
for the sake of your future.
I've come to take down SERN
and thwart the dystopian mess
they've created in my own time.
I'm here to protect freedom.
Aren't you worried
that by being here
you run the risk of
creating a paradox?
Ah, the so-called
'Grandfather Paradox?'
257 Name: Nameless Prophet-san [sage]
All I can think of is the European Laboratory for Particle Physics.
It doesn't exist.
451 Name: Nameless Prophet-san [sage]
If you time travel, can you meet yourself in the past?
It's possible to
meet your past self.
You'll simply change
world lines if you do.
What's a world line?
Inb4 parallel worlds.
You have to let go of this
idea of time as a single line
moving from past to future.
It's actually comprised of
infinite lines all
running parallel.
We call these "world lines."
Let's say for example
someone murdered you.
By traveling back
in time to prevent it,
I create two divergent worlds:
one where you're killed,
one where you're not.
The same basic idea is
true of all such actions.
The traveler splits off
to a different world line.
So his thing now
is he's Japanese...?
He rears up on U.S.
message boards back in 2000,
claiming he's from 2036...
...alludes to a
war-ravaged future
he's traveled back in time to
try and steer us clear of...
...takes the internet and every
underground publisher by storm.
Still, though... You'd think
a decade would've cooled
down the imitators by now.
618 Name: Nameless Prophet-san [sage]
Pretending to be? Huh?
Come on, stop giving me
dead links. It's annoying.
Damn it! Why'd you have to nix
all your files on the S.O.B.?
John Titor            About 12 Results
A dozen results...? No way.
Ten years ago every chode
with a .com address
was on top of this thing!
Impossible!
John Titor      About 56 results
No, no, no... This is wrong...
I had books about him on
this shelf! I'm certain I did!
Daru. It's me.
This better be good,
dude. I'm with Faris.
Where'd you move my books?!
I'm sorry?
The ones I had on
John Titor, man...
Look, I've always kept
them in the same place...
Tell me you moved them!
Wait. Slow down.
What?!
Who the Hell is
John Titor...? Dude?
I spent all night trying to
turn up pay dirt on the man...
No stone unturned, no forum
un-scoured... And yet...
"I have a question
for you, Titor...
About ten years ago...
The year 2000, in other words...
That's an interesting
topic you bring up.
Unfortunately, however, I've
never visited the year 2000.
Nor do I have any plans to.
Excuse me...?!
What in the...?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa! Not so fast!
Er, that is to say, hold the
phone just a moment please!
Or rather, delete the
pictures you just took of me
from your phone
for your own safety!
I'm sorry... Apparently
I've offended you in some way.
What were you
taking pictures of?
Evidence.
Evidence I was here... I mean...
Of the stuff I've seen...
I suppose you could say.
Can I show you something?
Sure?
This.
Quite the dinosaur
you've got there, miss.
You're an expert?
Sorry.
Do you know anyone who is?
Well, uh, Daru, but...
A friend of yours, I guess?
I don't think that's
any of your business...
Kindly delete those
pictures, if you would.
I need this Daru's
contact info. Please.
I think not!
I don't believe this...
You're trying to
strong-arm me, aren't you?
I'll delete it, if you tell me.
Uh... Ah... Very well then...
But you're mistaken if you
think I'll sell out a cohort...!
I'll give you my contact info.
What name should I type?
Can't you read?
It says Hououin
Kyouma right there!
Oubouin Kyouma
Fine... Allow me.
'Kay. Just send me
a blank text, then...
I'll reply back when
I have a free moment.
Welcome home, Meow-ster!
We've been waiting for y--
Oh! I didn't know it was you...!
Well then welcome
home meow-ster Okarin.
So... How's tricks, May?
It's Meow-ushii while
I'm on the clock, silly...
Ohhhh, you know what?
We should find a way to
make your name kitty-ish too.
How bout Rrrowkabe?
Is Daru around?
Oh, he's lounging in the back.
Kyouma!
What happened to your solemn
oath to darken our doorway
every three days, you
big goofy Frankenstein?
Ah... Blame the
Organization, love.
Oh... You poor thing!
What have they done now...?
Tell me you've got a plan!
Whatever it is, you
know we've got your back!
In good time... I'll take my
usual Stealth Field, thank you.
Hang on now... When're
you gonna let me join?!
Faris...! I cannot let you fight
my battles in good conscience.
Not even when I've mastered
my super secret special move?
Do what...?!
Surely you can't have
perfected it so quickly...
Oh, but indeed I have...
Months of hardship in the Guiana
Highlands couldn't deter me,
nor the death of
my beloved master...
No...! I have the power!
You do realize I hate you now...
So, about my text message...
Seriously. I'm not talking
to you. You're dead to me.
Ugh... Stop worrying...
I have no interest in a girl
who spews naught but falsehoods.
Watch it... I can't allow you
to talk about my girl that way.
Strong words for a Don Juan...!
Your precious harem
know you're here?
Nice try, chief... It doesn't
count if I fool around
on 'em with a flesh
and blood woman!
Okay. Change of
subject, please...
Here. Have a look at this.
Whoa... That's your classic
IBN Fifty-one-hundred.
Is that a big deal?
Dude, it's not just retro, it's
like the rarest of the rare.
'Bout a month ago,
word through the grapevine
had one floatin'
around here somewhere.
Your new friend and me probably
troll the same message boards.
And?
It hasn't turned up yet.
Knight Heart couldn't
even get a lock on it,
so my bet is the
whole thing was
just a rumor someone
threw out there
to light a fire under
the local antiquing crowd.
What do you think it's worth?
Well it's been
about thirty years
since they had
'em on the market...
PCs were still so pricey
back then not many people
had the scratch lyin'
around to buy one...
Kinda the dark ages, in a way.
Really...
Ah... and speak of the devil...
It would appear
this Kiryuu Moeka
is a woman on a
bit of a mission.
Sender: The Lightning Shiatsu-ist
Subject: I'm waiting
Hououin, I sent that mail! I'm Kiryuu Moeka!
Age 20! No real job!
I can mail you, right?
I'm sending it, whether you like it or not!
Moeka
Oh joy, the plot thickens: she's
a "freeter"--whatever that is.
And evidently only a person
of few words in person. Great.
What's up?
You owe me a lunch
for not unleashing this
chatty Kathy on you, man...
"Sorry. No dice...
My sources say it was probably
just a rumor... El Psy Congroo."
Bon appetit, Meow-sters!
Eat while it's hot.
Bitchin'! Prepare
to be impressed...
The
World's
in Danger!!
I'm about to do some damage!
Keep it in your pants.
Oh man, this is
heaven on a plate!
The
World's in Dang
er!!
I'll be sure to send your
compliments along to the chef.
Analysis: the gel-nanas,
hitherto fore so to be named,
have been ripped asunder
at the molecular level.
Hmm... They're basically
mutant bananas, you mean...
That can't be good. What do
you s'pose is causing it?
I think you'll agree the
only conceivable explanation
at this stage is some sort
of uncommonly intense EM wave.
What's your basis?
A mad scientist's
intuition, my friend.
Gotcha. Flyin' by the
seat of our pants.
Ready when you are, boss.
Superlative! Let us
then commence!
Property of Mayushii
Uh, you really wanna use these?
Fear not, Double-O 3.
These specimens are the fruit
of Mayuri's generous donation...
Yeah, they're hers.
We haven't time to quibble
over particulars, Hack,
for this is science.
Okay, but I think
one's more than enough.
Just note, while I was
willing to up the ante,
you remain a one
banana Cautious Carl.
You know,
I refuse to be insulted by
the guy who named this machine.
Phone Wave (Real
Name TBA) happens to be
a clever ruse to throw the
Organization off our scent.
Well, you're the only idiot here
who thinks they're sniffin'.
Oh is that a fact?
Just callin' it
like I see it, man.
Done.
What is it?
It's gone! Look!
Impossible!
Red alert...
Implement emergency lock-down
protocol Theta 666 immediately.
Don't give me that!
Damn you, there's no time to
push this through parliament!
Right now? Seriously?
Is this your idea of a joke?!
Uhh... Hey, if anyone's gettin'
punked here it's me.
Look, either you've palmed it
or we have a
teleporter on our hands!
A what? You think
it teleported??
Come on... That's crazy talk.
Crazy talk, is it...?!
Open your eyes!
How else does an
ordinary banana go from--
How. The. Hell...?
Um... That's funny...
I could've sworn we tore it
off from the rest of 'em...
Funny. I could've sworn I saw
you do it not a minute ago.
Yeah... That's what I thought.
I think... we might
be on to something.
Kinda seems like it, huh?
Interesting experiment
you've got going on there,
Okabe Rintarou... or wait...
I'm sorry, is it Hououin Kyouma?
Makise Kurisu...!
kisei sareta chikai mujihi nari juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
All those are being rewritten