Because that's exactly
what happens...!
And then you cave
in under the despair!
Four days from now, you're
going to commit suicide...
Deny it all you want,
but that's what's
fated to happen...!
There's no escape!
Luckily... I don't leave
things to fate anymore.
I've fought against
it for far too long!
And I'll keep fighting...
until Mayuri is safe!
The coin lockers...
At the Dai Building...
The computer is
inside one of them...
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Finalize
Apoptosis
Okabe...? What are
you looking for...?
Crowbar...! Explain later...!
No, not later--right now!
So she stashed a super-rare
computer in some coin locker...?
That's what she told me!
And somehow
nobody's come for it yet!
Huh... What now?
It's obvious, isn't it?!
I'm going to pry that
coin locker open!
You can give it a try.
But it probably won't work.
Yeah?! And why's that?!
Think of your results.
You've undone
D-mail after D-mail,
but it hasn't gotten you
any closer to the 5100.
So... maybe you
can only get the IBN
by going back to
the first world-line...
And to do that... you
have to do things in
order--no cutting corners.
Here we've finally found it...
and it does us no good...
Don't be so quick
to write off this lead.
She took the computer...
because this FB person wants
it in SERN custody, right...?
Ask yourself...
what's it doing in the
coin-locker...? C'mon...
She's handing it
off--of course...!
Stake out the lockers...
and we'll find FB...!
What're you doing here?
Bread
If she's coming...
I wanna see her.
But I thought you were
afraid she would hate you...
That's not a concern anymore?
Whoever she is...
I wanna know.
Does it matter?
I'm not sure.
Well, either way... we
won't be waiting together,
that's for damn sure.
Fine... I guess a little
company won't kill me...
What?!
Is something wrong?
Uh, no. It's fine, honey...
Why're you waiting
there with Moeka...?!
Have you lost your
damn mind...?!
You know she's dangerous...!
Look, it just happened, okay...?
I'll call as soon as I
have something to report.
Hey, what the hell...?!
That's just great...
That Okarin?
Oh, uh... yeah.
What's the matter?
I'm kinda sad, that's all...
It just feels like Okarin
and I haven't talked
much in a long time.
Heya, Mayuri!
Nae!
Too-too-roo!
You get one too,
Assistant Girl! Too-too-roo!
How 'bout you
call me Kurisu?
Ladies.
Afternoon, sir...
Sorry about yesterday...
Tell Okabe he's getting a
rent hike worth his kidney.
Uh... okay...
I didn't see
him once today.
Not that you'll hear
me complain...
Is he feelin' under
the weather...?
A cold may be the only thing
a freak like him can catch!
Uh-huh...
I, think he's out tracking
down parts for an experiment...
Course he is, right...?
Lucky bastard's
livin' the good life.
Huh...?
A young guy like him with
a room all to himself...
good friends like you two
and the husky kid...
Farts around all day...
Pretty sweet deal, right...?
While it lasts...
Dad, we gotta go...!
We're gonna miss the sale if
we just keep standing here!
All right! Then giddy-up!
Okay!
Bye, Mayuri! Bye, Kurisu!
See ya later!
So, Miss Bossy, whaddya
want for dinner?
Hmm... lemme
think about it...!
Perusing old
messages from FB?
Mhmm.
May I read one?
Let's... see... "I think you
made the right decision, M4..."
"To be honest...
no one has worked as hard
and intently as you, M4."
Who's this "M4"?
That's the codename
FB assigned me.
It's just between us...
Only she and I know it.
So it's special.
"Try not to put
yourself down...
Having a social phobia's
nothing to be ashamed of...
It's okay... In fact, I think
it's part of what makes
you such a unique person,
wouldn't you agree...?"
How very maternal of her...
That's it. On the dolly...
The IBN 5100...
Wait, so... that's... FB?
No. FB's a woman...
I'm sure of it.
Jackpot...!
Shinjuku... Now at Shinjuku...
I got work after this--can
you believe it?
Man, that's rough. I'm sorry.
See ya later.
Take it easy okay? Heh.
Damn it all...!
Hey...What's the matter?
I'll tell you later, okay?
That's... Mr. Braun...!
When's the last
time you drove a car?
At my driving test.
In that case, easy does it.
The big guy... Have
you seen him before?
I've never laid eyes on him.
What's he got to do with it?
Four days from now, you're
going to commit suicide...
Deny it all you want, but that's
what's fated to happen...!
There's no escape!
And it's on a plane
bound for France...
It's headed to SERN, no doubt...
And not a single woman along
the way who fit the profile.
Why the hell didn't you call?!
I've been on stakeout.
Cut me some slack.
I don't care either way...
It's just that, Mayuri does.
Strange how it feels... like we
haven't talked for a while now.
She really misses you, Okabe.
I'm sorry.
We're leaving.
Huh?
It's confrontation time.
Wait, hold on...
Confront who...?
He's been right beneath
our noses the whole time.
Well...! What brings
you 'round so early?
Why don't ya come on in...
So, what can I do ya for?
Ah, I got it...
You came to apologize
for all the trouble
you're causing, didn't you?
Oh, lighten up, kid...
When I told your
girlfriends here I
was gonna hike up
the rent on your place, I
wasn't serious about it, jeez.
There is something
I have to ask you.
Wow... You're polite
when it suits ya...
You're in cahoots with
an individual who goes
by the name of FB.
There isn't any point
in denying it...
I saw you send the 5100
off to the airport myself.
Look, We don't want
any trouble, okay...?
A meeting with FB--that's
all we ask of you...
Please, Mr. Braun...
How can we locate her?
Couldn't keep your
trap shut--huh, M4?
That, was the secret code
name given to me by FB...
Nobody else knew about
it, just me... and her...
But that would mean...!
How's it even possible...?!
Any idea why Okabe
calls me Mr. Braun?
You sell Braun tube
TVs... Y'know, CRTs.
Right you are, girl... And
who invented those tubes?
F... B...Ferdinand
Braun--of course!
No, you can't be...!
You're a man...!
I never once told you
I was a woman, did I?
Let's take this somewhere
else. Nae's sleeping.
They're always building.
Can't leave well enough
alone, can they...
And you're really... FB...?
Yeah.
But the messages...!
They were so...!
So "motherly"... right?
I did it to fool you, M4.
Guess I did a good job, huh?
No...
You weren't the only one.
Hell, that's my MO...
I tailor everyone's messages
according to who they
need to hear from most.
And of course...
it sure doesn't hurt any
that the lonely ones
tend to be pretty naïve.
Why'd you end up cutting
off contact with Moeka?
She outlived her
usefulness the moment
she put the IBN into that
coin locker for me...
So I cut her loose.
That's why we do all of
our recruiting through
text-messaging...
Lonely people do
what you tell 'em to...
Then later, they disappear
without a trace...
And nobody ever cares
enough to ask what happened
to 'em once they're gone.
I can't believe that you're
nothing more than a SERN dog...!
Woof woof.
Dammit, Mr. Braun... Suzuha
wouldn't have wanted this...!
She opened her door to
you... this's how you
honor her memory?!
Shut up... You don't get
to shame me like that.
Where do you get off,
dragging her into this...?!
This has nothing to
do with Suzuha...
It does!
What do you know,
you coddled little shit?!
How many winter nights
you spend huddled up
in some culvert...?
The concrete was freezing.
Hurt your bones, it was so
cold... I was just a kid...
Three, fours days straight
I wouldn't eat...
And when I'd lay down to
sleep... they'd come runnin'...
Who?
Well the rats of course...
They'd gnaw at me,
thinking I was dead.
I ain't made o' stone...
When someone threw
a rope down to me...
I grabbed the hell on.
Knew I'd never get a
chance like that again...
I've had to do some terrible
things along the way:
but hey, nothing in this
world is free, right?
Eventually, you come to realize
you're not climbing a rope...
You're dangling from
a noose... kicking...
And cutting yourself
loose just isn't a choice.
That's when your old
pal FB is there for you...
Oh my god... Moeka.
She wasn't gonna get
out of this alive
either way, you know...
Traitor or not, the girl'd
outlived her usefulness.
You're wrong about
me being a dog.
Nah, I'm a Judas goat...
Leading the lambs to slaughter.
Y'know, I thought about
making a run for it.
But that's no life for a kid,
growing up on the lamb.
I didn't wanna get my girl
mixed up in this shit.
But I failed. And
failure gets punished.
If I try to skip town though...
then they'll kill her.
There's only one way out...
one way that guarantees
they'll leave Nae alone.
Only thing I gotta do is die...
Wait--!
O... Oka... be...
Don't... leave me a... lone...
I'm... sor... ry...
Can you... please
forgive... me...
The D-mail...!
Okabe...! Get the phone!
Okabe!
Stop searching for the IBN 5100,and return to stand by.
Do not act under any circumstances.
Moeka... you're...
Shining Finger
(No Subject)
I won't need the IBN 5100
for a while.
Moeka
You don't need it?
Are you... sure...?
Shining Finger
(No Subject)
My boss said to stop looking for it.
Moeka
Hi! This is Rukako speaking!
Oh! Hey, Kyouma! Wh--?
Huh...? An IBN 5100?
Actually, we do!
This is it!
Daru!
You're gonna have to yell
louder than that...
He went to Comima, remember?
I beg of you!
Hear my request, O Daru!
So you're telling us...
The only way to
prevent Mayuri dying...
some way or another...
is to erase this world-line
and hop our way back to
the one from before you
sent your first D-mail.
Basically, just undo everything.
And to finish it... Daru
is hacking into SERN...
to erase the data
that first flagged us.
It's pretty nutty, all that
stuff about Mayuri biting it
and Suzuha being
my future-kid...
If the mad-scientist
thing doesn't pan out,
you should write for one of
those time-travel shows, dude.
That is an awfully
tempting alternative.
Are you buying this, Makise?
It's got legs, as a theory...
Getting some quantifiable
data would probably
help sell me on it...
But apparently,
that's impossible.
You did a hell of
a job engineering
the time-leap machine--I
really mean that.
Huh...? Oh yeah....? Aw...
Uh...! I... mean...!
Of course I did!
You and I...
"You and I...?"
Ah, don't worry 'bout it.
Huh?! And what is
that supposed to mean?!
C'mon, just let it go.
Guess who's
hacked into SERN!
There's some
hoodoo I gotta do
before I can delete
stuff, but we should
be good to go in ten.
I've every faith in
your abilities, hack!
It's hacker, dude. Jeez.
What was the
first one about...?
The D-mail, I mean...
I guess it was
something minor, since
you never did tell me.
Aw, don't be shy...
It can't be worse than
you getting all octopus
on me when we first met.
Undoing the D-mails...
will return us to the
original world-line.
A world-line...
in which SERN's tyranny is
never allowed to take root...
But to keep Mayuri alive...
To return... to that
version of fate...
Makise Kurisu...
...must die.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten