Seriously...
World War Three?
Let me put it into
perspective for you:
that's upwards of 5.7
billion human lives snuffed out
by the year 2036.
And it all starts with this.
But... what is "this?"
Totally a mech...
Please tell me it transforms.
It's a time machine, Daru.
Sorry?
You're familiar with it...
That's good, Uncle...
Very good... I can
get to the point.
We're gonna run interference.
I refuse.
Okarin...
I've been jumping
from world-line to
world-line for weeks.
I've run interference...
So many times I'm barely
myself anymore...
The only way I was able to
land back onto this world-line
was by allowing Kurisu to die.
And now you're asking me
to go another round...?!
I refuse!
What are you talking about?
Kurisu...? Oh...
You mean the scientist
chick who got, like,
stabbed or whatever at the
Radio Building the other day?
Rintarou... Hear me out...
What if I told you the
circumstances of her
death on the afternoon
of July 28th, 2010 play
directly into what
kicked off the war...?
That the reason I'm here,
is to see to it she survives?
I'm listening.
I don't have a clue
how it all dovetails...
All I know is I've been
entrusted with an
important mission...
Rescue Makise Kurisu and
shift things to a world-line
beyond the divergence
barrier; free of the
attractor field...
A little place we
call Stein's Gate!
To you, insisting on life's merits and meaningless proofs
inochi no shuchou to muimi no shoumei
anata ni wa taikutsu shinogi ni taranu koukei
is pathetic and unfit to relieve your boredom
shihaisha kidori no orokana shuzoku wa
The conceited fools who act like they are the leaders
unuboreta chisetsuna teiri wo narabeta
are proof of a basic theorem
mugen to shinjita ai mo sora no kanata mo
A love that believed in infinity and the far side of the sky
bokutachi ni shimesareta kasou no jiyuu
were shown me by the freedom of my imagination
yuugen sore wa mujihi ni toki wo kizami
Finity mercilessly recorded the passage of time
asu sae mo hitei suru sentaku e
leading to a choice that puts my future at stake
Hacking to the Gate
ikutsu mo no kagayakeru hibi nakama to no yakusoku
I mustn't pretend that I never made a promise
nakatta koto ni wa shite wa ikenai
with my friends back in the day
sono tame ni toki wo azamuku nokosareta shikake ni
So now I try to beat time itself with the gadgets I am left with,
mou mayoi wa nai kodoku no kansokusha
and I observe alone in my solitude, but never doubt myself
Open the
Steins Gate
I don't believe it...
You actually hatched this
plan yourself...
By that I mean you will...
With dad...
Though you're the first
to admit it's pure conjecture...
Push comes to shove,
it's possible this is
all wishful thinking...
Even if a Stein's Gate
world-line exists,
the odds of us reaching
one are slim to none.
Odds be damned,
though: I'm all in...
As you always like to remind us:
nothing ventured,
nothing gained, right...?
If a future without World War
Three is worth the risk to you.
Take my hand.
Um... Okay to be honest,
I don't think I understood very
much of what just got said...
But...
This friend of yours...
This Makise Kurisu...?
Sounds to me like she's
worth taking a chance, right?
I, say you should go for it!
Face it, chief.
It's your cuppa tea...
All this World War Three
stuff seems, well...
No offense, you understand,
but tailor-made for your
special brand of crazy.
I do this for her, no
one else... Got it?
Whatever gets you there.
Climb aboard!
It can actually carry two?
Well, yeah... Like
this puppy's inventor
would've have skimped on
installing a backseat...
Be careful.
Leave your cell
phone here.
We'd all be screwed five
ways from Tuesday if it
crossed signals with the one
your past self'll be carrying.
Watch it for me?
Good luck, guys.
Nice, uh... set up you got.
Thanks... Works like a charm;
I've already stopped off
at 1975 and 2000...
She's running low on fuel,
though... That's the thing...
You've got to watch the
indicators like a hawk.
Wait. So we can not only go
backward in time, but forward?
I should hope so...
What the in hell'd be the
point if we couldn't?
I see... This one must come
from a different world line
than its twin...
Have a seat... I'm setting
coordinates for the day of,
just shy of twelve o'clock...
I don't dare go back any
further because I can't
change our position.
If we stir up trouble
at the Radio Building
it might throw Kurisu's
movements out of whack.
We're about to pull an
ungodly amount of Gs here,
so you might want
to prepare yourself.
Okarin...
What are these?
They come with the territory.
Little beads of time...
Kinda pretty, huh?
Come on.
Sorry. I, uh... just need to
let my stomach settle a bit...
Somebody's a wuss...
Hurry it up!
'Kay, critical point:
avoid running into your
past self at all costs...
We could have a major paradox
on our hands otherwise...
How long do you
think this'll take?
Uh... Well... Maybe twenty
minutes, give or take?
Alright, I'm going to stay
here and prep the time machine
for our return trip, and you do
what you can to save Makise.
Wish me luck.
July 28th...
The day I found
Kurisu on the floor,
soaked in her own blood...
Mayuri and I had come to
see Dr. Nakabachi's lecture
and were waiting for it
to start when we heard
a sound on the roof...
That's right.
This must be when Mayuri
heads to the vending machines
on the seventh floor.
Is anything not
an emergency?
I'm sorry. I know
sometimes it's not,
but this one counts for sure.
Better play it safe. I'll take
the far stairs back to eight.
I don't believe it...!
A metal Oopa!
And that's good?
You bet it is!
Should be safe now...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ku... Kurisu...
Um... have we met before?
No... This is too much...
I don't... think
I know you... do I?
Kurisu...
Look, whoever--
What is your trauma...?
Don't rush to help me
or anything...
I, uh...
I'm just... Here to see...
Your attention, please.
Doctor Nakabachi's
conference is about
to begin in the 8th
floor lecture hall.
All interested are welcome.
At least finish a sentence!
Printed on the handouts
there in front of you
is more or less the hard
blueprint for one of
mankind's oldest ambitions...
Professor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
Of course, the
theoretical scaffolding
begs some explanation.
As I'm sure you're aware,
mainstream science currently
boasts something like
In the brief I was given,
they said you'd be able to pick
her out instantly. Is that true?
Yeah.
Right. Bear in mind, though...
It's probably a bad idea
to take her off site.
We don't know who
kills her or why.
And in the event that
her death is a fixed
point on the timeline,
we don't want things
getting more complicated.
I learned that the
hard way with Mayuri.
Doctor!
Save your questions...
I have none, sir...!
I throw down the gauntlet as
to your "theory's" authorship!
Do you take us all for
babes in the wilderness...?!
Please! World lines?
Kerr Black Holes...?
Any moment now, this is
where she'll end up...
What on earth
am I going to do?
Wait! What if she's
killed somewhere else
and dragged here...?
Damn it! I hadn't
thought of that!
There she is...
This is where it happens...
What is that she's reading...?
Time machines...?!
Is that why so much
is riding on this?
Stupid kids...
What in the hell
do you want?
Look, please... I just want
you to read this... 'kay Dad?
"Dad?!"
Nakabachi's her dad?!
Look, I... I'm just trying
to bury the hatchet...
It's been years...
Too damn long...
I want you in my life again.
Don't tell me her
father's the one who...!
I put on my thinking cap,
as you like to say, and well...
I'm now convinced that
you were right all along.
I wanted your opinion
on the theory.
If this paper gets accepted...
you can lord it over all the
stuffed shirts who laughed
you out of the academy.
I did not get "laughed out!"...
I turned my back on their
politics to pursue my
researches unfettered!
Sorry...
This isn't half bad.
Really?! 'Cause I was
thinking, maybe,
if you were okay with the
idea, we could publish it
under both our names.
I mean, after all,
you're the one who
inspired me to write it--
Don't be ridiculous...
Go home.
What?
If this paper sees the light of
day, it'll do so under my name.
Excuse me?! That's
called stealing!
I knew you could be cruel, but
I never thought you'd stoop to--
Shut up!
You dare call me a thief?!
Bitch! What makes you
think you're so much
better than me...?!
A daughter's got no
goddamn right to
outshine her father!
Every second you're
out there whoring
to make a name for yourself,
you trample my reputation
as a genius of the age!
You were my heckler,
weren't you...?
Heh... I see... You were in
cahoots to make nattering
ol' Nakabachi shit the bed
during what should've been
his moment of glory...
Well, You succeeded.
But success comes at
a price.
Dad, no!
Stand your ground;
protect her!
Where's your heckling now...?
Come on, let's hear it!
Son of bitch...
Dad, this is crazy...!
Please stop!
So I'm crazy...?! I'll show
you crazy!!!
Look out!
You're an idiot...
A DNA fluke...!
You're not as smart as me...!
My name belongs in the annals
of history... You're nothing!
Daddy, please...
If it hadn't been for you...
I wouldn't be the academic
laughing stock I am now!
Stop!!!
Oh god...
Oh my god...!
Look at that... Poetic
justice all around, I'd say.
I'm sorry... I didn't mean...
What...?
I didn't mean to
drag you into this...
I just wanted him to...
To acknowledge me...
Kurisu...
I'm so scared. I... I... don't
want to die... I'm not ready...
This wasn't...
wasn't supposed to...
No... oh god...
Please no!
Neat-o! They're already back!
Okarin!
Whoa. Dude...! What the
hell happened to you?!
He's gonna be alright...
It's, just... a little
bit complicated...
I'm responsible for
her death...
I'm responsible for her
death... I'm responsible
for her death...
I'm responsible for her death...
Okarin...
Walk it off...
Look, I know you're in shock,
but you've got to
pick yourself up...
We've got enough
fuel for one more trip
and now we know how
things play out, so--
No! I won't do it...!
I won't put myself
through that again!
Whatever I do,
Kurisu will always die...
Okarin, it's your phone.
A text?
Open it.
I shouldn't...
Just do it.
Turn on the TV.
It says to turn on the news.
Seriously?
Despite the cargo bay fire,
Dr. Nakabachi's plane
managed to land safely
within the borders of
the former Soviet Union,
to which he'd recently defected.
Fate was certainly
smiling on me...
If this guy hadn't set off
the onboard metal detectors...
Mayushii
My thesis would've
been barbequed.
That's my metal oopa!
I know it is...! See look!
I wrote my name on the side
right after Okarin
bought it for me!
No, I see. It's just,
why's it in Russia?
That thesis of his...
That's what starts
World War Three.
It basically
sparks an arms race,
only the goal is which country
can build a time machine first.
Take first place
and win the world...
That's how it starts, but things
get hostile pretty quick...
Then war... Then people are
getting killed in droves.
The lives of 5.7 billion
people are at stake here...
Save Makise Kurisu... and
you save every one of them.
I can't do it.
Things'll end up just
as they did with Mayuri.
No matter what
I did, she died...
There's no point...
It's all the same.
No! You only tried once!
You can't say that!
Once?! ...Are you mad?
I tried dozens of times!
And every time, I failed!
Believe me, I know...
You may not think I do, but
I know how cruel time can be...
We like to imagine we can
bend it to suit us, but...
This was bound to happen.
It was stupid of me to play
along... I'm sorry, but...
I'm... I'm just done...
Let time have it's way.
Since when have you
been the type of person
who's "just done"?
You're not fooling me.
You've never given up
on anything, ever...
Remember when I couldn't bring
myself to say bye to grandma...?
You went to her grave
every day for me until I
was ready to do it myself.
You never got mad
and you never quit...
And because of that I was
finally able to let her go.
So, no... I'm not letting
you throw in the towel.
Listen, a video file
should've turned up
in your inbox on July 28th.
That's right... I'd forgotten...
It should be viewable now...
You had to fail saving her
once before it would unlock,
so to speak.
What the hell are you
talking about?!
I apologize...
I know it was a lot to put
you through, but things
had to be this way...
The whole point was
for you to see that file.
Is that...?
Hale and well met...
Old friend.
Is that you?!
That you're able to
open this means
you've seen firsthand
what became of Makise
and failed to prevent it.
I feel for you. I really do.
That said, the pain
you're going through
right now is necessary.
I daren't deny you
--us--the bitter
inspiration it represents.
Without it, you cannot hope
to carve out your destiny.
Now we can marshal our
resources properly.
I hereby charge you with the
task of reaching Stein's Gate...
To do so, two conditions
are absolutely essential:
one, you must destroy
Nakabachi's ill-gotten
time travel thesis before it
crosses into Russia's borders...
Second, you must
rescue our beloved Kurisu.
But how?! I've tried--
I'm fully aware
that the grisly nature
of her death appears be set
in stone due to its position
within the so-called alpha
attractor field. However...
I'll just come right out with
it: it is possible to save her.
You're simply going
about it the wrong way.
Listen carefully: you must
not--I repeat, not--
alter any detail surrounding
her death as witnessed by you.
That is, the version of
yourself prior to the
botched rescue attempt
that allowed you to
view this video file...
To do so would alter the
past too drastically.
Think of your experiences
immediately following
the first D-mail: the
three weeks you spent
jumping through time
were instigated by that text.
It's what gave you
a history with her...
Your desperate,
bitterly ineffective
bids to save Mayuri...
The countless sacrifices...
The terrible Rubicons crossed.
All of that must
stay in your head.
The period spent adrift in time
constitutes your unique reality.
It must not be distorted.
To do so would be tantamount
to a betrayal of who you are.
I know that to label Kurisu's
death as traumatic is
the epitome of understatement.
Believe me, I do.
The memory of seeing her
life ebb away as I held her
in my arms haunts me still.
But the pain it wrought can be
wrought in turn to greater ends.
It what's brings you
to yourself.
So trick yourself.
Save her without changing the
apparent fact of her death.
Convince your past self that
she's well and truly dead,
even though she lives.
Keep the past to all intents
and purposes where it is.
That's what will get
us to Stein's Gate.
Of course...!
I don't think I get it.
That goes for both of us.
I've every faith
that you understand.
Incidentally, the time
machine's model is Type C204.
I doubt I need tell you
what the C stands for.
It's for Christina...
The target world line's
charming little nickname
comes care of me as well;
which is to say,
it comes from you.
Care to guess its significance?
There's none
Bingo.
There's none.
And to further
please our whimsy...
Operation Skuld will be the
name we assign to this mission.
Forge of yesterday whatever
you must to save the future...
without detectably altering the
past as you understood them.
kako wa hanareteyuki mirai wa chikazukuno?
The past retreats, but does the future truly approach?
Okabe Rintarou sees Makise
lying dead on the ground
in a pool of her
own blood.
Keep the past, for all intents
and purposes, where it is.
kansokusha wa itsuka mujun ni kizuku
An observer would realize the contradictions there
Deceive yourself in every last
detail... Deceive the world.
kami no tsukuridashita sekai wa kanzennaru mono de zettai no kinkou
This world shaped by God is perfect and lies in absolute balance
Do this, and victory
is assured.
Best of luck to you, old
friend. El... Psy... Congroo.
sore wa orikasanaru guuzen uchuu kibo no kiseki
A superimposed coincidence, a miracle on a cosmic scale
Okay. Trippy... You have
any idea what your future
self is tellin' you?
mamoraretekita GATE "kisei" wa owatta
The restrictions on the guarded gate are now abolished
Oh wow... You get
really suave.
Open the Eyes
"zero" ga kako de "ichi" ga mirai "ima" wa dokonimo nai
"Zero" is the past and "One" is the future, "The Present" is a fabrication
"Operation Skuld..."
"El Psy Congroo..."
somuku koto no dekinu LOGIC
This is an undeniable logic
Do I never grow out of the
cloak and dagger act?
Open the Eyes
heikousuru musuu no sen sentaku wa boutoku e
Amidst the countless parallel lines, I choose blasphemy
I'll be as barking mad
then as I am now.
bokura no "sonzai" sae utagau sono me ni utsuru keshiki wa
Doubting existence itself, Those Eyes bear witness to
Yeah, but is that so bad?...
Ah to hell with it...
If Stein's Gate so decrees, then
so am I compelled to behave.
"shuusoku" o suru
Convergence
Hououin Kyouma accepts
the challenge...!
With gusto!
Deception is my forte...
Let the world beware!
Oh ho. I think the Okabe we
all know and love is back...
Uh-huh... Good thing, too...
futatsu no hari ga sasu jikan no gainen mo
Even the basic concept of time, as depicted by two hands of a clock
The Okarin who just broods
all day isn't nearly as fun.
Hear me...
privileged companions...
kansokusha shidai de hizumi o miseru
Will bend and distort to the choice of the Observer
Time is ours... Hououin
Kyouma's mind
recognizes no limit...
kami ni ataerareta eichi wa kanarazu "hate" ga aru zettai no ryouiki
The knowledge God gifted us must have some limit, an absolute territory
Neither does his reach!
Heave anchor...!
This ship of fools
is about to embark!
Sore wa oroka yue no guuzen manekarezaru kiseki
It tells us that these are foolish notions and unwanted miracles
Tozasaretekita gate "kisei" wa owatta
The gate that once was shut is supervised no more
Open the eyes
Kousoku he to te wo nobashita omoide no parusu ga
My mind wished to reach the speed of light
Tobikomu fukashigi na logic
and fell into an eldritch logic
Open the eyes
Uchuu ga mada kakushimotta chitsujo no nai riron
The lawless rules of the universe remain hidden from us
Mugen to yobareta ten to ten ga fusei na chikara wo karite
What we call eternity is but dots connected, empowering each other
"Saisei" wo suru
and resurrecting us time and time again