And to further please
our whimsy...
Operation Skuld will be
the name we assign this.
Forge of yesterday whatever
you must to save the future...
without detectibly altering
the past as you understood it...
Okabe Rintarou sees Makise
lying dead on the ground
in a pool of her own blood.
Keep the past for all
intensive purposes where it is.
Deceive yourself
in every last detail
Hey dad, hand me
that screwdriver.
Why do you keep
calling me that?
Chop chop.
Alright folks; this is
our line in the sand...
There's just enough juice
left in this puppy
for one last jump to
the past and back.
But then...
you won't be able to
return to your own time...
Total non-issue.
I never planned to.
We do this right, the future
as I know it will alter enough
so that I'll never have needed
to come here in the first place.
And that was the idea all along.
'course, the flip side
to that equation is,
if we screw this up I'm
basically stuck here for good...
a bitter ex pat stewing
in "coulda beens."
Too clichéd a fate for you.
Oh yeah?
Damn right "yeah."
You are under the
wing of Hououin Kyouma,
whose name among those
in the know resonates
with visions of topsy-turvy-dom
and inverted status-quos...
Take solace in that...
Agreed?
Agreed...
Let's do this.
Hear me...!
Operation Skuld begins now!
Let the world tremble!
To you, insisting on life's merits and meaningless proofs
inochi no shuchou to muimi no shoumei
anata ni wa taikutsu shinogi ni taranu koukei
is pathetic and unfit to relieve your boredom
shihaisha kidori no orokana shuzoku wa
The conceited fools who act like they are the leaders
unuboreta chisetsuna teiri wo narabeta
are proof of a basic theorem
mugen to shinjita ai mo sora no kanata mo
A love that believed in infinity and the far side of the sky
bokutachi ni shimesareta kasou no jiyuu
were shown me by the freedom of my imagination
yuugen sore wa mujihi ni toki wo kizami
Finity mercilessly recorded the passage of time
asu sae mo hitei suru sentaku e
leading to a choice that puts my future at stake
Hacking to the Gate
ikutsu mo no kagayakeru hibi nakama to no yakusoku
I mustn't pretend that I never made a promise
nakatta koto ni wa shite wa ikenai
with my friends back in the day
sono tame ni toki wo azamuku nokosareta shikake ni
So now I try to beat time itself with the gadgets I am left with,
mou mayoi wa nai kodoku no kansokusha
and I observe alone in my solitude, but never doubt myself
Damn it all, where are you?
Achievement
Point
I had my hands on you not a
fortnight ago, I'm sure of it!
Achievement
Point
"Let the world
tremble," he says...
Not a bad line...
Might'a had more "umph"
if you hadn't followed
it with "oh crap..."
What's the hold up, guys?
The longer we leave the time
machine parked on the roof,
the likelier it is that someone
is gonna notice it's there.
I must be getting warmer...
The Glow Stick Saber?
You stoppin' off at
a rave on the way?
I require the fake blood
cleverly hidden in its tip.
Oh, weird! You never
told me it had blood!
Ah, I get it...
Is that gonna substitute for the
pool of gore you found her in?
Exactly.
If the me from July 28th
discovers Makise's unconscious
form in said pool of gore,
he --that is, I--will
assume her dead
and the past shall be unchanged.
Thus will Operation Skuld
fulfill its purpose.
Seems solid on the face
of it, I guess, but...
I'll say it: doesn't that
gambit seem a little too,
I dunno... easy?
I mean, to my ears the future
you sounded like he had
something a lot more abstract
and convoluted in mind.
That's just what he
wanted you to think...
All evil geniuses obscure
their true intentions, Daru.
It's in their nature.
But fear not...
I see behind the veil...
My tricks are as
child's play to me!
I'm not sure whether I should
be impressed or terrified.
I'm goin' with terrified.
Hey...
Okarin...?
Um, did Kurisu, like...
sit in this chair over
here sometimes?
Maybe even a lot?
I suppose so...
I can totally remember
her sitting here,
talking to us about stuff.
Right?
When she was excited,
she'd get all serious.
Sometimes I'd have a
hard time following her.
The two of you used
to argue all the time...
But, you know...
The way really good friends do.
Man, I'll have
whatever she's having.
Trust me, May, a superstar
like Makise Kurisu
wouldn't slum it in
a cave like this.
Oh...
Yeah...
That would be kind of strange...
Maybe I just dreamed
it or something.
Or maybe Okabe's not the
only one with Reading Steiner.
Yeah, well...
That wouldn't
exactly surprise me.
By that I mean,
it's not a super power.
Everyone has it.
When world-lines break off,
deep down we all remember
how things used to be.
It makes perfect
sense to me that Mayuri
would have some
memories of Kurisu...
We're here...
That is...
Mayuri's here because Kurisu
made the ultimate sacrifice.
Listen to you...
You liked her a
whole lot... huh?
Well now...
She was my assistant...
You might even say
she was a confidant...
As vital to me as
the air I breathe...
Aaawww...
Of course, the woman
was desperately
in love with me, too.
2-D life is so much
simpler than this.
Well...
There's no question
about it , then...
You've got to save her.
But I'm bettin' you
knew that already...
Indeed.
Promise to be careful, okay?
And promise to come back!
Don't you worry.
U-umm... Miss Amane...
If it's really true that
I'm your old man or
whatever, then, uh...
Who's your mom?
Don't worry, it's a
pleasant surprise.
Sure it is...
Let's go!
Alright. Same thing as before.
Avoid running into yourself,
otherwise do what you have to.
Got it...
You leave the Glow Stick
for me at the appointed spot.
No problem.
Forge of yesterday whatever
I must to save the future,
easier said than
done, but here goes.
Not sure how all
this fits together...
But clearly the first order of
business is to prevent Mayuri
from getting her paws
on that metal oopa...
Take that out of the mix,
and the time travel
thesis will burn to cinders.
Bingo.
I'm sorry.
I know sometimes it's not,
but this one counts for sure.
These are really,
really rare, and I'm broke.
I look like an ATM to you...?
Too bad so sad, Greedy Gus...
Life lesson.
The Reality Principle does like
to disabuse us of our whims...
Ah, cool!
Oh yeah? Is it rare?
Nuh-uh, I don't think so...
But he's super cute anyway!
Done. On to the next.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ku... Kurisu...
Um... have we met before?
I don't... think I know you.
Kurisu...
Look, whoever--
What is your trauma...?
Don't rush to help
me or anything...
I, uh...
I'm just...
I've come here to
save... your life...
Your attention, please.
Doctor Nakabachi's conference
is about to begin in the
8th floor lecture hall.
All interested are welcome
At least explain what you mean!
Note to self...
Adlibbing my way through a
portrayal of past me is awkward.
Kurisu found the oopa...?
Mayushii
Of course!
Ah, but since that little
fellow is made of your
garden variety plastic,
the time travel thesis will go
up in smoke en route to Russia.
Good. Very good. Excellent!
Next phase: deflect her
homicidal maniac of a father,
and render Makise unconscious...
The blood's dried up!
Okabe you fool!
You can't seal a viscous
fluid up for heaven knows
how long and expect
it not to congeal!
What the hell do you want?
Look, please...
I just want you to read this...
Think, damn it!
There must be
something I can use!
Anything...! Surely...!
Size it up...
I can get Nakabachi out of
here; that's the easy part...
The tricky bit is the blood...
Something in this room
will have to do...!
Shut up!
How dare you call me a thief?!
That's it!
Doctor!!!
Who the hell are you?!
Who am I, he asks.
Why, Anarchy incarnate, sir!
An archon buffeted by the stormy
passions of madness and chaos!
But you would prefer
my mortal handle...
The name...
Is Hououin...
Kyouma!
I hope that's not your
idea of intimidation...
Wait, you're the damn heckler
from the conference!
I see how it is...
The two of you were
in on this together...
Planning to make nattering
ol' Nakabachi shit the bed
during what should've been
his moment of glory, huh...?
Well, m'boy...
You succeeded beautifully.
Dad, no...!
Run!
Run?
Not just yet...
The man's pulled his
knife out for a reason;
I'm curious to see what it is.
Are you out of your mind?!
That's a very good question.
But surely the issue of my
sanity is neither here nor there
for a tough old bird like you?
You're mocking me...!
Aw, sorry...
Is it hard getting
short-shrift from a living god?
Don't push me!
I'll rip your goddamn eyes
right out of their sockets!
Well, I'm right here.
Can't imagine what's
stopping you...
Unless of course you're
just a simpering blowhard...
That's it, isn't it?
Of course it is!
You're a washed-up,
spineless coward!
No... Oh god...
Dad... Wha...
What have you...?
You... You provoked, me...
Stay calm...
Bite the bullet...
Just a little more...
You... You provoked, me...
This isn't over you
crazy son of a bitch!
Oh my god. Alright, just...
Try not to move!
I'll call an ambulance!
Hello?!
Yes, I've got a man
here who's been stabbed
and is losing a lot of blood!
I told you...
We need paramedics at the
Radio Building immediately!
I came here ...to...
I came here...
to save your life.
Well done...
I think we've got it.
Oh, Kurisu...
Uncle...
Farewell.
Wait...
Please...
We have to be absolutely sure...
Look, you're just gonna
have to take it on faith.
We don't have time.
I've got to get
you out of here--
Just wait.
Uh... I know you're there.
Best of luck...
You'll need it...
The next three weeks...
Are going to be hardest
three weeks of your life.
You make me crazy,
you know that?
There are no words to
describe how stupid that was!
Stupid, perhaps. But it worked.
Listen, I've only stopped
the bleeding superficially--
get to a hospital the
minute you're back...
And hold on;
it's gonna get rough.
Here we go.
Is this...?
If you're asking me whether
we've reached Stein's Gate,
I don't know.
Guess we'll find out.
I do know that if your
theory hit the mark,
the thesis will burn...
which means the world
superpowers won't start their
time travel pissing contest...
and that World War
Three'll never happen.
Much as I might like to, I'm
afraid I can't stick around...
So, let me get out a
thank you now while I can.
It's been a trip.
Thank you...
See you in seven years.
Card: To Okarin
Card: For Okabe Rintarou-sama
Okabe
Rintarou-sama
Hey!
Huh.
Call me a crackpot if you
helps you sleep at night,
but mankind's future
was riding on that thesis!
Now it's gone!
All gone!
Such outbursts are
motivating Russian officials
to reconsider his defection.
Dang it!
He's so hard to track
down when he wants to be...
Well, if he comes back
tell him I was here.
Uh... Before you go...
This identifies you as
Lab Member Double-0 Six.
Wait...
When did I become a lab member?
Well, you probably wouldn't
yet remember your induction...
Give it time, though.
I wonder what the letters mean.
Kyouma?
He was actually just here.
Yeah?
I keep missing him...
Hey, This may sound kinda weird,
but did he give you anything?
You know, as a matter
of fact, he did...
Double-O Seven...
Guard that designation
with your life...
If ever you're in need of
assistance, cleave to that pin
and chant "La
Yoda... Stasella."
Sorry, kid: your pal went on his
merry way not two minutes ago.
Mayuri!
Oh, yeah. Manners.
This our brand new part-timer.
Nice to meet you...
My name's Kiryuu.
Took a shine to her when she got
short round here out of a jam.
Said she didn't have a job,
so I thought, eh, why not?
Shiina Mayuri.
It's funny...
Freak Show was fallin' all
over himself when he met her
and she haven't even
gotten her name out.
Consider it an open
invitation to our humble lair.
Thanks.
That's very kind of you.
Too-too-roo!
It's good to have you back-arin!
Did you just mash up "Okarin"
with "Good to have you back"?
Uh huh.
Don't tell me he's not here.
He won't be long.
Just runnin' a few errands.
Okay... Ah!
Hmm? Oh, those.
Lab Member badges, apparently.
Double-O Three for me;
Double-O Two for you.
He says they go all to
way to Double-O Eight,
but did I sleep through a
couple of meetings or something?
'Cause I don't remember
that many people
bein' on board with us.
"Okarin" must be the "O."
...Shiina, Hashida,
Urushibara, Faris, and...
Hm.
Wonder what the M,
the K and the A stand for.
Beats me...
He put the last one in a box.
Says Double-O Eight'll
show up in seven years.
I realize it may be hard
to believe, but trust me
when I say I have it on
very good authority.
That what we're callin'
the voice in your head?
You're the reason
they show up, actually.
Say what?
That's a long time...
But I'm sure whoever
it is will be super cool
and totally willing
to cosplay with me.
I'm s'posed to
wait seven years...?
My mind doesn't
go that far ahead.
Just think, though...
How much fun will it be with so
many new friends at the lab...
And I don't think
we'll change too much...
No matter how
many years pass.
Where are you now, I wonder...
Doggedly hammering away at
some ground-breaking new
thesis over in the States...?
It's not hard to see you
pulling a slew of all-nighters
in front of a dry erase board...
Well, whatever the case,
I just hope you've made peace
with your father's issues...
I've made my peace with the
fact of you having no memory
of our three weeks together...
Took a while, though...
Whether or not you and
I ever see each other again,
the world's a decidedly
better place with you in it.
As long as you're out there,
doing your thing,
we all benefit...
And bittersweet though it is,
sometimes just knowing
I'm not the only one who
sees things as I do is enough.
It...
It's you!
I've been looking
everywhere for you!
I don't even know how to
begin to say what I want to...
It's me... The jig is up.
She's wise to us...
Do what...?
What do you mean you
want me to protect her...?
Very well, just
never let it be said
I don't indulge you
lot to a fault...
Yes, I'm aware...
And if that's its choice
far be it from me to argue...
alright, then.
El, Psy Congroo.
"El what...?
So we meet
again, Christina.
Knock it off
with that crap!
My name's not "Christina,"
and I'm sure as hell
not your assistant!
Uh... Wait...
Good to have you back...
Assistant o' mine...
Christina, a.k.a.
Kurisu.
Perhaps the universe can't be
justifiably called infinite...
But the possibilities
within it...?
Different story altogether...
That much I've learned.
This...
...is the choice
of Stein's Gate.