Impossible...
Egoistic
Poriomania
Behold...
my bleak and dusty doom...
It's me...
I've fallen prey to
their wily saboteurs.
What......?!
So my current peril is...
is in fact the will...
of Stein's Gate?
Yes, of course.
Two weeks ago...
Less than, in fact...
The signs were all around me...
Plain as the nose on my face...
How could I have
been so blindsided?
Agreed... I'll check in later...
if this arid wasteland
hasn't undone me.
El...
Psy... Congroo...
Two weeks ago
Wassssup!
Hm? What the--? So...
you've joined the yakuza
or you're going on safari...
Am I in the ballpark?
These threads aren't
safari... They're L.A.
Short for... "lab appropriate?"
You're so forgetful, Okarin!
They're holding a big
Rai-Net tournament in America,
and Faris got an
invitation to compete in it,
so she's taking us all
with her for moral support,
don't you remember?
Ha...! You mean the
Great Federated States need
the presence of one Hououin
Kyouma to put things to rights!
Do you know how
delusional you are?
Hey, Kurisu just texted me!
Let's see what she says...
Looks like she's all
caught up with her work,
so she'll be able to
visit us out there!
And she made sure to
mention Okarin coming, too...!
Lookit!
What do we got...?
"Don't bother bringing
Okabe unless you have to...
My scientific credibility
can't afford it."
Man, if that ain't a textbook
slam-fest, I'll eat my hat.
Pish-posh...!
She wants us to sow the seeds
of the lab's trans-Pacific plot
under the guise of
a simple vacation!
Then I'm gonna pack
my big oopa pillow!
America, huh?
I hope it's a one-way trip.
Bring me back a gift, okay?!
Course I will, silly...!
How about you, Moeka,
do you want anyth--?
Macadamia nuts X 6
...Anything but.
Moeka
Or, uh...
Some chocolate...
Uh...
Here they come...
Reason for visit?
Well...
if you're going to be blunt,
let me refer to my manifesto.
"Aha...!
Look upon this
visage of chaos...!
I am a mad scientist...!
your precious Founding Fathers
cannot save you now!"
So, you're a mad scientist, huh?
No...! Wait!
I'd retract my previous
declaration regarding
any intended pandemonium
within your fine country!
In retrospect,
I should have explained
that it's an entirely
figurative manifesto...!
There he goes...
How dare they...?
Trying to block the entry
of a scientific luminary
such as Hououin Kyo--
Still like to rant, huh?
Typical.
Okarin...?
Aren't you gonna say hi?
Huh...?
Of course, it's you...!
How embarrassing not
to recognize my assistant.
I am not your assistant!
At first...
I thought perhaps you were
an Organization assassin
sent to neutralize yours truly.
What an idiot...!
He's worse than Leeroy Jenkins.
Still trolling the web, huh?
Shut it, Daru!
Just get in the damn car
before I change my mind...!
Uh...
hold on...
Don't tell me that
you intend to drive.
Got a problem with that?
Oh, Rukako?
Yes, Kyouma?
Please fetch me a taxi.
Hey! Son of a...
I watched you get out of
the stupid cab, you big faker.
What?
Cab fare please.
Um... excuse me??
You freeloading--!
Kyouma!
Look! It's Faris!
Meow come you cancelled
the hotel reservation
I made for you?
Oh, you'd rather our
enemies be privy
to our precise coordinates?
Oh no!
You mean the Seven Lords of
the North American Continent?!
Yes...
The Seven Philosophers!
It's time for the final
apocalyptic battle?!
Almost...!
But we must be careful not to
make the first move, my pet.
Don't you worry!
I'll send 'em all packing with
the Perspicacious Death-Paw!
You mean...
you've finally mastered the
most lethal of attack moves?!
Then cry havoc...!
And let slip the
Perspicacious Death-Paw-equipped
cat-girls of war!
Until flesh and bone
fail me, and my spirit
returns to the mead-stained
timbers of Valhalla!
The U.S. shall
taste of Ragnarok!
Pretty fancy domicile
for a mere assistant, no?
You're outta here as soon as
you have somewhere else to stay.
Step away from the tub!
Hands off the soda!
Aw, you too?!
Hello out there!
This is Julie Woodhouse
with the weather!
Why does this seem so familiar?
Cause this is exactly what
we'd be doing if we were home!
Creatures of habit, all o' you.
So... how's life been
treating you over here?
Fine, I guess...
Same as it did before.
Not writing any papers
on time travel, I assume?
Nah...
I thought I'd just
leave the raving about
alternate world-lines to you.
Fair enough.
But people have been known to
harbor the rare stray memory
from those other
world-lines, you know.
Look, I know what
you're getting at, okay...?
You wanna know
what I remember?
I remember you saving me
at the Radio Building,
and me finding you afterward
so I could thank you properly...
And that's all.
So you don't recall
anything more substantial?
Huh...?!
No...
Substantial like how?
Never mind.
Hello?
Really? Where is it?
No... Oh god no...
Are you trying to get
us killed, woman?!
See ya.
Oh no you don't!
You're really going to ditch
us at this house of ill-repute?!
Pretty much...
That's what you get for skipping
out on the room Faris set up.
What were you thinking...?!
Do you know how many
horror movies I've seen
that were set in one
of these deathtraps...?!
Some hillbilly psycho will
spot me through the blinds,
chainsaw through the door,
and jury-rig my face
into a belt-buckle!
How tiny of a role does
reality play in your life?!
Now you ask him that?
Kurisu...
I know motels can't be
as horrible as they are
in the movies but...
I'm still sort of...
nervous...
You'll be fine...
Now, I guess we had
better figure out
who's bunking with who, yeah?
Well, I've shared a room
with Okarin a whole
bunch of times before...!
We used to have
these great sleepovers
when we were young--just
the two of us!
Just you two?
Oh, get your mind
out of the gutter.
She just said, "when we
were young," didn't she?
What sort of
sad little virgin--?
You be quiet...!
The point is...
Mayuri's not sharing
a room with the guys!
Maybe you can bunk
in with Rukako--
He's kind of a guy, I guess.
Okay.
Or you know what,
maybe I'll just stick
around here for the night...
Then Okabe, rooms with Daru...
Mayuri's with me...
Huh...?!
So I'm all by myself...?!
I don't wanna...!
Okay, Mayuri and
I still share a room...
Daru is alone...
And you'll be...
I won't be scared at all...
with Kyouma nearby.
Yep...
Still a dude.
How did Makise end up as the
one with a bed to herself?
Because...
Rukako and Mayuri
sharing a room is fine.
Yeah it is...
Yuri-licious...
Dream on, Daru...
Plus, if their room were a
garden of Sapphic glee,
wouldn't this one be ya--?
What now?!
Hey, Okarin...?
Yes. What?
Wanna do rock-paper-scissors
to see who's gonna
sleep in the car?
What's the matter?
I surrendered the bed to Daru...
Mere courtesy, I assure you.
We need him running on
all cylinders tomorrow.
Lost at rock-paper-
scissors, huh?
Yeah, well, what are
you doing out here then?
I dunno.
Hey.
Huh?
Don't go just yet.
I want to ask you something.
What madness is this?!
It comes in diet?!
Take a couple back with you.
At the current exchange rate,
they're cheaper to
import anyway.
So, what's this
burning question...?
Of course!
You want me to
look over your work!
Genius that I am, it's--
You know what?
Just forget it.
It's not the first time
you've told me that, actually.
It's not?
Oh, that's right--it was
on another world-line.
You wouldn't know.
That's what I'm
talking about...!
I can think of a hundred
reasons why this
"alternate world-line"
craziness could never be true...
but then, I dream things...
things that feel more like,
I dunno, memories...
Moments like...
you're crying on an overpass
in Akihabara, and I'm there...
...or we're debating
equations written out
on a whiteboard, neither
of us backing down...
...or we're sitting
together on a stairwell...
and I'm patching up a
hole in your lab coat...
It seems you remember more than
your consciousness admits to.
So, they're all real?
When you get right down to it,
their authenticity is a question
of perspective and semantics.
Having never truly taken
place on this world-line,
"dream" is as appropriate
a term for them as any.
But they...
they actually happened on some
of the other world lines...
Yeah.
I see.
Um...
Can I...
ask another question...?
What is it?
There's this...
one particular... dream...
I keep having... But...
in this one... we're...
Yes...? We're what?
We're, uh...
If I could help you remember
it somehow, I would.
Yeah, I'll bet!
I'm so glad Okarin and Kurisu
are getting to spend
this time together...
Say your prayers,
Rai-Netters!
And that's the match!
Way to kick ass, Faris!
You guys got pwned!
I did it!
Faris! Faris! Faris!
This chick's Rai-Net
cosplay is awesome!
Aren't you glad
I brought it Ruka?!
Here's... your omelet, master.
Hold on...
You just served me
without meowing.
Why do I have to
be a cat-girl maid?!
Because!
Part of your duty as goodwill
ambassador to the States
is extolling
Japan's maid culture!
I don't remember volunteering
for goodwill ambassador,
because I didn't!
We agreed to work the tournament
if they'd pony up the funds
for our plane tickets...
Ergo, your ears and apron.
So why am I stuck
wearing them, huh?
No one flew me anywhere.
It's for the greater
good of the lab.
Then you put on the damn apron!
You know, it's good to
see you so full of moxie.
I mean, last night you
seemed so pensive...
about the alternate world-lines.
Pensive...?
No, I was just a little
tired--that's all...
I mean, it's not
like I... care.
You're better off that way.
Believe me, those paths
are better left untrod.
None of it was real...
Not in the life I know.
You're right.
Thanks for waiting!
I didn't know they
were gonna run late...!
Suzuha...?
Suzuha!
How is she even here...?
This contradicts her farewell...
Before she left she said...
See you in seven years.
This world-line is
devoid of time-travel,
so there can't be a Suzuha until
her birth seven years from now.
But there she is...
Suzuha, in the flesh...
Maybe I was wrong
about this world-line...
Maybe it does have
time-travel... and worse...
Huh...?
What do you mean he's gone?
Now that you mention it...
I did see somebody in a lab
coat walk out of the event
hall a little while ago...
Hey, you guys!
So I asked around...!
Turns out Kyouma jumped
into a taxi and sped off!
No way!
Maybe the Organization's
after him...!
Dude's finally
lost his marbles...
Kurisu...!
Never thought I'd
have a doppelganger.
Trippy.
The resemblance is... uncanny.
I'm not even from L.A.
I was in town for
the tournament,
and now my friend and
I are heading to Vegas.
Any other day, you
wouldn't've seen me.
What're the odds.
Y'know, this lookalike of
mine must mean a lot to you...
You followed me
into the boonies...
It's sweet...
And more than a
little expensive.
If you knew her...
I think you would understand.
So, does that mean you don't
know where she is these days?
She's incommunicado.
But later...
seven years from now...
we'll meet again.
There, ya see...?
It'll all work
out in the end.
Funny that you
mention seven years...
A psychic told me
I'd get married
and have a kid around then.
Yeah... S'dumb.
No... That sounds right.
Huh...?
Sorry for cutting into
your travel time like this.
I'm glad you did.
Later!
Later.
"See you in seven..."
Daru, my friend...
you're gonna do just fine.
Wait...! Sixty-seven cents to
my name... and no charge.
How the devil do
I get back?! What?!
I started walking...
No other choice, really.
Kurisu...
Dammit to hell...!
I refuse to die in this
worthless, sun-bleached tundra!
Do your worst,
you sandy bastard!
You shall not claim the
life of Hououin Kyoumaaaaa!
I should've told her...
when I...
had the chance...I'm a fool...
I'll second that.
Just a mirage...
Wrong, but I'm flattered.
What your heat-addled brain
is perceiving right now
is an actual female.
I was worried about you.
Not worried enough to
fill up the gas tank
before you sallied forth...!
Excuse me for rushing out here!
My mistake!
What about your phone?
So inept.
You're a fine one to
talk, Mr. "Dead Phone
an' a Handful of Change!"
You'd be vulture chow right now
if I hadn't come and
scraped your sorry butt
off of this highway!
Cut me some slack.
I caught a glimpse
of what looked like
an old friend of mine
getting into a car,
so I grabbed a cab and
followed her, alright?
So that's what happened?
Uh-huh.
I see...
I thought maybe you had run off
because of what I said in
the diner this afternoon.
Hardly. Wait...
What did you say?
Huh?! Uh... you know...
About it not being real...
That. Right.
Yes, that!
What else could I possibly
be talking about...?!
I have to get to the bottom
of these dreams I'm having.
Why's that?
Because I...!
I just...Remember how...
I mentioned another dream...?
One I... didn't really
talk about...?
Why does it feel more real
than things that've
happened when I'm awake?
It was.
What...?!
Because it was real...
For both of us.
Wait, what are you saying?!
I'm saying that on an
alternate world-line,
I told you I was
in love with you.
I mean... I am in love
with you, Kurisu.
How do you feel?
That's not fair.
We might have gone through
a ton of stuff together
in those alternate world-lines
you've seen, Okabe...
But I'm in this one.
And whatever
happened between us
during that time feels
like a dream to me.
I don't know...
what you mean to me yet.
I have an ability
called Reading Steiner...
It's how I remember
things across world-lines...
It's how I remember you.
Fate gave us three weeks...
and I relived them...
time and again...
a rat skittering through a
maze of his own fashioning...
but my one constant...
the one truth that never
failed me... was you.
So I'll say it again...
I love you...
That's just something
you should know.
But what am I to you...?
Not in dreams,
not in dim memories...
What does your
heart say right now?
Okabe...
If... you really wanna know...
Just close... your eyes.
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
is a basic matter of little glamor to you
Imprisoned in the past we lament the future
and not even miscalculating a single speck of dust would be permissible
Our dreams stretching out as infinity and the future we imagine
are a vain privilege we allowed ourselves
Finity is what the two hands of the clock point out
forcing us to make cruel decisions in life
Hacking to the Gate
Now I cross world lines with every passing second
and wish to protect your smile
Now I am again sucked into a time loop as a solitary observer
where sadness holds no sway