"Outcome of trial:
Human is dead. Mismatch."
Human is dead?
Uh-huh.
Someone...
...died?
Apparently so.
What else is there?
According to this,
there's more in "Jellyman's
Report, number 143."
And that is...?
Your guess is as
good as mine, dude.
There's a weird lookin'
database here, though...
Okay... What is this?
Some... kinda proprietary code?
Daru?
Eff this!
I officially have no idea
what I'm looking at...! Die!!!
Maybe this would be a
good time to take a break...?
Hhhh... Who did I think I was?
Unreadable code is unreadable.
You've fought nobly, sir.
Take a breather.
Take a freakin' nap, more like.
I got some more
noodles, if you want.
Thanks, May.
I'll take it lyin' down.
Proprietary code...
He was say something
like the IBN 5100
was built before
PCs were using BASIC,
so it can read IBN's proprietary
programming language--
The IBN 5100's
singular abilities
are needed to halt
SERN's ambitions...
I would very much like to
speak with you at some point.
John Titor
This is my email address.
If you contact me, I will reply.
Enter Subject
There's something I want to ask you
To: John Titor
Subject: There's something I want to ask you
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Interpreter
Rendezvous
How much clothing do you have?
I threw a couple of Daru's
things in the mix, too...
Sorry; we've been pulling
a lot of late-nighters...
You should be able to tell
his unmentionables from mine
by the disparity in size.
Oh my!
Okabe!
Wassabi!
That is not my
name... Firstly...
Secondly, a hearty "hale and
well met" will suffice...
Thirdly... From what pit
do you mine your slang?
Wassabi, Suzuha!
Cut it out...!
Wait a sec, since when
do you two know each other?
We spend too much time
in the same building not
to have met eventually.
And just lookie at
the sweet Rai-net card
she gave me when
we did: Good as gold!
Where you off to?
Oh, laundry...
Okarin and Daru
have been working late,
so they're getting kinda stinky.
Part-timer!
'Less you wanna be a
short-timer, get crackin'.
Right...
And you stay
clear of her, Romeo.
Interesting appellation
to lay on me,
when clearly the
love-struck one here is you.
Shut it, freak...
One day you're gonna
mouth off like that
in front of my daughter...
At which point
I'm gonna end you.
Nae? Your rodent?
Hey, don't talk
about her like that!
If anyone's the rodent it's the
guy drooling over the damn kid!
I'm right here,
and I am not a kid!
I am a skilled warrior.
A what?
You tell him, part-time girl...
Keep that sharp tongue of
yours whetted on his blunt head
and I'm certain you'll
rise through the ranks
of your battalion in no time.
Oh, shut up...! You contaminate
people with your craziness!
Hey! I can take care of
myself, 'kay, thank you.
You'd think I had
a sign on my back
that said
"insert crazy here..."
Hhhhh... See ya.
Yeah, we...
It's a little tic of hers,
you might say...
I've dubbed it
"Shaking Hands with Stardust"
Bet if I did this long
enough, I'd reach a star.
Best wait till you
can see some, though.
Hey, now...
Just 'cause I can't see them
sometimes doesn't mean
they're not always there.
EM waves, definitely...
Which, of course, would
be the simplest explanation
for the cell phone's
odd behavior...
Except... That banana was...
This humble kitchen
appliance... is a time machine!
Hmph! Whatever.
Oh, dear... I hate leaving Faris
here in the dark all alone.
Look away.
'Kay.
The man's a universe
unto himself:
ever expanding and
plagued by entropy.
Of course it'd be
Shining Finger...
Come on, Titor.
Respond to my damn text...
I don't like being
held in suspense.
Received Mail
Tell me how to reach the Super Haker!
Okay, okay. I get it.
Lay off... Ugh.
You have a new message
John Titor
Are you for real?
Thank you for contacting me.
Regarding the screen cap
you sent of that code:
it is indeed a proprietary
programming language
developed by IBN.
You'll need an IBN
5100 to un-encrypt it.
Good luck finding one, though.
Hop to, people! The lab
is now at Def Con One!
Super top secret emergency
protocol's in full effect!
Okarin. You're kind
of scaring me...
Wake up, pork pie!
Our battle with the
Organization is about
to reach a frenzied pitch!
We have the means to smoke
them out of the shadows!
D'you just say
something about pie...?
Focus on SERN, damn you!
Puppet masters of an
inconceivably vast
worldwide conspiracy?!
Dark overlords obsessed
with twisting science
to their own vile and
nefarious purposes?!
The world needs only one
despicable mad scientist...!
We have to realize our
goal of global dominion
before the upstarts
cut us off at the pass!
'Kay, I'm just
gonna say it: I'm lost.
Here's the plan... we track down
and snatch up an IBN 5100...
That done, we crack SERN's code
like eggs over a
cast iron skillet!
Into the breech, friends!
Uh... I hate to tell you...
But I gotta work today.
I stand alone.
Received Mail
Time:
Sender:The Lightning
Shiatsu-ist
Subject:Sorry if I'm bothering you.
Are you mad? Sorry if I'm bothering you. I
really need the IBN 5100 information, and
right now, you're the only one I can ask...
You might be of
use to me after all.
Well, lookie here.
Excuse me.
What now?!
You're coming with me.
Hey, hold it!
Received Mail
Time:
Sender: The Lightning
Shiatsu-ist
Subject:
Let's both do
our best!
I don't have any real information.
How about you?
Moeka
This was a nice jacket
when I woke up today.
How can you not have dug
up a single lead yet...?
Bacon-fed moron...
There a reason
you're scowling at me?
This look's not meant
for you... Rest assured.
Yeah, well...
Then knock it off.
Sulking, are we...?
To her credit,
Mayuri felt you might be
inclined to irritability...
Don't you think
you're a bit too old
to rely on such
childish tactics?
Why hello, Kettle.
My name is Pot.
Anyway, what'd you
want to talk about?
It's very simple, Christina.
I want to you dispense
with the attitude
and come back to the
lab on assignment.
You consider that the
attitude might have something
to do with that name?
Kindly let me finish, Zombie.
When do you ever?!
How did I end up in league
with a head-case like you...?
From this point forward,
my curiosity can suck
it up or go to Hell.
What...? Seriously?!
What's wrong now?
Is it bad news?
You've no idea. Wait...
Suppose this text
obsessed girl's in bed
with the Organization?
What Organization?
The only one that matters!
A big, transnational
conglomerate secretly pulling
our strings from the shadows!
Oh, wonderful. You're one
of those... A conspiracy nut.
What's wrong?
Uh... Nothing.
What do you want from me?
I said it was nothing!
Pursue it and you loose a tooth!
Lashing out... No matter...
Come with me to
recover my laundry
and I'll give you your mission.
Uh...
I'm not some slave girl on
a chain... Wait, laundry?
Hmmm. Interesting setup.
Your hotel doesn't have one?
No, it's too ritzy
for that kind of thing.
'Sides, I'm not really
all that comfortable
with leaving my
clothes in public.
Well, observe how
the other half lives
and be grateful I ushered you
across that--Still no change?
Why would there be?
It's a washing machine,
not a particle accelerator.
Oft times the most enigmatic
features of the universe
couch themselves
in the commonplace.
Who, for example,
could've predicted
a cell phone transforming a
microwave into a time machine?
It's not a time machine!
Huh?
Listen... Time
machines are fiction...
You've seen what you
wanted to see, that's all.
Keep on with this idea
that you've somehow
discovered one and I'm walking.
Why do you insist on denying
the evidence of your own senses?
I'm not.
Hah! But of course...!
Some sort of trauma...
I see it... Clearly...
You were struck by a bolt of
noonday lightning on the plains
of Arkansas at age five,
left to fend for--
Shut up.
Then what?
Theoretical limitations,
that's what! It's impossible.
Theories are no more
than lexical chicanery...
The love poetry of imbeciles...
Accept what you've
seen. Come on.
No.
You know, this
stubbornness will end--
I said no... so lay off...!
I'm not going to get lost down
the same blind alley as dad!
I'm sorry.
That was uncalled for.
No, no!
I'm quite satisfied
with the outburst
I wheedled out of you just now.
Well played, me!
Anyway, the point is,
your microwave is not,
nor will it ever be,
a time machine.
Yeah, yeah...
Listen, while you're here,
I'm sorry I made
you join the lab...
You, don't have to stay...
But I want you to know
I'm not one to hold a grudge...
Your lab designation
will remain open
in the event that you
ever change your mind...
the 004 slot will forever
and always belong to you.
Oh, quit trying to act all cool!
Hey! Damn it, that was
like the perfect sign-off!
It might have been, yeah; if
your laundry wasn't still here.
If anyone's leaving,
it should be me. Goodbye.
Ugh, what?!
I believe in street argot, the
phrase is "payback's a bitch."
Now you can go.
See you around. Never.
Hold it.
Hey! Watch the jacket!!!
I meant to pick your
brain about the IBN 5100.
And that would be...?
An old PC.
What for?
There's that curiosity again...
You really want to know?
No...! Maybe an overview...
Hmph.
Very well... The IBN is
connected to SERN's secret plot.
We need the machine's
unique functionality
to decode the proprietary
programming language SERN uses
to mask all interdepartmental
exchanges vis-à-vis
its covert time
travel experiments.
Are you appropriately shocked?
Right... That's what I get.
Oh, I see... Sarcasm, huh?
Well Patter off to that veil of
ignorance you call a life, then!
Mark my words, Christina:
you will rue the day you
saw fit to underestimate me!
Where are you getting
that name from? Gah...
We need the machine's
unique functionality
We need the IBN 5100's special functionality.
to decode the
proprietary programming...
That's what I get for
fraternizing with know-it-alls.
A PC?
Yeah. A really old one...
and it only costs
fifty-one hundred yen...
Least I think so.
Uh. Hold on...
You don't mean...?
Too-too-roo! Guess what, Okarin?
I found something
out that's going to put
a big fat smile on your face.
No Cell Phones
No cell phones, big-shot.
Faris said she's totally seen
the computer you're looking for!
No Cell Phones
Isn't that awesome!
I said--
Hey!
Damn kid.
This doesn't cover your bill!
Faris, Meow-meow!
Faris, Meow-meow! Faris,
Meow-meow! Faris, Meow-meow!
Okay... The Hell...?
Hiya! Welcome Meow-sters!
The competition for the
Faris Cup is about to begin,
so I hope you've
brought your game-face!
Who here thinks they
have what it takes
to get their name
on a specialty omelet?
AHHHHHH! Faris, meow-meow!
Faris, meow-meow!
Wh-What dimension
did I fall into?
Hey! Too-too-roo!
Mayuri...
Perhaps you can explain
what I'm witnessing here...
Has there been a
gravity distortion...?
Silly... It's the Faris Cup.
Huh?
That's when Faris
plays Rai-Net Battler
with anyone who
wants to step up.
Kyouma!
Have you come to challenge me?
You're kinda late,
but it's not unusual for
me to take ten at a time,
so I can squeeze
you in... Just go--
Thank you, no!
I've come here to lay
my hands on the IBN...
You will tell me where it is!
That so?... I'll be glad to
tell you if you agree to play.
Uh! Stop spouting
off nonsense...!
I'll have you know that nothing
less than the fate of the world
hangs in the balance here...!
I've no time for games--
The Faris Cup is for
people who want to compete;
everyone else must wait outside.
Is it now acceptable for a maid
to banish her young master...?
I need that PC!
Can't hear you.
Be warned, my dear: time
demands I not go easy on you.
Sounds like someone's
feeling confident.
C'mon. Think it through...
You do know that Faris
ranks nationally, right...?
Daru... Behold... as I take
your lady-friend here to school.
My strategy is
absolutely failsafe.
I'll bet it is.
Special codename...
K. B. O. O. M.!
Otherwise known
as KAH-BOOM!
Certainly sounds awesome...
You intrigue me.
Feign impassivity
while you can...
The moment my strategy
detonates, your national ranking
will be summarily reduced
to brick-dust and tears.
You're passionate...
That's good.
Remember our deal...
By engaging in battle,
I secure the right to
be told everything
you know about
the IBN... Agreed?
Kitties never lie.
Bring it!
Prepare to face an opponent
who will change
your view of the game!
I surrender!
Well that was a lot of build
up for a lot of nothing...
That was your big,
balls-out strategy?
Huh... If I didn't know better,
I'd say you intended
to be a suicide bomber...
Kaboom... K B... O...
O. M... Ooooooh...
Note: Self-destruct = Jibaku
Lamest. Anagram.
Ever. ...Oh crap...!
Now...! The intel I require
if you would please, Faris...
What?
He recovers quickly.
You're sure
demanding for a loser.
Lest we forget, I didn't agree
to win, I agreed to participate.
See... The most formidable foe
is one who cares not
a whit for the game.
Is that fair?
Well... I'd have to
look it up... but...
All's fair in love and war!
I was brilliant!
Brilliant? Dunno about that...
Cheesy, definitely.
Silence...! Where've
you got the IBN 5100?!
I don't.
Of course you do!
Dad had one around the
house when I was little,
but that was years ago...
It's long gone now.
Eh? Blast...! Your special move!
You actually used
it against me...
It's the Side-Saddling...
Question Dodge!
How did you know...?!
Well, kudos to you...
Indeed you've somehow
seen right through me...
Very well done.
Was that really all you knew?
Sorry... Last time
I laid eyes on an IBN
was at a shrine
somewhere in Akihabara.
Wait... A shrine?
"Kurisu. Good to hear from you
all the way over there in Japan.
Hope you're enjoying yourself.
Posed your question to the
professor and he said that,
yes, the IBN 5100
is indeed able to work
with special programming
languages that antedate Basic."
He was right?
Huh. A PC... I'd have
to run it by my father.
It's an IBN 5100.
He may not recognize the name,
but if he let's me have
a gander at it I'll know.
Okay. I'll ask him.
It's all on you now.
Code words, please.
Uh, El Psy Congress...?
It's Congroo!
Go ahead.
It's me.
Me who...?
I know a lot of
people by that name...
Though I have to say...
You sound like someone
I once knew in Paris.
You're like the most impossible
human being I've ever met.
Could it be my errant assistant?
When did you change
your name from Christina!
Will you give it a rest?!
There's that
ever-present attitude.
You bring it out of me!
Hmph. What do you want?
Where are you?
Why would you want to know?
No reason.
En route to Yanabayashi Shrine,
if you're so disinterested--
Oh, a hang up.
Very classy. Harassment!
What was that call all about?
I wanted to know where you were.
I don't remember
asking you to show up.
Well, That's understandable,
since you didn't.
Sorry to keep you
waiting for so long.
Ah. Did you talk to him?
Yeah... And you're not
going to believe this,
but the one we've
got lying around
just happens to be the
model you're looking for.
It is?!
Hold on, are you...? You're
talking about an IBN 5100?!
Uh-huh... Um...
Who's your new friend?
Assistant...
So, where's it stashed?
Uh... Hey! Don't just blow
me off! Introduce us...!
I think you can do a little
better than "assistant."
We're not here for
an ice cream social,
and you're lucky
I deign to call you that.
You chauvinistic son of a...
Fine. Whatever makes you happy.
This is Makise Kurisu.
My assistant.
Good... But, for the record,
I'm not his assistant...
So... what was your name?
Ruka Urushibara. Hello.
How old are you?
I'm actually turning
seventeen this year.
One year younger than me...
What...? I don't believe that...
You look so... I don't know,
put together... I'm jealous.
Oh, please...
You're way prettier.
Um... I, uh...
I'll go get dad...
That... was hilarious.
Did I say something wrong?
Wow.
I'm having a hard time believing
this day's actually come.
Uh, why is that exactly?
Well, you see...
The person who sort of
donated this thing to us
made a point of saying
that someday a young man
in dire need of
it would turn up.
Til then we were just
supposed to look after it...
I guess it had to
have been something
like ten years ago now.
Makes perfect sense...
It's Fate; the tides of destiny.
Stein's Gate has chosen!
Again with that?
Wow. It really is the
right model. That's crazy.
This is fantastic.
Is that what you're
looking for then?
Any chance we might borrow it?
I don't see why not.
I'm in your debt, good sir!
Lift with your knees.
Uh-uh.
Damn it, Christina,
earn your keep!
Stop calling me that!
Why don't I get you a cart...
I wouldn't dream of imposing...
You've done quite enough...
You should be ashamed!
How dare you
put the man out?!
Oh, please...!
Do you even listen
to yourself talk...?!
You're a loon!
Can't have too
many friends, right?
I hope my Ruka here
takes a page from you two.
Yeah.
Wait here.
It won't take a second.
Your dad's a sweet guy.
You really think so?
I'm not going to get lost down
the same blind alley as dad!
Excuse me?
Nothing.
Sorry... It, uh...
Looks like the cart's
seen better days.
Things you don't
think you'll be doing
when you wake
up in the morning...
Stop whining and
put your back into it.
Hey...
Come on.
Never mind then!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Kindly refrain from taking
your frustrations out
on my lumbar, please!
Hang on! How is it that
I'm the one who has
to schlep backwards?!
Because that's the
direction you're facing.
I can't be facing
backward, genius.
Sure you can! I believe in you!
Appreciate the encouragement,
but I really think we need to be
moving sideways... Scratch that!
I know we need to
'cause I'm about to drop this
thing on your freaking toes!
kisei sareta chikai mujihi nari juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
All those are being rewritten