I'm calling a it a day--
help me lock up, yeah?
Okay!
I never said that, you liar!
Not in actual speech, perhaps,
but your eyes were begging
me to take those breaks!
Yeah, because you looked like
you were about to up and
die every couple of feet!
Don't be naïve--I was
merely feigning weakness!
What, we weren't
conspicuous enough already?!
Okabe! Wasssup!
What's in the box?
Heh! Dying to know, are you?
I'd be sworn to
secrecy most days,
refusing to divulge its contents
even under threat of torture--
My arms are on fire! Can't you
tell her what it is later?!
Oh, buck up, buttercup.
Fine--do it now!
But would you please just
skip ahead to the good part!
How could you say that...?!
This box is a reliquary...!
Its precious cargo demands
a properly-paced denouement!
Lemme guess, it's an IBN 5100?
What...?!
How did she pluck the answer
out of thin air like that?!
So, how'd you track it down?
Fate guided my footsteps
to Yanabayashi Shrine,
where it languished amid the
dusty offerings of yesteryear--!
Wow...!
Fate's gonna crush your
footsteps if we don't hurry up!
Makise Kurisu...?!
Uh...? Uh huh...?
Who is this person?
She's Mr. Braun's new
part... time... help.
Did I... miss... something...?
C'mon, kid--let me
see some hustle!
We're closin' up here!
If looks could kill,
I'd be a goner...!
Well, you do have a
right dastardly face.
Huh?!
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Starmine
Rendezvous
Daru, your t-shirt is so big!
It's like the sail
from a pirate ship!
Or a rug...!
Made from a big polar bear!
Mayushi is frolicking
on my shirt...
She's getting her
adorable all over it!
Steady now! Easy does it...!
Thanks, Captain Obvious!
It's Kurisu!
Oh hey, Mayuri... Sorry
to just barge in like this.
You can come here
whenever you like...!
After all, you
are a member now!
What happened to
never coming back, hmm?
Frailty, thy name is Assistant.
I'm here 'cause you're too
weak to carry the thing...!
I certainly didn't
come of my own volition!
Ah, you... you don't like it
here at the Future Gadget Lab?
Wait, what?
No, I... I didn't say that.
It... it's complicated...!
So, what's in the mystery box?
You dying to know...?
I'd be sworn to secre--
An IBN 5100.
Huh...?! Come to papa...!
Dude, Okarin, way to go!
Seriously, this is why
we love you and follow you.
I don't follow him.
Uh... Anyway, let's see
if it still even boots up!
Good thing I was talking
about it at the maid café, huh!
Indeed. Couldn't have
done it without you, Mayuri.
It works!
How long will it take you to
crack that proprietary code?
Don't hold your
breath or anything...
I mean, this computer
is older than I am...
Older than the interwebs, too...
which means I can't just pop
an Ethernet cable into the back.
This stuff an' a
gum-wrapper should do it.
Huh...?
I'll get right on it...
Assistant, you heard the man.
You braying it ad nauseum
doesn't make me your assistant.
Oh, but you are!
No... I'm... not!
Okarin, you should go.
She's not gonna know where all
those nutty little shops are.
Hhh... If I must.
Let's be off, Mayuri!
Nah--I think I'm
gonna stay behind
and give our new lab member
the grand tour of the place...
If you know where everything is,
maybe you'll end
up liking it more
and you won't wanna go away!
O foul enchantress!
Working your hoodoo
on that innocent girl!
Working my what?!
Hush. Don't fight it, Makise...
Give in to the
Sapphic goodness...!
Keep on dreaming, pervert!
Hey Makise, what does
"Sapphic goodness" mean?
Uh... how about
that tour...? Y'ready?
All right! Let's show her
what's behind door number one!
Hold on. Is that
a shower back there?
Uh-huh...!
But sometimes the
water gets really cold
if you stay in there for a
bit too long, and that's no fun!
You mean...
you've actually used this
shower to bathe yourself...?
Yeah, every once in a while!
You have to promise me you'll
never shower here again, Mayuri!
She's perfectly safe!
I should buy you
some pepper-spray...!
Why do you hang out with
these weirdos, anyhow?
Is it blackmail, or coercion,
or brainwashing or what?!
Nothing like that.
It's just I'm Okarin's hostage!
That's it--I'm calling the cops.
Wait!
She just said
she's your hostage...
You two are going down.
No, silly.
I wanted to be...
And so far it's super fun.
You'll see!
Huh? What...
is she talking about?
Hmph... Well, I'm off.
See ya later!
It's not the exact thing he
wanted, but I'm sure it'll do...
Waaaaassssup!
How's the ol' 5100 coming along?
Shh! Don't speak of it--not
even by its number!
Came to get some parts, huh?
Need any help?
I'd have never guessed
the part-time TV girl
knows so much about PCs.
Yeah, but when it comes to IBNs,
there's one guy who
has all of us beat.
Are you serious?! Put me in
touch with him, immediately!
I can't.
Do you wish for us to be
at loggerheads over this?
Look, it's not
up for discussion.
You're treading a
very dangerous path!
He's dead... Okay...?
That's why I can't.
He's been dead for years now.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who should
apologize... For before.
Did my assistant
offend you in some way?
Just met her.
Did she glare at you, perchance?
Or scoff! She packs
a wicked scoff!
Neither one...
She hasn't done anything.
What, then?
She hasn't done anything yet...
But I promise you, she will.
Just be careful...
She's bad for your health.
What do you mean?!
Air raid--get down!
Huh...?
It's just a news chopper...
For the fireworks
display later on.
What a relief.
Fireworks, huh...?
Hey, wait I've heard of those!
"Heard of"...? Meaning
you've never witnessed them?
I wanna see 'em! Where do I go?!
Follow yonder road
down to the river
and you should get
a fair enough view.
Awesome!
I'll message ya...!
Just gimme me your e-mail!
A festival?
Yup! Fireworks and everything!
It's been so long...
Wanna go watch 'em?
Oh, uh... well... I guess...
Look...! There's Okarin!
Too-too-roo!
Homeward bound?
Mm-hm!
How did the parts hunt go?
Total success, of course...
Ah... So... you
guys're really gonna
keep working this
time machine angle, huh?
Don't tell me you care now?
You do, don't you?
No...! Well, maybe a
just a tiny little bit...
But I still think your kooky
SERN conspiracy theories
are nothing but
a bunch of hot air.
The truth. That's all
I'm interested in... okay?
Sorry, Mayuri.
Sorry?
I think I'm gonna
skip the fireworks
and go back to the lab.
That's okay. I should prob'ly
be heading back home, anyhow.
Cool.
But Makise...?
Are you gonna keep coming back?
Yeah... After all,
I'm a member until I fly
back to America, right?
Yay!
Night-night!
Why would she even
bother to ask...?
After all...
you are my assistant--
of course you're
coming back to the lab.
She told me the two of
you were childhood pals...
But I still don't get how
one of you turned out
so socially inept while
the other one's normal.
Yes, well, poor Mayuri always
has been a little bit different.
I didn't mean her, genius!
Part-Time Warrior
First
Message
More than I imagined!
Fireworks are great!
"Here's my first e-mail!"
"Better than I imagined!"
"Fireworks are amazing!"
So that was the last
time it worked, huh?
Ooh! Mind if I use this?
I love a good lab coat...
Calms me down.
Look at you!
The sight of you enveloped
in that lab coat...!
To the very
marrow it thrills me!
Uhhh... What the hell
are you going on about?!
Need you ask me...?!
That coat is a
pledge--a symbol!--
that you are a
friend to Science!
Stop!
I keep telling Daru and
Mayuri to wear one,
but they don't get it!
But not you, you understand...!
Ergo, I want you to jam your
hands into your coat pockets!
Huh...?!
Now, woman!
Okay! Like this?
Perfect! Our stance
is that of the lucky few
who know the privilege
and burden of having dedicated
their life to research!
It's kinda sexy...
...every time you wear it,
marvel anew at my generosity!
All I'm going to marvel
at is your stupidity...!
What are you hiding in there?
Shut up! I haven't
eaten since lunch,
and that was a long time ago.
Oh, very well...
I'm feeling generous, so dinner
will be on me this once.
The fruit of your labor.
Are you serious?!
You object?
You're damn right I do...!
Tell me there's
something else!
We do have a stockpile
of instant ramen...
But no one raised on
the windswept moors
of America would ever deign--
In a cup?
Mm-hmm.
I suppose that'll do.
So, what flavors do you have?
Salt an' soy sauce!
I'll have the salt... Though,
I had better use a fork.
No point stalling.
Time runs out, you lose anyway.
Wanna throw in the towel?
'Cause that one at the
end is clearly a virus card.
Just saying.
Hah! Whatever you think is
gonna get you through the night.
Oh good, thank you for making
my decision so much easier.
Last turn... And... go.
Oho...
I see you're drinking that soda
with extraordinary aplomb.
Uh... Seven years in the
States--whaddya expect?
We could go grab something
harder, if you're game.
Nah, none for me, thanks. I'm
still underage, so you know...
I was talking about
the caffeinated version
of what you're holding.
That's harder to you?
What purpose have I for alcohol?
That soda you hold is the one
and only drink of
the intelligentsia!
Uh huh your love of carbonation
is a beautiful thing--
now stop peeking at my cards.
And, that's the game, my friend.
No offense, but you're not
the sharpest tool in the shed
when it comes to looking
at the bigger picture.
You're so caught up in your
whole "damn the torpedoes" deal
that you never think about
what the other guy's doing.
You got played, Okabe.
Sorry.
Hold on!
What'd I say...?!
You know perfectly well!
What, that you kind of
suck at the big picture?
Don't be a jerk--it's the truth.
No! Just after that...!
When you referred
to me as Okabe!
So...? What's the
matter with that...?
Just because you
call me Assistant,
it doesn't mean I'm going to
call you Boss-man or anything--
Listen!
For the last time, Christina...!
My name is Hououin--
I'd thank you to remember it!
Henceforth... you
will call me Hououin!
Or if that's too hard...
Kyouma is also, acceptable.
Hm? Are you crying down there?
What's there to cry about...?!
Just 'cause some maniac
jumped out of his chair
and started screaming at
me about his damn fake name
and scared me half to death? No
that's totally fine, no problem!
Daru... The woman is
weeping. Why is this?
Think about what she told you
in that big breathless rant.
Let's see...
This part should plug
into--nope. Nope... My bad...
So, if this is right,
then these cables
should shimmy on down...
through... here... Yeah...
Assistant...
No... but go ahead.
Maybe you should
call it a night...
Your hotel is nearby, right?
Don't worry... If it doesn't
work by morning, I'm outta here.
Shouldn't you at
least call your family?
Haven't seen Dad in seven years,
and Mom's in the States...
Trust me, no one's
waiting up for a call.
A genius orphan, swaddled
in your threadbare lab coat.
I am not "swaddled," weirdo.
It's alive...
It's aliiiiiiiiive!
You got it to work?!
Hashida Daru for another win!
Does any of it look helpful?
I haven't mucked around yet...
But hey, this thing
says "Z-Program"...
So that file was
created back in 1973?
Looks like.
SERN--when was it founded?
In the fifties--
fifty-four I think.
And this machine first
came on the market in...?!
Ooh, me! Nineteen seventy-five!
Did SERN actually smuggle
a whole programming
language into the 5100s
just to further their
covert time-travel plan?!
That seems like
a bit of a stretch.
But it is possible, right?!
How about we
just read the report
and then we'll
know what's up...?
I can't wait for it to be
something totally innocuous
and then you're forced to drop
this stupid conspiracy crap.
Ugh. This font is killing
my eyes...! Somebody tag in!
Just be glad it's not French...
Okay, it reads,
"The Control of Space-Time and
its Destruction of History..."
Oh, yeah... Everything sounds
better when you read it!
Better watch yourself...!
Keep whispering in
his ear like that,
you might join the
2D ladies in Daru's harem.
Yeah... I think not.
Okay, I'm skipping ahead.
"Creating a stable world
spanning from past to future...
this will be the true
raison d'être of SERN
as we move into
the 21st century."
There, you see?!
They mean to rule us!
You're being paranoid...
Tab down further.
Down past the abstract.
2-D girls aren't as bossy.
Let's see... More fluff...
List of participants...
C'mon, tell me what
they actually did...!
Here we go! "The Z-Program
will test the feasibility
of space-time
transference through
the collision of...
high-energy... protons..."
"Of space-time...
transference..."
See?! That has to
mean time-travel!
No it doesn't!
I'm right, dammit...!
SERN's been conducting
clandestine time-travel research
for the past 40 years--
at the very least!
Just stop, okay?!
No jumping to conclusions!
"Program Phase #1:
Construction and utilization
of Large Hadron Collider.
Program Phase #2:
Practical application
and tuning of lifter."
Daru, what are these
"lifter" things about?
You remember all that
buzz about ionocrafts...?
Same principal, but with
a less science-y name...
Like this, take a look.
Is it floating?!
That's what happens when you run
a high-voltage current
through aluminum.
What exactly does
floating aluminum
have to do with time-travel?
I don't know,
but they're spending
an awful lot of time
on it, aren't they...?
It says this thing
requires a lifter
and the presence
of a black hole.
Keep on reading...!
"Program Phase #3 is some
kind of animal testing...
And Program Phase #4--
Say it!
"...Human testing."
Which brings us right up to...
"Human is dead- mismatch."
No.
We stumbled across that phrase
when we first
hacked our way in...
What did the part
after that say, again?
"More details to follow
in Jellyman's report."
Well, it's high time that
we gave it a look. I say!
You sure my opening this
folder is a good idea?
If this stuff is legit,
then we're all in it way
above our pay-grade!
Don't tell me you're
chickening out now.
He does have a point...
SERN doesn't mess around--and
if we unearth this report,
we'll all be privy to
their darkest secret.
So, what, you're
not going to read it?
Save yourself.
You've got a bright
future ahead of you...
Once we read this file...
I can't guarantee
any of our safety.
Hold on, is that... concern
I'm hearing in your voice?
Well of course it is!
You're important to...!
...our scientific endeavors!
Thanks for your concern,
but I'm not going anywhere...
I'd be up all night
thinking about this anyway.
So you're in,
come what may?
Oh yeah.
And what do you say, Daru?
Well I mean I have been
pretty bad-ass so far...
If they haven't managed
to trace my hack by now,
then we should be golden.
Very well then. We go.
To raid Jellyman's report
for precious intel!
This act will go
down in lab history
as Operation Laegjarn's Chest!
What is that,
Norse mythology?
Why do we need to
name it anything?
Just have him
open the report.
Daru! Fire off a broadside!
I'm on it.
More files?!
Hmm... Yeah...
Fourteen of 'em...
I'll just pick one at random.
"Report #10. Subject:
James McCarthy.
Birthplace: America.
Z-Program 4.
Experiment Date:
28 January 2005.
Result: Human is
Dead. Mismatch."
Not that again!
"We believe the subject
was unable to withstand
the supergravitationally-
induced compression
or survive transmission
through the Kerr black hole."
And an article...?
Oh my god--look at the date...!
April 3rd, 19... 21...!
"New York. The corpse
of a man was found
half-emerged from the wall
of a building on 14th Avenue."
"The state of the corpse
has defied all explanation,
as the soft tissue has
turned gelatinous..."
Oh my god.
They're capable
of time-travel...
Lethally flawed, but still...!
"Report #8. Subject:
Linda Hill.
Birthplace: England.
Z-Program 4."
"Experiment Date:
15 February 2004.
Result: Human is
Dead... Mismatch."
"October 2nd, 1972.
The gelatinous body
of a woman was found
on the roadside in the
Indian city of Dharmapuri."
"The woman's lower
legs were destroyed,
most likely by the
tires of a passing car."
Another...!
"Report #7.
Subject: Michael Lang.
Birthplace:
Germany. Z-Program 4.
Result: Human is
dead. Mismatch."
Good heavens--even here...
"May 24th, 1936.
Gelatinized body found at
the foot of Kyoto's Mt. Hiei."
And there are
fourteen of these...?
Wanna see another?
I've seen quite enough...
You okay, man?
I... I need some fresh air...
I've never seen him
so shaken up before.
Why'd the test subjects
go all dessert-cup?
Judging from when
I've read so far...
I think SERN is
developing tech
to allow time-travel
via Kerr black holes.
I can only imagine
what sort of trauma
that would inflict upon
a living human being,
trying to cram it through
a singularity like that.
I'm not surprised that
they've all turned into mush.
It's like trying to squeeze this
sponge into my clenched hand...
You see?...
The insides get wrung out.
So basically, it's
a really tight fit?
Yeah.
You're squeezing into something
extraordinarily narrow.
You're making time-travel
sound pretty freaky.
Huh...? What's wrong
with squeezing int--
Daru, you're such a pervert!
Says the girl talking about
squeezing things
into tight spaces.
Yeah, I meant a black hole.
There you are.
Hey... Listen...
I know it's crazy...
But just look
at it this way.
Now that we're sure it's true,
we have to figure out what
our next move is gonna be
What'd I say?
Our next move is
patently obvious.
Huh?
We have Future
Gadget numero eight,
the Phone Wave
(Real Name TBA), do we not?
We... will build a
time-machine first!
And SERN will come to nothing,
because we will
rule the world instead!
Why did I even bother to ask?
kisei sareta chikai mujihi nari juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
All those are being rewritten