Curséd be these hands...
what granted you life...!
Now honor our sulphurous
contract... writ in blood...!
Let the ebon
flames burn black...!
Fulfill my wish, O beast!
Ahhhhh!
How'm I gonna heat up
my chicken tenders now...?!
You can expect this level
of disregard for your things.
You might wanna run for it.
Don't be a butthead...!
You should say
that you're sorry--
then go out and buy
me a new microwave!
Surely not in this economy?
No photographs...!
I was very clear on that!
A keepsake.
Huh?
Shining Finger!
Check it, ladies, the
upgrade is complete...!
Phone Wave Mark II Version 1.03
is ready to rock your world...!
Thanks to the heroic
efforts of yours truly,
we can now shuttle D-mail
to any number we feel like!
Excellent work, my friend!
We should get back to
the experiments, then!
Is it really a... time machine?
You're not to breathe
a word of it to anyone.
I sure do hope Mr. Prawn
doesn't get mad at us again...
Part-time girl!
Hello down there!
Hi!
This is no time for too-too-!
Where's... Mr. Braun?!
Who's that?
Daddy's name
isn't Mr. Braun...
Oh, you're talking
'bout the big boss-man.
I think he's been
out on a house-call
for most of the afternoon.
House call?
Why you think I'm
fiddling with my bike?
Now, Mayuri.
Tutturu
Received Mail
From: Mayuri
Subject: (None)
--   Mayushii
It's real!
Hey... what was that...?
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Divergence
Singularity
I betcha some
juicy chicken tenders
would go really
well with all this...
Huh? Hold on...!
Where's the bag with my soda?!
Sorry. Sold out.
Then you beat a path from
store to store till you find it!
I wouldn't have to explain this
to an assistant worth her salt!
I'm not gonna schlep all over
town just to get you soda...!
Here.
Hand it over...
I'm a mad scientist,
not some shriveled octogenarian
mewling about his fiber intake.
Let the round
table now assemble!
Just a sec, man--I'm
gettin' the sweats.
What in the nine hells do
you think you're doing...?!
You want the
Organization to hear this?
Why not invite them in?
Yeah, whatever.
What's a Round Table?
Starting now, Operation Wyrd
goes into the second
phase of experimentation...
which will allow us...
to gauge D-mail's effect.
Barley tea's so
good in the summer...!
You want some, Moeka?
Okay, so what kind of
experiments are you thinkin' of?
We are going to change the past.
No way. We are not taking
that kind of risk...!
What if it results
in a time paradox?
Then so be it...!
Any true mad scientist
would absolutely kill
to know if D-mails can
really alter the past.
You disappoint me, Assistant.
I... I just think...
How are you gonna
prove it, Okarin?
Thank you so much for asking.
By virtue of a single event,
the occurrence of
which will brook no doubt.
Picking the winning
numbers in the lottery!
Okarin... I'm
disappointed in you.
Dude, sick! I'm totally
rollin' up to the curb
at Queen May's in the earthbound
equivalent of a Star Destroyer!
Instead of being Greedy Gus'es,
wouldn't it be a lot nicer
if we tried to make
world peace happen...?
We could give everyone
on Earth an oopa cushion!
Seriously, man...
Way to be a total jackass.
I'm trying to see if I can alter
the blasted past, woman...!
We need a quantifiable change!
And that's the first
thing you could think of?
Quiet, Little Miss Moneybags!
"Moneybags"...? What the hell?!
Well that's what
you really are...!
Lounging in some
opulent hotel room
your parents are paying for...!
"Let them eat cake!"
eh there, Antoinette!?
Don't you have a lotto to fix?
Makise's right.
We should figure that out.
Which one should we win, though?
Which one, indeed...
What's the matter?
Not sure...
Where is Double-O Five?
Dunno.
What're you doing?!
There ya go.
Can't take my eyes off of
you for a second, can I?
I texted... You never replied.
I really want to borrow
the IBN 5100. Please...
Ill take that as a yes?
Dude, smoking hot aside,
what a space-cadet.
Christina!
You are hereby tasked
with preventing her
from wandering off!
Huh...?! Hey!
I'm not your guard dog.
Poor Moeka, stuck on the couch.
Would you like me to give
you the grand tour of the lab?
It really is a
whole lot of fun...!
If you don't believe
me, just ask Kurisu!
Hmmm... now where to start...
How 'bout the Lotto 6?
It looks juicy.
They've just announced
this week's winning numbers.
So now we send them into the
past... and see what happens.
You're really going to do this?
If you've a better
idea, speak up!
The numbers're right here,
so we can do it whenever...
Looks like the current jackpot's
at... Two-hundred million!
Two... hundred million...?!
Whoa, Daru! Hold on...!
That's a little much, yeah...?
Say wha?
Well... hitting a jackpot of
that size would only serve...
to... draw unwanted
attention to ourselv--
What a total chicken.
Second prize?!
Oh, good call. Only 23 million.
What's third?!
Seven-hundred thousand.
Perfect-that-one-yes!
Good form there,
fearless leader.
This from the girl who's
quailing in her boots
at the thought--
This is an oopa cushion!
If you ever feel oogy
and you need to
some cheering up...
just-give-'em a big hug!
Next stop! The lab refrigerator!
What's inside you today...?
May I...?
Time to earn your
keep, Double-O Five.
Here's your first Future
Gadget Lab assignment.
Oh! This is exciting!
I would like you to compose
the D-mail message...
Something that will convince
the ignorant me of a week ago
to buy a ticket with the
number we've provided.
Seven days is...
168 hours. Cool if I round up?
That'll do.
Buy Lotto-6
You'll win!
Short and sweet.
Okay. Ready when you are.
Stein's Gate will finally
swing open to admit me!
Not that again.
Give the crazy the day off.
You're remarkably
close-minded for a scientist!
You looked like you
were... both having fun.
Fun?
Dealing with this nut-case?!
They're the OTP in the
fan-fic I call my life...
We are not OTP!
Oh...! So you know the jargon
of the fan-fic community...!
Huh...?! I don't know
what you're talking about!
It rolled off your
tongue so naturally...
Look. If we're gonna
do this, let's do it!
'Kay, everybody--I'm getting
ready to fire up the Phone Wave!
We are not taking
that kind of risk...!
What if it results
in a time paradox?
Come on...!
Fortune favors the bold!
El... Psy... Congroo!
Sending...
Sent
Okarin...Okarin...!
Hey, are you in there...?
Are you okay...?
I... I don't know...
How long... how long have
I just been standing here?
Um... about 30 seconds, I guess.
I actually lost
half a minute...?
You don't remember anything...?
We were talking about
what D-mail we should send
to see if it would really
alter the world line...
Then all of a sudden...
You rushed over
to the Phone Wave
and you went,
"hahhauah" all breathy-like.
Hey Mayushii--do that
breathy thing again, yeah?
Oh give it a rest, Daru!
Sorry.
Buy Lotto-6
You'll win!
It arrived...
Are you sure
you're feeling okay?
What about the money?!
From the lotto ticket...!
Did we win third prize,
Christina?! Tell me!
Stop calling me that...!
Wait... what ticket?
You really, don't know
what I'm talking about?!
I'm confused...
For the lottery...!
Our experiment
to change the past!
Sending back a D-mail!
Stop acting like such a spaz!
We haven't come up with
a message to send back yet!
What...?
Wouldn't it be nice if we tried
to make world peace happen?
We could give everyone
on Earth an oopa cushion!
They really don't...
remember it at all...
It's open!
Oh! Hey, Ruka! Come on in!
I hope that you can
forgive me, Kyouma!
What...? Why?
Here...
Oh-two... and
twelve... eighteen...
an' all the rest... Rukako!
How'd you come up
with these numbers?!
Um... well I... tried
to buy a lottery ticket
using the numbers you gave me...
Come again...?!
You said I should
play those numbers
because they were lucky
or something, so I tried...
That... was when?
Guess it's been
about a week now?
Omigosh, is your
brain psychic, Okarin?
So, are we winner-winner-
chicken-dinner or what?
That's the thing...
I got one of the numbers
all turned around in my head.
Huh...?!
Aw, you were so close, dude!
Man, that sucks!
Okabe... did you use the
Phone Wave to do this...?
Where's the bag with my soda?!
I'm not gonna schlep all over
town just to get you soda!
There's no doubt in
my mind that I sent it.
Nothing...
Like it never existed.
Perhaps... my actions
have rewritten the past.
They've no memory
of the experiment.
We discussed it and
carried it out together.
No one else remembers it.
I'm the only one.
This feels just like that day.
Come on... think...
Whatcha looking at?
Something important to me.
You okay?
You look like,
you've been brainwashed.
I, look that rough?
Hell... Maybe I was.
A bit of brainwashing
would certainly
explain whatever's
going on--What the hell?!
You haven't been chipped.
Uhhh...
Whatever it is,
nobody's brainwashed you.
Good... to know...?
Hey, how do you wash your brain?
Well...
A mad scientist like yours truly
would be happy to explain it.
Maybe we'll hold off 'til she's
a little less afraid of you.
There's something
I have to know.
Tremor, huh?
There was one a
while back, I know that.
The shop was
shaking pretty heavy.
You should have felt
another about ten minutes ago.
Nope. Dunno how
I could have missed it.
You feel it?
Nope.
Could you be any
more of a perv?!
C'mon, they stick out...!
Nature wants me to look at 'em!
See? I told ya it's easy
to hear what's going on.
So ungodly loud...!
Did you hear us going on
about the time machines, also?!
Mm-hmm! That was
super interesting.
Well, the knowledge
you're privy to is--
Relax! I'm not gonna go
around blabbing about it.
Y'know... if it's a
problem with the time machine
that's got you all
down in the dumps...
why not try hitting up
ol' John Titor for advice?
In his earlier posts...
Titor did mention
that altering the past
would change the...
the "divergence number,"
I believe he called it...
which would in
turn shift existence
onto a different world-line.
Any memories from
the previous world-line
that don't agree
with the new reality...
are basically overwritten with
the non-conflicting memories
they would have experienced.
The D-mail tossed
us from a world-line
in which Rukako didn't
buy a lottery ticket
onto one in which he did.
And the past changed
to reflect this new track.
In this world, we never
sent the winning numbers
for third prize back in time.
It isn't that they
don't remember it...
to them, it never
actually transpired.
Yet I remember everything...
But how is that possible?
Aw, balls! Nae!
Whatever you do,
don't tell your daddy I was
slacking off out here, okay?!
Only if you let me
ride your bike later!
Got yourself a deal!
Hey...! Frankenstein!
Good luck with
that stuff upstairs.
Oh... thanks...
Son of a...!
Yay, you're home!
Okabe!
What the hell were you
doing out here with my kid?!
Huh?!
My good Mr. Braun,
I've no idea what you're--!
Don't lie to me!
That's my baby
girl you're eying,
so don't think you can
run your experiments
on her up there in
that creepy lab of yours!
How dare you
insinuate I would stoop
to using a child as a lab rat!
Why don't you ask
Suzuha what we were doing.
She was out here with us!
Say what?
Is that the truth, honey?
Uh huh, she was out here--
but she definitely
wasn't slacking off!
She wasn't, huh...?!
Why you lazy good-for-nothing!
I'm making a break for it!
What the hell am
I paying you for?!
All ya do is goof off!
Look at this!
You haven't even
started on this repair!
I... I won't do it again!
Due to unforeseen circumstances,
I'm calling off today's
Phone Wave test...
Go home, you guys.
Okarin...?
Hey... Didn't you
hear me, Assistant...?
You're free to go.
Just doing a little thinking.
Oh yes... You'd rather sit there
and stare at my back than
return to the gilded cage
of your state room--right,
Little Miss Moneybags?
Quit calling me
that stupid name.
I'm composing a very
important message here...
If you insist on loitering,
do try to keep your inarticulate
brain-starved moaning
to a minimum, Zombie.
Oh goody. We're back to
my least favorite nickname.
You're like a schoolgirl,
waiting for that cute
boy to write back.
Speaking from
experience, are we...?
What's up, anyway...?
Who're you texting?
John Titor.
Huh?
Rukako
The Lottery
I'm really sorry
From: Shining Finger
Subject: I Had Fun
Next time, tell me about the time machine.
It's a promise. A promise, right?
Bye! Moeka
Daru
Daru?
What's going on?
Okarin--thank God!
Look, I just realized
I've made a terrible mistake!
What was it...?! Talk, man!
It's all... all my fault...
I left my wallet
back at the lab!
What?
Yeah! And Queen May's
shut its doors to me!
I hate to ask, but
could you maybe--?
Too-too-roo! Hi, Okarin.
Oh, hello there, Mayuri.
Daru's gonna be hitting
you up for money...
You don't have to give
him anything though, okay?
Okie-dokie...
But I called to see if you
were feeling any better.
If you're not, then I give
you permission to hug
my oopa cushion for as long
as it takes to cheer you up!
You know what,
I may just do that...
You have a good night, okay?
Don't forget to hug it, okay?
Huh. You're all smiles again.
It's him!
I received your message...
From what you describe,
I can only conclude
that you altered the past
and shifted the world line.
Your scenario does
puzzle me, though.
I don't understand how
you have retained memories
of your original past.
It is problematic.
I swear it's the truth...
This has happened
to me twice now...
What do you make of it?
I don't know.
In the version of 2036
from which I hail,
the idea of using e-mail
to alter past events
hasn't been explored.
The concept of altering the past
and shifting the world-line
is nothing new to us.
That said, it operates within
limits we've
thought were absolute.
No one has ever
been known to maintain
their memories across world
lines and observe their changes.
Even so...
Kyouma... It might be
that you have that ability.
You might be the one person...
who can guide the world
beyond 1% divergence.
"Guide the world?!"
What is he talking about?!
What is this 1% divergence
you're talking about...?!
And what lies beyond
it that's so important?!
Sending...
Sent
Beyond it lies true freedom.
Your future is condemned
to dystopia unless that
barrier can be crossed.
My goal is to save the future...
And you may be the
only one who can do it.
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
No... It doesn't make any sense.
This has got to be
some kind of mistake...
How can I... save the future...?
That's absurd...
Kyouma... I ask you...
...to be... our savior.
kisei sareta chikai mujihi naru, juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
All those are being rewritten