Alright. We've established
beyond a reasonable doubt
that our D-mails are indeed
being sent into the past, but...
We didn't exactly
improve my chances
against Faris in
the Rai-net tourney.
Now, now.
We can't work miracles...
Sure... In Ruka's case
there were issues of accuracy,
but I'm confident
the time machine
will be fully operational
with one or--
Time machine?
Mind your business!
That's exactly what
I'm trying to do,
if you hadn't noticed...
Now, would you like some
milk, sugar, or flavored syrup?
No thanks!
Awwww. Having trouble choosing?
Meow, meow!
Nuh-uh!
Gah... you get the come-hither
stare, seriously...?
I want you to die--
Oh Kyouma. Why keep secrets
from each other, my darling?
You really believe me liable
to crack under such
a paltry display?
You are im-purrr-vious, sir...
How 'bout you, Daru?
Rest assured he's
just as strong as I--
We built a machine that sends
text messages into the past.
Have you zero restraint?!
Really...? Well, now...
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
Evidently a secret is what
we tell one person at a time.
Excuse me?
Okay, that is not fair!
You can't just... Ugh!
Why do you always have
to be so predictable?!
Uh... what'd I...?
Just so you know... I was
not having an argument!
Alright, but you
certainly fooled me...
and your eyes are
still bloodshot.
Whatever. I got dirt in
them or something. Shut up.
Ugh. Could this
be any more clichéd?
It wasn't what it looked like!
Things are
complicated, okay?!
Don't even think
about going there!
I didn't breech the wall.
You're the one
who brought it up.
Well I don't want
to talk about it.
Christina--
Go away! Don't talk to me!
Look, for what it's worth...
I cherish our friendship...
I'm here to listen, so...
Seriously?
As calculated.
She took the bait... Yes...!
Wrapped around my little finger
like a mobster's pinky ring.
Ass.
Nice work out there today.
Yeah? Thanks, Faris!
You're probably on your
way to see Kyouma now, huh?
Mhmm. He wants me to pick
something up for lunch.
So, have you seen it
with your own eyes, then?
The time machine...
I'm sorry...? Oh...!
You mean the Phone Wave!
The what?
All the lightning
and cracklies... Bleh.
And the tingly bit...?
It actually kinda
scares me... I don't know.
Oh wow, I bet it looks
likes something straight
out of a sci-fi movie!
Yeah... But if I had
to be totally honest,
I liked it better before
they started messing
with this time travel stuff.
How come?
Well, I guess... 'cause
every time they use it,
it feels like
Okarin's further away.
This round table discussion
will now commence--
Me first, please!
Go on.
'Kay, Point of order...
Mayushii said she
wasn't cosplaying today,
but look at her.
She's not cosplaying...
That's her school uniform.
I just didn't feel
like changing out of it.
Ultra realism... Whoa...
Who knew it
could be... so...
That's enough, thank you.
Don't even finish your thought.
You are gonna eat, aren't ya?
Ah... Will you knock if off!
I'm trying to chair
a meeting here!
You told me to
bring everybody lunch.
I'm just doing
what you said.
Forgive him, sweetie.
He's just upset 'cause
he's not Sir Galahad.
The topic of discussion on
the lab docket for the day...
...happens to be
corporeal time travel!
Mayuri... Is there any
barley tea left in the fridge?
Mm-hmm. I think so.
Realism is awesome...
It's me...
The Organization has infiltrated
and demoralized my constituency.
I can't get a toe-hold on their
diminishing attention spans
with even the most
grandiose of proclamations...
So what's new, you guys?
You're each of you
barbarians for dismissing
so pregnant a topic out of hand!
It's a moot point.
If we can send
information to the past,
who's to say we can't--
I say.
Thirty six bytes of information
is our natural barrier.
Which means we're limited
to text... Plain and simple...
But if you think we
should try shoving
a whole person across that
boundary, go right ahead...
If you want to risk
turning into a Gel-Okarin.
Sounds pretty gross.
Someone got schooled.
Look, SERN's already established
how enormously difficult it is
to travel bodily through time.
Bear in mind,
if the world's largest particle
collider can't manage it...
What chances does a
souped up microwave have?
You act as though we
haven't seen what it can do.
No... I just don't know how...
What we do know is that
SERN's methods revolve around
the conjunction of a black
hole and some kind of lifter.
It's a fair assumption our setup
here works in the same manner...
It's also a fair assumption
that whatever's acting as our
lifter isn't the microwave.
So what is?
Who knows...?
Add to that the fact we can
only send out D-mails
at certain times...
I mean, come on; even for
a prototype what we've got
to work with here
is fairly rudimentary.
Until we know more...
We should keep the wishful
thinking at a minimum.
How typical.
Yeah, okay, reality check:
serious research isn't
always a wildlife safari...
If you profess to be a
scientist you should be prepar--
I am decidedly not a scientist!
I am a mad scientist!
Oh, for the love of...
Could you be more of a Wesley?
Uh... 'scuse me?
Were you... Referencing...?
Look, whatever you
think I took that from,
you're wrong, so just let it go!
Please try to stay focused!
Very well, back on point then.
Speaking of SERN,
what's our update on the intel
we've culled from
their internal server...?
Christina...
Madam... Next Gen!
I said leave it the hell alone!
Oh, going too boldly, am I?
Yes, you--
I have nothing
noteworthy to add.
I see... Kindly continue to
investigate then, Nurse Chapel.
Damn it, lay off!
So, Daru... How's the
hacking coming along?
I got ziltch, man. Sorry.
Until we can crack
the proprietary code
the companion
server's built on,
we're basically
spinning our wheels.
Is that not what the IBN is for?
You make it sound
like we got one on tap.
What are you saying?
I thought we'd, deciphered
the code already...
Uh... I'm good,
but not that good.
So what's become
of the 5100, then?!
Dude, how in the
frack should I know?!
Nonsense.
Okarin, what's the matter?
Okay... Level
with me, Christina.
Have we not located the
5100 and brought it here?
I... I don't see
how we could have...
We don't have the
first clue where one is.
Alright. Just for
the sake of argument
let's assume I believe you.
To reiterate: you say we got one
on loan from Rukako's father...?
Yes... Exactly.
You and I carried the
damn thing here ourselves.
Yet between the two of us,
you're the only one
with any memory of this...
Clearly our D-mails are
shifting things around.
Yeah... but so dramatically...?
I mean, broken down, the texts
we've been sending are trivial.
It's the Butterfly Effect.
In theory, even the
simplest interference
can cause world
lines to split...
From one where we didn't
buy a lottery ticket
to one where we did,
for example...
The facts of one world line
change ever so slightly,
and from there the
process just feeds on itself.
It's like shooting pool:
one ball hits two,
those hit two more
a piece, and so on.
Time travel's long
been associated
with this kind of risk.
So where's the IBN
in this world line?
No idea... Where was it?
No. No, you're right.
We had one.
I asked dad and he said we'd
been keeping it in storage.
Thing is... It disappeared.
I see...
Well?
No cigar...They did
in fact have one
as I remembered, but
apparently it's gone missing...
Great... Someone pilfered it...
Of course they
don't know when,
which means the
trail's gone cold.
So, a dead-end...
Well, I don't know
about anybody else,
but keeping a computer in a
shrine seems weird to me...
'Sides, who would've
known it was there?
Hey, Faris!
Yeah, what's up?
Well...
I've got all the questions
for tomorrow's maid swap here...
Ten of them outta do
the trick, don't you think?
Oooh. "If you could travel
back in time and redo one thing,
what would you chose and why?"
What would your answer be?
Oh, well, you know...
Past is past... I've never
really been one to dwell...
Like the feline,
my first and only concern is
with the moment I'm living right
now; taking pleasure in each--
Sorry. Excuse me for a second.
Meowrrlll, Faris speaking.
Kyouma... hey, what's up?
Is it true that you
once stored an IBN 5100
at the Yanabayashi
Shrine for safe keeping?
I didn't, no. But, I mean...
Well, dad had a bunch of old
computers, so maybe it was him.
Uh... Kyouma...
Be straight... Not that
it's any of my business,
but does this have to do
with you guys' time machine?
C'mon, don't be shy!
Is that what I think it is?!
Oh wow...! A real metal oopa!
Don't even think
about trying me.
You'll just lose it again.
Huh? What?
You can stand there if
you want. I've things to do.
Kay. Hang on a sec.
Hey, Daru!
Comin', hold up.
What is that?
Limited edition swag...
I've got zero impulse control...
Hey, like you say, boss...
When Stein's Gate opens,
the stout of heart are
there with cold hard cash.
It's not a comic book shop!
Why are you even here...?
You should be holding
down the fort...
You, too;
I do not like my assistant
to be there by herself.
To hell with a bunch
o' that, ass munch!
I'm not lettin' you drop in on
Faris at home without me there!
If Daru gets to tag along,
it's not fair if I can't!
I told you;
I'm not even sure why she
invited me in the first place.
Hey, it's Kirari!!!
Ah, not again...
Wait! Damn it all...
The IBN 5100...
Shining Finger!
I need to talk to you! Please!
Shining--! Moeka...!
Kiryuu Moeka!
Why...? I don't understand...
It's supposed to be here.
You...
The IBN... I...
heard you say--
Please... Do you
know where it is?!
No, I don't... I thought you...
You... You don't know?
Okarin...! Where's she going?
I don't know.
C'mon guys--
That girl really knows
how to wear clothes.
I've got to get her into
cosplay one of these days.
Yeah...
Hold on... Am I wrong
or are you talking like
the two of you have
met somewhere before?
Uh... because we have.
What... How...? When...? Where?!
You... brought her...
into... the... lab...
After Moeka sent her D-mail...
as far as the gang was
concerned, she never existed.
Now, though...
when Ruka sends one...
Moeka's somehow
back in the fold.
Every time D-mail gets used,
some detail about the
past drastically alters.
You sure we've got
the right address?
Pretty sure, yeah. Let's see...
It's on the top floor.
The young mistress
will be with you all
in just a moment...
Please wait here.
Well...
I suddenly realize why butler
cafes haven't really caught on.
I've never seen a
real live butler before!
Look! The people are
like ants from here...!
What a splendid view!
Oh dear...
We're never getting' him back.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah...! Hey there!
Faris out of her maid getup!
My life is officially complete!
Faris...!
Yes?
The opulence of
your living quarters
begs a rather obvious
question, do you not agree?
Ummmm... meow, meow, meow...!
Don't toy with me...!
Explain yourself or we
hereby part ways, madam!
You don't have to be so rude...
My family owns a great deal
of land here in Akihabara...
Most of it, as a matter of fact.
Wait, so like the
whole town is yours?
In a nutshell, yeah.
Uh... So I'm kinda confused...
She and the city have
the same name, kind of.
So, you know...
No...! I know her by
no other name but Faris!
Stop acting like
a petulant child.
It's quite alright, actually.
Moe culture thrives here
mostly because of my influence.
So it's a compliment.
Wha...?! You...?!
She has her finger on the
pulse of our generation, dude;
I've always said so!
The maid cafe is the wellspring
from which all manna flows!
I bow to her vision!
You're very sweet,
but I'll thank you not to
let the cat out of the
bag about all this...
I want everyone to treat me
like the same ol'
Faris they know and love.
I will take your
secret to my grave!
Thank you, meowster!
Can the cat lingo!
Where've you
secreted the IBN 5100!
Oh... I'm gonna get
to that... But first...
If you'd all be so kind,
I have a itty bitty
widdle favor to ask...
Ha! You intend to extort us?!
It's really not that big
of a deal, I promise you.
I'd, just like to use
D-mail for myself one time;
that's all I want. .
Why put a cap on it...?
You can send as
many as you like!
Hey...! Third party
access is not something
with which we're comfortable...
Yeah, okay. So we
make Faris a lab member
and it's not really
an issue anymore...
Out of the question, damn it!
It's just we don't yet
understand the consequences...!
Oh, I see... so we can
use it to win the lottery,
but Faris, that's
crossing the line...?!
That's some B.S., man!
She just wants to use it once.
Ugh. That's not
what this is about.
Wait... There's no guarantee
we'll be able to find
the 5100 again--if "again"
is even the right word now.
Faris may be able to help.
Very well...
But you may only use D-mail
on condition that you consent
to become a
full-fledged lab member!
As of this moment,
you are christened
Double-O Seven, Akiha Rumi--
Ahhh!! Shut up!
There. That oughtta do it.
And you're absolutely
certain you want
to send it back
in time ten years?
Oh yes. I'm sure.
So, what does it say?
Something... secret.
That is not how this works...!
As head of the
Future Gadgets Laboratory,
I have a right to know what
we're unleashing on the world--
Nyuh-uh...
Boys aren't allowed to pry
into a girl's private life!
You wouldn't want people reading
your text messages, would you?
Women's lib!
Okay, fine. Simply hit the send
button and the deed is done.
Hello?
Assistant... snap to!
I require a status report--
Is that your idea of manners?!
Glass house, much?
Ugh! That woman! Of all the...
Hello?
Hououin Kyouma
speaking, don't hang up.
Hououin...? Oh, it's you.
I thought I had a
stalker or something.
I show up on your caller ID!
So? For all
I knew a serial killer
could've gotten a
hold of your phone.
A veiled confession that Hououin
strikes fear into your hear--?
She does that one more
time I'm going to scream!
Bad connection, or what?
No. She's just a cold-hearted,
self-absorbed harpy!
Hello?
Now you listen to me!
Okabe Rintarou
calling for Makise.
Speaking.
Uh, yes. I was wondering
if I might impose upon you
to activate the Phone Wave
as per the settings laid out
in the prior text message--
that is, if I'm not interrupting
anything important, of course.
Now that is how
to be civilized...
I see why you don't
do it often, though.
You sound like a twelve year
old when you talk like that...
Incidentally, don't you
think it's time we stopped
calling it the
Phone Wave? I mean...
Ugh! I'm not polite
often because
A.) I'm a mad scientist
and B.) you're not worthy--
The two of them
have something going?
Sometimes they have a
little trouble getting along.
So, kinda. Yeah.
Will you send?
You know...
Maybe... This isn't
such a good idea...
Faris.
We have full discharge...
Go for it now!
Hello?
Who are you?
Huh?
Daddy!
"Daddy?" Kyouma wasn't
bothering you, was he?
No... Sorry to run,
but I've got to be on my way...
it was a pleasure
meeting you, though.
Wow.
Your dad seems like a really
sophisticated type of guy.
Duh. He raised Faris.
He's gotta be like a secret
super hero or something.
Uh, Sir...?
Are you familiar with the
IBN 5100 by any chance?
Well, there's a name
that takes me back decades.
You have one?
Oh, I'm afraid I jettisoned
mine quite some time ago.
Do you remember if you happened
to "donate" it to the
Yanabayashi Shrine...?
Sorry. I'm not even
familiar with the name...
Well good day to you all.
Okay, so before
Faris sent her D-mail...
the shrine'd had
the IBN in storage,
but it'd gone missing...
But now... apparently it was
never taken there to begin with.
Every time we send a
message to the past,
things get shifted around...
For every detail that changes...
how many are out there
that I have no knowledge of?
Oh god... What if things
can't be shifted back...?
What if we've gone too far?
kisei sareta chikai mujihi naru, juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
Earth to Okarin!
Snap out of it, silly;
I wanna stop in Nakano
before we head home to get an
Ai Sword doujinshi, 'member?
Wait, Nakano...?
You can't be serious.
You do know Nakano's not
exactly on the way home?
Yeah... Sure be nice
if they opened up a shop
around here someday
where I could buy one.
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
Have you lost your senses...?!
Our backyard is
lousy with such--
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
You're a real
goofball sometimes.
Forgotten where we live, dude?
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten